Hi. Hello.
你好。 你好。
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
你好。 你好。 你好。 你好。
Oh, my God. Hold on. Give me a second.
我的天啊。 坚持，稍等。 你稍等一会儿。
Your Hey, guys.
你们的嘿，伙计们。
What's up?
怎么了？
Um, so I wanted to talk about our new set
嗯，所以我想快速谈谈我们在 R 上的新设置，嗯。
What's it called? The bedroom. Yeah. Right.
这叫什么？ 卧室。 是的。 对。
So I thought it'd be very cool to, you know, change some things up
所以我认为改变一些东西让它看起来更漂亮会很酷。
So that's why I've been spending the past,
所以这就是为什么我一直在度过过去，
you know, couple of hours doing it looks really cool.
你知道，几个小时做这件事看起来真的很酷。
Also, if you do, what's it called?
另外，如果你这样做，它叫什么？
If you do a, um.
如果你做一个，嗯。
If somebody gifts.
如果有人送礼。
I think. Was it.
我认为。 是吗。
I forgot what the thing was.
我忘了那是什么东西。
If somebody donates, like, more than 50
如果有人捐赠，比如，超过 50
and then or, like, more than 1000 bits,
然后，或者，像，超过 1000 位，
or if a raid happens something special or something cool pops up on the screen.
或者如果突袭发生了一些特别的事情或者屏幕上弹出了一些很酷的东西。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Let me show you guys because I think, you know, it'd be really cool to show.
让我向你们展示，因为我认为，你知道，展示它真的很酷。
Let me just show you instead.
让我来给你看。
So no one has to like, you know, do anything thing.
所以没有人必须喜欢，你知道，做任何事情。
I think it's really cool. Uh,
我认为这真的很酷。 呃，
I'm just.
我只是。
It looks super sick, dude.
看起来超级恶心，伙计。
Oh, my gosh. Look.
天啊。 看。
Look at that.
看那个。
Yeah. I don't know who did it.
是的。 我不知道是谁干的。
But. Yeah, so the new alerts are a full screen thingy
但。 是的，所以新的警报是全屏的
which pops up depending on how much you donate.
这取决于你捐赠了多少。
So people that donate like 1000 bits or over $50 or, um,
所以捐赠 1000 比特或超过 50 美元的人，或者，嗯，
I think if somebody reads, they'll have like that special alert
我想如果有人阅读，他们会像视频游戏叠加效果一样在屏幕上弹出特殊警报。
And I think that's really sick.
我认为这真的很恶心。
Yeah, it's really cool, right?
是的，真的很酷，对吧？
I like it so much on all of these assets.
我非常喜欢所有这些资产。
I got R for free from my friends are free RAF
我从朋友那里免费获得 R 是免费的 RAF
from Ushio and Wonder Penguin
来自 Ushio 和 Wonder Penguin
Oh, thank you for the bits, Joss.
哦，谢谢你，乔斯。
Thank you so much, dude.
非常感谢你，伙计。
Yeah, it's really cool.
是的，真的很酷。
It's actually, it feels actually like a video game.
实际上，它实际上就像一个视频游戏。
It's called the Great Sage Streamer on Arts Online Puck.
它被称为艺术在线冰球上的大圣流光。
So if you guys are interested, it's, ah, it's out there
所以，如果你们有兴趣，它，啊，它仍然在那里供其他人使用。
I just want to use it myself because I thought it was pretty darn cool.
我只是想自己使用它，因为我认为它非常酷。
So today we're going to be playing Wafaa,
所以今天我们要玩Wafaa，或者我和Lily一起玩。
Oh, let me see. Playing with Lily.
哦，让我看看。 和莉莉一起玩。
Shoo!
嘘！
Albert's scar.
阿尔伯特的伤疤。
And then that's it.
然后就是这样。
Yeah, we're playing with a lot of people today, and I'm super ex-army.
是的，我们今天和很多人一起玩，我是超级前军人。
Invites shoo in a means of a party
以派对的方式邀请shoo
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Yeah. I'm like.
是的。 我长得像。
We were, like, um, very last minute with
我们就像，嗯，最后一分钟，因为每个人都在做自己的事情。
It was, like, only me and all Kate.
就像，只有我和所有的凯特。
We're getting cute in. Hold up.
我们越来越可爱了。等一下。
Ah, Bella. Shopping for the gift solves.
啊，贝拉。 买礼物就解决了。
Thank you for all the bits, guys, and for the.
感谢所有的位，伙计们，以及。
I'll try and read through everything at the end of stream America.
我将尝试在流美国结束时通读所有内容。
I see it, so.
我看到了，所以。
Hold on. Let me.
坚持，稍等。 让我来。
Let me turn on my
让我打开我的
way. I'm on. Right. Hello?
方式。 我在。 对。 你好？
Oh, there you go.
哦，给你。
Hello, y'all. Sorry.
大家好。 对不起。
Yeah, I just want to a chat real quick.
是的，我只想快速聊天。
What's up?
怎么了？
We're just.
我们是正义的。
We're just in the lobby.
我们只是在大厅里。
Oh, my God. My building is like, 85, four.
我的天啊。 我的大楼是 85 号楼，4 号楼。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I we're playing California. Okay? That's what.
我在玩加利福尼亚。 好的？ 就是这样。
I did.
我做到了。
I saw around
我看到周围
where we are.
我们在哪里。
We maybe Central. Rudy Central.
我们也许是中央。 鲁迪中央。
It's like, you know, even it out, I think.
就像，你知道的，即使它，我想。
Okay.
好的。
Central.
中央。
Well, our. You've been.
嗯，我们的。 你去过。
You've been fucking climbing.
你他妈一直在爬。
You kind of just running up the ladder.
你只是跑上梯子。
Yes. I'm trying very hard to get better.
是的。 我正在努力变得更好。
Okay. Oh.
好的。 哦。
Max. And.
最大限度。 和。
Oh, by the way, nice to meet you. I'm Shu.
哦，顺便说一句，很高兴认识你。 我是舒
Hello, Shu. I'm pleased. To meet. You.
你好，舒。 我很满意。 见面。 你。
Oh, you're both.
哦，你们俩都是。
I already said that. I
我已经说过了。 一世
Oh, well, you didn't differ my strength.
哦，好吧，你并没有改变我的力量。
It's nice to meet you guys.
很高兴认识你们。
Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你。
Shu finally gets a couple of.
舒终于得到了几个。
Oh, my gosh. Yeah, she's finally there.
天啊。 是的，她终于来了。
Yeah, I tell you something.
是的，我告诉你一件事。
Together.
一起。
What's up? Off dream we have.
怎么了？ 我们有梦想。
Yeah, we.
是的，我们。
Played Florence off stream,
播放了 Florence
but we haven't gone, so doing an actual collab just yet.
的直播，但我们还没有离开，所以还要做一个真正的合作。
Alexander's our first one. Yeah. Wow. Yeah.
亚历山大是我们的第一个。 是的。 哇。 是的。
Yeah, he
是的，他
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
It was so. Big.
就是这样。 大的。
I can't play Viper.
我玩不了蝰蛇。
I'm, like, literally in a maple to.
我就像，从字面上看，在枫树中。
Like.
像。
Go play arena.
去打竞技场。
And that way we're playing on Breeze Okay.
这样我们就可以在 Breeze Okay 上玩了。
Ah, I'm not tired of this game.
啊，我不厌倦这个游戏。
Just if I look over.
只要我看过去。
Oh, here we're playing. Yeah. It's all good.
哦，我们在玩。 是的。 这一切都很好。
This is my first time playing ranked.
这是我第一次玩排位赛。
And I can't.
而我不能。
Yeah, we are fucking omega.
是的，我们是他妈的omega。
Carrie. Albert
嘉莉。 阿尔伯特
has been coached, like, three times.
已经被执教了三遍。
Oh, coached oh.
哦，调教了哦。
We hired a sexy coach.
我们聘请了一位性感的教练。
Okay, hold on.
好的坚持住。
Let me put.
让我放。
You know, I've got the arena.
你知道，我有竞技场。
I'm comfortable for.
我很舒服。
Her. OK.
她。 好的。
You guys, you listen to music when you play violent, by the way, or. No.
顺便说一句，你们玩暴力的时候听音乐，或者。 不。
I think it's more entertaining, but it's a bit harder to focus.
我认为它更有趣，但它有点难以集中。
Yeah, it.
是的，它。
Is. Yeah.
是。 是的。
Like, I cannot focus with music.
就像，我无法专注于音乐。
Because, like, the footsteps still. Yeah.
因为，喜欢，脚步还在。 是的。
It's like there's a
就像有很多我学到的音频提示一样，好的，我必须，
like, look out for that.
喜欢，注意那个。
A guy cranking music up. OK.
一个把音乐调高的人。 好的。
Yes. Yes.
是的。 是的。
If you crank it up, the fade like death in doesn't even matter
如果你加快速度，像死亡一样的淡出甚至都无关紧要
you just get used to it.
你只是习惯了。
You know what, you're, you're right.
你知道吗，你是，你是对的。
The ability doesn't matter.
能力无所谓。
Claim playing every round cause I can't.
声称玩每一轮，因为我不能。
Oh, actually.
哦，其实。
Oh, cover the mass.
哦，掩盖群众。
Yeah.
是的。
Um, where I'm like I'm going to, I'll sit and tube
嗯，我想去的地方，我会坐着管
It's a tube. Yeah. OK, yeah.
它是一个管子。 是的。 好的，是的。
Whatever this is called, I call it tube because it's a long tube.
不管这叫什么，我称它为管，因为它是一个长管。
Right?
对？
Oh, let me see.
哦，让我看看。
It's like to put up
就像放
literally stream it.
从字面上流它。
Or you're still setting up your shoe.
或者您仍在设置鞋子。
Shop because.
购物，因为。
I was like, oh, wait, we're going to the server.
我当时想，哦，等等，我们要去服务器。
So I was like, Okay, sure.
所以我想，好吧，当然。
I mean, be it to be. Okay.
我的意思是，就这样吧。 好的。
Everything okay?
一切都好？
I'm coming. I'm coming. They're coming.
我来了。 我来了。 他们来了。
Oh, they are all pushed in.
哦，都被挤进去了。
What the heck? Oh.
有没有搞错？ 哦。
Phoenix at 78.
78岁的凤凰。
Spike planted.
穗种植。
Lot to.
很多。
Nice to nice to.
很高兴。
Chamberlain 26.
张伯伦 26.
It's iPad.
它是 iPad。
Is it all right you.
你没事吧。
All. Yeah.
全部。 是的。
One that's on the back side.
一个在背面。
If you can approach the bum now
如果你现在可以接近流浪汉
we actually get low on time.
实际上，我们的准时率很低。
Type it.
键入它。
Nice. Nice.
好的。 好的。
Nice job, guys.
干得好，伙计们。
Nice.
好的。
It's nice.
很好。
Nice, nice, good. First round.
不错不错不错不错 第一回合。
Oh, my. Yeah.
天啊。 是的。
My knees are going to kill after this.
在这之后我的膝盖要死了。
Watch so much kitty.
看这么多小猫。
He always says whenever every rally we went out, we were out.
他总是说，每次我们出去的时候，我们都出去了。
We went out that we.
我们出去了，我们。
Now I have to have this. Set up still.
现在我必须拥有这个。 静置。
Holy shit.
天啊。
To do.
去做。
This in between rounds.
这在两轮之间。
Well, see, right?
嗯，看，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
So. Oh, my God. Oh, yeah.
所以。 我的天啊。 哦耶。
So easy game.
这么简单的游戏。
Easy life do you might be here.
轻松的生活，你可能在这里。
I'm looking to.
我正在寻找。
I don't see anything yet.
我还没有看到任何东西。
They might just be going through
他们可能只是在经历
there.
那里。
They're just rushing in there.
他们只是冲进去。
That person.
那人。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, gosh.
哦，天哪。
Oh, I'm curious for you, Holly.
哦，我对你很好奇，霍莉。
I'm going to this the flashing.
我要去这个闪烁。
There.
那里。
I got for.
我得到了。
Me remaining here.
我留在这里。
A flawless,
完美无瑕，
flawless.
完美无瑕。
Okay, everyone here again.
好的，大家又来了。
I'm apparently gold one I don't know.
我显然是黄金之一，我不知道。
How you higher than I thought.
你怎么比我想象的高。
Not that I thought any. Well.
不是我想的。 好。
Well.
好。
I know it's because I'm just so used to like me.
我知道这是因为我太习惯喜欢我了。
Uh huh. Yeah. Explain yourself.
嗯。 是的。 解释你自己。
Playing with, like, people.
和人一起玩。
My era.
我的时代。
I'm like, from.
我喜欢，从。
It's like when I whenever I like.
就像我喜欢的时候一样。
I honestly think I shouldn't be here.
老实说，我认为我不应该在这里。
But it's not you. It's me.
但不是你。 是我。
You. I'm used to being my.
你。 我习惯了成为我的人。
Well, I'm sorry.
好吧，我很抱歉。
I forgot to buy another flash. I'm dumb.
我忘了再买一个闪光灯。 我好蠢。
I know.
我知道。
Oh. Oh, to all.
哦。 哦，对所有人。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
There's you all. OK, watch out.
你们都有。 好的，小心。
They might be pushing up your wallet. Maybe.
他们可能会推高你的钱包。 也许。
Yeah.
是的。
And mine try to want it meant.
而我的尝试想要它的意思。
I think Kaitlyn's arm was it in a corner.
我想凯特琳的胳膊在角落里。
OK, Well, that's good, because we more up Oh.
OK，恩，那就好，因为我们比较起来哦。
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
是的。 哦耶。
That was
那是
yeah.
是的。
Yeah. Oh.
是的。 哦。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
You see him? He was so tiny. Oh, yeah.
你看见他了吗？ 他是如此渺小。 哦耶。
Small boy.
小男孩。
Stand tall. We evaluate.
站得高高的。 我们评估。
We say, OK, because we save.
我们说，好吧，因为我们保存。
Now we're in a good spot.
现在我们处于一个好位置。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
That's true. That's true.
那是真实的。 那是真实的。
Yeah. This is the. Yeah. OK.
是的。 这是。 是的。 好的。
I think that's a good little spot for you guys that.
我认为这对你们来说是一个很好的小地方。
I didn't know. You played your Ruby. Lily did.
我不知道。 你玩了你的Ruby。 莉莉做到了。
I'm like, oh, you should.
我想，哦，你应该。
Come.
来。
For real.
真的。
No cap on God.
上帝没有上限。
Oh, no cap on God.
哦，上帝没有上限。
Yeah, no cap on a stack.
是的，堆栈上没有上限。
She Boston respectfully.
她恭敬地波士顿。
A oh again.
又是一个哦。
A oh vipers. Maybe one or two.
哦，毒蛇。 也许一两个。
Oh, that was messed up.
哦，那是一团糟。
That well, but.
那好吧，但是。
In a long. Way.
在长。 方式。
I'm going to people.
我要去人家。
It's okay.
没关系。
That means they have less space to go through.
这意味着他们可以通过的空间更少。
It's gonna work out.
它会成功的。
Or are they they just plain default Maybe.
或者他们只是普通的默认可能。
I think maybe I'll watch B, I'll watch B, they might be up
我想也许我会看B，我会看B，他们可能会起来
there in a, like, pyramid.
在一个，像，金字塔。
Corner.
角落。
Let me flash them the place by Clint.
让我用克林特把他们闪到那个地方。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, God.
天啊。
All in flash.
一切尽在眼前。
All right.
好的。
We should all go at the same time.
我们都应该同时去。
I'm an old friend.
我是老朋友。
Follow if you want.
如果你愿意，请关注。
Oh, man.
天啊。
She's won the money. She's won three.
她赢了钱。 她赢了三场。
I don't know why I'm pressing that.
我不知道我为什么要按那个。
Let's go. Oh.
我们走吧。 哦。
Nice.
好的。
Oh, hey.
噢！嗨。
Nice, nice, nice shots.
不错不错，拍的不错。
Not to
不
put you guys
把你们
the enemy.
敌人。
Is there a way to make extreme kill, like,
有没有办法让极端杀戮，比如，水平？
Oh, I have a ceasefire. Ok.
哦，我有停火协议。 行。
Oh, you do? Can you share that with me later?
哦，你会吗？ 以后可以分享给我吗？
Just right click it and then rotate 90 degrees.
只需右键单击它，然后旋转 90 度。
Oh, that's that's that also works.
哦，那就是那也有效。
I could d empty Yeah. Yeah.
我可以清空是的。 是的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I'm going to opt out.
我将选择退出。
OK, listen.
好的，听着。
Wait. You guys have the same name, your shoe and show.
等待。 你们有相同的名字，你的鞋子和表演。
Oh, it looks like b there's a wall.
哦，看起来好像有一堵墙。
There's some big. Games.
有一些大 游戏。
Yeah, it's getting personal toll.
是的，这是个人损失。
Yeah. So is everyone here?
是的。 所以大家都在吗？
I only every. Single person here.
我只有每一个。 一个人在这里。
Oh, ok. I'm running. I'm running.
哦好的。 我在跑步。 我在跑步。
Kyle. Oh, Kyle's down. Nice oh, my God.
凯尔。 哦，凯尔倒下了。 不错哦，我的上帝。
Your tracksuit?
你的运动服？
Yeah.
是的。
One day show two visited my stream, and I said, hi, shoe.
一天节目二访问了我的直播，我说，嗨，鞋子。
He actually called the shoe.
他实际上打电话给鞋子。
It was crazy.
这太疯狂了。
I didn't expect that It's crazy.
我没想到这很疯狂。
You want to know?
你要知道？
Oh, no. Oh, it's not.
不好了。 哦，不是的。
We don't need to pick. OK.
我们不需要挑选。 好的。
I haven't.
我没有。
We have a flight coming and going. So let's chillax, shall we?
我们有一班飞机来来去去。 所以让我们放松一下，好吗？
Don't want to pick that guy is scary with that.
不想挑那个家伙是吓人的。
He's going to eat your arse.
他要吃掉你的屁股。
Look, is there someone behind us?
看，我们后面有人吗？
It was window.
那是窗户。
Another was. You sure? Okay. Okay.
另一个是。 你确定？ 好的。 好的。
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
Oh, less fun. Yeah. Well.
哦，少了些乐趣。 是的。 好。
This is here. OK, he's flying back.
这是这里。 好吧，他飞回来了。
Kill him.
杀了他。
All right, let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
Oh. Oh, OK.
哦。 哦好的。
I hope. They're OK.
我希望。 他们都还好。
They won't expect the heat from the side
他们不会期望来自闪光灯侧面的热量。 那么你。
Oh, then you know.
哦，那你知道的。
Yesterday. God. Oh, they don't know that one, though.
昨天。 上帝。 哦，虽然他们不知道那个。
Beautiful skin.
美丽的皮肤。
Wait, what?
等等，什么？
What the fuck happen?
他妈的发生了什么？
This is fun.
这很好玩。
Who needs training dummies.
谁需要训练假人。
When you have of weird.
当你有奇怪的。
Well, let me.
好吧，让我。
Oh, actually, doesn't matter.
哦，其实，无所谓。
You're rich.
你好有钱。
Scary if you want.
如果你愿意，可怕。
Like a gun gun, like mature gun, gun.
像枪炮，像成熟的枪，枪。
But here
但在这儿
what's your cause?
你的原因是什么？
The same thing I. Just wanted, you know?
和我一样。只是想要，你知道吗？
You want me to pay for it?
你要我付钱吗？
Yeah. Tax put on the company. Credit card.
是的。 对公司征税。 信用卡。
I agree. You know.
我同意。 你知道。
Eat the rich.
多吃富含。
The rich.
富人。
You're a.
你是一个。
I hear. I don't hear anything.
我听见。 我什么也没听到。
How did they got fucking hit me?
他们他妈是怎么打我的？
Oh, there's one, two, one, two.
哦，有，一，二，一，二。
Oh. It's two.
哦。 是两个。
But holes.
但是坑。
Yeah, it's holes.
对，就是坑。
It's all that is called. It's you wants to be. Ah.
这就是所谓的一切。 是你想成为的。 啊。
Let me help you out here. I'm ordering.
让我在这里帮你。 我正在订购。
Nice. Nice.
好的。 好的。
Reloading.
重新加载。
I'm going back to be.
我要回来了。
Yeah, they're not here, but there's just the one, dude. Oh.
是的，他们不在这里，但只有一个，伙计。 哦。
Okay. Only
好的。 仅有的
oh, man.
天啊。
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
哦，不错，不错，不错。
In there with.
在那里与。
Where would they be?
他们会在哪里？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Oh. Oh, middle.
哦。 哦，中间。
Yeah.
是的。
Go look mad. Hold on.
去看看疯了。 坚持，稍等。
One be.
一个是。
Yeah.
是的。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
Oh. Oh, nice. Nice
哦。 不错哦。 进攻不错。
I'll run out and run out of nice ways.
我会用尽所有好方法。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Clean. Clean.
干净的。 干净的。
I got him a luxury. Toyota. What's.
我给他买了个奢侈品。 丰田。 什么是。
Oh, what does that mean?
哦，那是什么意思？
Creature I think.
我认为的生物。
What a fancy way to say. Creature.
多么花哨的说法。 生物。
What language?
什么语言？
That's Spanish.
那是西班牙语。
Oh, I know some Spanish.
哦，我懂一些西班牙语。
I'm not crazy.
我没疯。
I wonder if I am going to cop out.
我想知道我是否会逃避。
Oh, hold on.
哦，等一下。
Laurent. Drop
劳伦特。 降低
Thank you.
谢谢你。
That's
那是
nice.
好的。
Nice, nice.
好好。
You know the cook?
你认识厨师吗？
I've got.
我有。
A leave.
请假。
A little bit of an opening. OK.
有点开口。 好的。
I like.
我喜欢。
Openings.
开口。
I to be.
我要。
This one be.
这一个。
Oh. Nice shot. It.
哦。 好球。 它。
I can't hold me. I can't hold me.
我抱不动我。 我抱不动我。
I don't see them in my tube.
我没有在我的试管中看到它们。
They didn't come to my tube, but
他们没有来我的管子，但是
Oh. Sorry.
哦。 对不起。
I see I mid.
我看我中。
One tunnel. The.
一个隧道。 这。
One on site. Here.
现场一个。 这里。
You've got this shoe shine crispy shot.
你有这个擦鞋香脆的镜头。
Oh, not about trade.
哦，不是关于贸易。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, a setup.
嗯，一个设置。
Fuck. Who
他妈的。 谁
I don't
我不
I don't know.
我不知道。
Where are they where they go.
他们去哪里。
Oh they go a certain way.
哦，他们走了一条特定的路。
You want a. Oh.
你想要一个。 哦。
All right.
好的。
Billy trade
比利贸易
Skara let him die first and then you go with the kill.
斯卡拉让他先死，然后你去杀。
Oh, wait. I
等一下。 一世
oh tackle bomb press.
哦，解决炸弹新闻。
Line-Up Line-ups.
排队排队。
You guys have the bomb maker use it.
你们让炸弹制造者使用它。
They're probably both in there.
他们可能都在里面。
You need to push is going to line it up.
您需要推动将其排成一行。
Go get Emily.
去找艾米丽。
All right. Oh.
好的。 哦。
Ha, ha. 70 pin.
哈哈。  70针。
Stick it.
坚持到底。
I got you. I got you. I got your.
我接到你了。 我接到你了。 我得到了你的。
Oh, let's go.
哦，我们走吧。
Oh, we I got me up.
哦，我们让我起来了。
Oh, no, oh, no.
哦，不，哦，不。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
哦，哦，哦，哦。
Blast the first.
先爆一波。
Nice try.
不错的尝试。
Nice try. Nice try. Attention.
不错的尝试。 不错的尝试。 注意力。
I learnt something.
我学到了一些东西。
As close
尽可能接近
where they like to push more often.
他们喜欢更频繁地推动的地方。
Air bees.
空气蜜蜂。
Rules.
规则。
But yeah.
但是，是的。
They go everywhere.
他们到处走。
I'm going to Washington this time.
这次我要去华盛顿。
Can song cover my to go trend up.
歌曲可以覆盖我的趋势。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Anti anti anti.
反反反。
Coming.
未来。
O are them there.
哦，他们在那里。
When they 28.
当他们 28.
Oh ones elbow.
哦，肘部。
Ooh. My bed good luck.
哦。 我的床祝你好运。
Oh or you looking at the mouth I got distracted.
哦，或者你看着我分心的嘴。
Due to a two or three I'm running. OK.
由于一个两三个我正在运行。 好的。
I think I.
我想我。
Spike planted what. We.
斯派克种了什么。 我们。
I'm giving up mid I'm giving up mid hold on
我放弃了中途 我放弃了中途 坚持
All right.
好的。
For a long time I just try
很长一段时间，我只是想赢。
01 I think
01 我认为
that player standing.
那个球员站着。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, wait, no.
哦，等等，不。
Oh, I'm flying to you know what to do.
哦，我飞到你知道该怎么做。
And I'll.
我会的。
I jump of a box into the you like my still for fun
我跳进你喜欢我的盒子里，为了好玩，他开枪打死了我。
Yeah. Glad.
是的。 高兴的。
I can buy you. Goodbye me OK.
我可以给你买。 再见我好。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Gracias.
格拉西亚斯。
I'm leaving you to defend me this time I'm gonna fish out
我要离开你来保护我，这次我要用刀钓鱼。
Which you Watkins can do.
你沃特金斯能做到的。
You have.
你有。
Uh, I have, like, one share of skin.
呃，我有，就像，一份皮肤。
That's about it.
就是这样。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Do you want my back?
你想要我的背吗？
I was thinking of wearing
本来想穿
this to it.
这个给它。
Nice.
好的。
Good job talking with me to see if there's one.
干得好，和我谈谈，看看有没有。
You still down?
你还下来？
Nice.
好的。
Well, then that last one, I think it's on.
好吧，那么最后一个，我想它已经打开了。
Sony. And he's on Target on site already.
索尼。 他已经在 Target 现场。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I'll flash
我会闪
the flash gun
闪光枪
is he's left side pyramids, or he might rotate it out.
他是左边的金字塔，还是他可能把它旋转出来。
Nice job.
不错的工作。
Hey. Oh,
嘿。 哦，
nice shot.
好球。
Oh, yeah. When you do well, you like it.
哦耶。 当你做得好的时候，你喜欢它。
But when you do.
但是当你这样做的时候。
It, just think.
它，只是想想。
Yeah, I if I am as bad of a day, I just slap
是的，如果我一天也这么糟糕，我只会一巴掌。
I could buy.
我可以买。
And when you sit.
当你坐着的时候。
On next and it.
在下一个和它。
Gotcha.
明白了。
I can buy for you even though I should probably.
我可以为你买，即使我应该买。
Know I.
知道我。
Like you a lot some let's whatever you pay me
像你很多人一样，让我们​​以后付钱给我。 不
yeah yeah yeah
耶耶耶
small pause before he's out of that
在他离开之前稍作停顿，他是那个家伙，是的，是的。
Play.
玩。
OK. Three people it just got pixels and Marshall's.
好的。 三个人，它刚刚得到像素和马歇尔的。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
So then Marshall.
那么马歇尔。
I'm going to push them.
我要推他们。
Without a line-up.
无需排队。
No, I just checked it.
没有，我刚查过。
Was it good.
怎么样？好吗。
Oh. What's going on?
哦。 到底是怎么回事？
Oh, how did it get there?
哦，它是怎么到那里的？
Did he see if you have my where are they?
他有没有看到你有我的他们在哪里？
Oh, they're playing b, plan b, b b b ok.
哦，他们在玩 b，plan b，b b b ok。
OK. Yeah.
好的。 是的。
And they often beat you way.
他们经常打败你。
At flashes for their smoke cut away.
他们的烟雾一闪而过。
I'll throw some in there.
我会在那里扔一些。
Oh, that's that's that's the photo decoy.
哦，那是那是照片诱饵。
I didn't fall for it.
我没有上当。
They're top the bomb if you can't one.
如果你不能，他们就是炸弹。
An enemy remaining.
剩下一个敌人。
Everybody is going together.
大家一起去。
Shouldn't be at all for her.
根本不应该适合她。
But she's out. Oh, that's my backside.
但是她出去了。 哦，那是我的背影。
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
Nice, nice, nice. Find my. I think you can.
不错不错不错不错 找到我的。 我想你可以。
Only hold until
只等到
you're off.
你走了。
On a but it's just a visit.
但它只是一次访问。
With you with what's died. Now.
和你一起死去的东西。 现在。
Where did you die?
你死在哪里？
I died back set, but they probably grabbed it and ran somewhere.
我死了，但他们可能抓住了它并跑到了某个地方。
Oh, it's right. Oh, there it is.
哦，对了。 哦，是的。
I got this OK. We know the drill.
我明白了。 我们知道演习。
Stick your.
坚持你的。
Butt. That's my eyes.
屁股。 那是我的眼睛。
The announcers. Thanks.
播音员。 谢谢。
I can buy me.
我可以买我。
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it was your op, and I killed the person who killed you.
是的，我很确定这是你的行动，我杀了杀你的人。
Hmm. This op has lived for, like, five rounds now.
唔。 这个操作现在已经活了五轮。
Nice. And got all this round.
好的。 并得到了所有这一轮。
I think in his.
我认为在他的。
Defender sided not versus in soccer sided.
防守方不支持足球。
I have no idea.
我不知道。
Colour
颜色
I, I could roll my eyes like that.
我，我可以这样翻白眼。
I'm a viper sighted bad.
我是毒蛇，视力不好。
I'm going to be. You know what you're
我将会是。 你知道你是什么
all right.
好的。
That character's cracked here.
那个角色在这里被破解了。
Oh, shoot.
哦，开枪。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Nice to be along a flash history.
很高兴成为一个闪光的历史。
Oh, I was.
哦，我是。
Here long day with.
在这里度过漫长的一天。
Got one like the other.
得到一个和另一个一样。
OK. Careful when you enter.
好的。 进门时要小心。
I'm holding in.
我正在坚持。
Oh, they're all back there.
哦，他们都回来了。
Oh the 39.
哦，39。
Awesome Smith wife
令人敬畏的史密斯妻子
I sure I got your back.
我确定我得到了你的支持。
OK she has 110 life.
好吧，她有 110 条生命。
110 think that's.
110认为是。
Oh looks like.
哦，看起来。
Yeah.
是的。
Spike planted
穗种植
I almost died. I'm going to hide.
我差点死掉。 我要躲起来。
Oh OK
哦好的
nice.
好的。
That if you. Yeah you can.
那如果你。 是的，你可以。
Sweets thank you you go for you
糖果谢谢你为你加油
whoo.
哇。
Let's go
我们走吧
last round in the half.
半场最后一轮。
01 final.
01决赛。
We lose it anyway.
无论如何，我们都会失去它。
Thing
事物
all right Albert.
好吧，艾伯特。
Show to me
给我看
what show.
什么秀。
Show me the collection.
给我看看收藏。
The collection.
集合。
Collection
收藏
since the last round. The me.
自上一轮以来。 主题。
I mean, you want. This gun, I. Will.
我的意思是，你想要。 这把枪，我。威尔。
I'm holding out. I'm holding.
我坚持。 我抱着。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
You can give you you. You deserve. Please.
你可以给你。 你应得的。 请。
So we want to play. Let's play.
所以我们想玩。 让我们玩。
Yeah, I do want to get a skin. I just don't.
是的，我确实想要皮肤。 我只是不知道。
Oh, that's not once in the marquee. Yeah.
哦，这不是一次在选框。 是的。
Oh, you.
哦，你。
Yeah.
是的。
That's way I'd like it was peaking on the other side.
这就是我希望它在另一边达到顶峰的方式。
So where are they?
那么他们在哪里呢？
One was to pressure.
一是施压。
Yeah.
是的。
Chamber has four shots on his off now.
钱伯尔现在有四次射门。
Four is. Up.
四是。 向上。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
There's one made. There's one made. They crossed into the elbow.
做了一个。 做了一个。 他们越过肘部。
There might be be no one might be be altered.
可能没有人会被改变。
To humid.
要潮湿。
Well, I'm a card.
好吧，我是一张卡片。
From a flash.
从一闪而过。
Oh God.
天啊。
There's two out there. Oh.
外面有两个。 哦。
I mean Chambers. Amy.
我是说钱伯斯。 艾米。
We have, we have Spike. We have Spike. We can play with Spike.
我们有，我们有斯派克。 我们有斯派克。 我们可以和斯派克一起玩。
We just saw let them push us
我们刚刚看到让他们推动我们
j'accuse.
指责。
Oh, closer to you.
哦，离你更近了。
I can watch to hold onto.
我可以看着坚持下去。
Oh, powerless
哦，无能为力
ok. I see a lot of action.
行。 我看到很多动作。
This is not a good space.
这不是一个好的空间。
Oh. 30 seconds.
哦。  30秒。
Oh, he's 18.
哦，他18岁。
One enemy remaining.
剩下一个敌人。
Nice area.
不错的地区。
Nice Jones guys they used.
他们使用的尼斯琼斯家伙。
All right, you still.
好吧，你还是。
I got it inside my eyes.
我把它放进了我的眼睛里。
Switching sides.
换边。
You guys are kind of.
你们有点儿
Dude, I.
伙计，我。
I took a two hour.
我花了两个小时。
Now, before this, I had free McDonald's.
现在，在此之前，我有免费的麦当劳。
Oh, I feel like so ready to take on the world.
哦，我觉得我已经准备好迎接这个世界了。
Oh, shoes. See? Chicken nuggets.
哦，鞋子。 看？ 鸡块。
Yes, I did.
是的，我做到了。
I always get it.
我总是明白。
Like, I might as well since they're back home.
就像，我还不如因为他们回家了。
I always like those ones better than the regulars.
我总是比常客更喜欢那些。
Yeah. So good.
是的。 超好的。
I like a lot of these places. You guys.
我喜欢很多这样的地方。 你们。
Team meeting. Team meeting.
团队会议。 团队会议。
Hello? Hello. Hello.
你好？ 你好。 你好。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
So, Sage Shu, I want you to wall in our right side.
所以，舒圣，我要你挡在我们的右边。
I'm going to dash into a smoke and then start planting.
我要冲进烟雾，然后开始种植。
You guys just burst on the site and cover me.
你们只是在网站上爆发并掩护我。
I'm triple smart.
我聪明三倍。
I was excited. Yeah. Yep.
我很兴奋。 是的。 是的。
OK, now we can only play B because we don't have viper.
好的，现在我们只能玩B，因为我们没有毒蛇。
OK, so I'm serious.
好的，所以我是认真的。
I don't have to.
我不必。
Go back so fast. I have no flashes.
回去这么快。 我没有闪光灯。
I'm going in.
我要进去了。
Oh, i'm low.
哦，我很低落。
I'm low and low.
我又低又低。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I'm a god of dog.
我是狗神。
I'm chillin on suppress reloading.
我对抑制重装感到很紧张。
Oh, there's only two left dog.
哦，只剩下两条狗了。
Nice on my porch healing.
我的门廊愈合很好。
Oh, there's one city. There's one city that's kale.
哦，只有一个城市。 有一个城市是羽衣甘蓝。
All right.
好的。
What's his name?
他叫什么名字？
Kimber.
金伯。
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
That flush helps my arse so much. Any info on Larson now?
那冲洗对我的屁股有很大帮助。 现在有关于拉森的信息吗？
He might be anything noble. Oh, well, he's met his met.
他可能是什么高贵的东西。 哦，好吧，他遇见了他的遇见。
Hello.
你好。
All I got problem.
我有问题。
You got him?
你得到他了吗？
We have enough time. You can go
我们有足够的时间。 你可以走了
surely we don't all.
我们当然不是全部。
Don't really.
不要真的。
Know anything right now, OK?
现在什么都知道，好吗？
Like, ooh.
像，哦。
Yeah. Nice, nice, nice.
是的。 不错不错不错不错
I hate to.
我讨厌。
Say it, but probably best to play as a team.
说出来，但可能最好作为一个团队来玩。
Hey, that was fun when you just go in plenty.
嘿，当你大量进入时，那很有趣。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
He's talking so much go on. Go. Bingo.
他说了这么多继续下去。 去。 答对了。
Just go. Just go. Just go. Be a good. One.
去吧。 去吧。 去吧。 做个好人。 一。
Right. I'll just the same thing.
对。 我会做同样的事情。
It's cousin.
是表弟。
Yeah. We can't celebrate at all.
是的。 我们根本无法庆祝。
Well, what if they five sec be.
好吧，如果他们是五秒怎么办。
Didn't we fucking go meet.
我们他妈不是去见了面吗？
Them and be right. Same thing. Let's go.
他们是对的。 一样。 我们走吧。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
We fake a and then go back down.
我们假装一个然后回去。
I'm going to flush them.
我要冲洗它们。
Oh she's in the smoke.
哦，她在烟雾中。
Let's I to oh.
让我来哦。
Nice.
好的。
Get the plant seats here. OK
在这里获取植物席位。 好的
oh yes Marshall and
哦，是的，马歇尔和
nice one.
好一个。
Oh I knew.
哦，我知道。
Of follow one
跟随一个
of the most.
的最。
Certainly
他当然不会打败我们所有人。 最大限度。
Right
对
like what the fuck?
什么鬼？
Alvin there got.
阿尔文得到了。
I felt scared for the phoenix when that I.
那时我为凤凰感到害怕。
Yeah, I could feel. The.
是的，我能感觉到。 这。
Sweat from his balls. Going to spike. Up.
从他的球上流汗。 要去秒杀。 向上。
All right.
好的。
We're going to do almost the exact same thing,
我们将做几乎完全相同的事情，但表明你将成为秘密特工。 代理人。
You sneak up a once, they all rotate, get the ball, we're going to sell.
你偷偷摸摸一次，他们都轮换，拿到球，我们要卖掉。
Then we're going to.
然后我们要去。
Oh, you're not a plant.
哦，你不是植物。
You only a plant hired.
你只雇了一个工厂。
Wait for the rotation and then come with us.
等待轮换，然后和我们一起来。
Sell it with a sell. Oh, yeah. I mean, I'm not even daschund.
卖掉它。 哦耶。 我的意思是，我什至不是腊肠。
OK, we got your back here and we don't even know.
好的，我们得到了你的支持，我们甚至不知道。
Enemy spotted me.
敌人发现了我。
Dave Hillshire or shot.
戴夫希尔希尔或射击。
Yeah.
是的。
OK, let's go.
好的，我们走吧。
Let's get out of here.
让我们离开这里。
You guys.
你们。
We saw that.
我们看到了。
You're on a right and you're planting right now.
你在右边，你现在正在种植。
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, totally.
是的。 是的，是的，完全。
I beautiful.
我美丽。
Beautiful.
美丽的。
I want to play perfect.
我想玩完美。
Well, there's no one here.
嗯，这里没有人。
Step in the spike.
踏入尖峰。
Oh, spike down.
哦，秒杀。
OK. No, it was not clear
好的。 不，不清楚
is on.
开启。
It's ok. It's ok.
没关系。 没关系。
You have better guns now to you.
你现在有更好的枪给你。
You're going to get a you're going to 44 K here
你会得到一个你会在这里 44 K
oh 900 that head.
哦900那个头。
Shot killing all no.
枪杀一切没有。
Over it I'll wait that had shot you didn't know I shot you.
在它上面，我会等着你不知道我开枪打了你。
Know it was just the body shot.
知道这只是身体射击。
I was damaged already. Yeah.
我已经被损坏了。 是的。
Why are they.
他们为什么。
One ember was a bullet. A hundred.
一个余烬是一颗子弹。 一百。
Yeah.
是的。
I think there's one nest but might have went a.
我认为有一个巢，但可能去了一个。
30 seconds left.
还剩 30 秒。
Yeah.
是的。
They have big big boy guns.
他们有大男孩枪。
All the time.
每时每刻。
They are not. God, you're insane.
他们不是。 上帝，你疯了。
You're insane. Oh.
你疯了。 哦。
Oh. That's very nice. Very nice.
哦。 那很好。 非常好。
I can. See. Yeah.
我可以。 看。 是的。
Blue move in after I strike that wins.
在我击中获胜后，蓝色移动。
Oh sure.
行，可以。
Easy or way for people can buy.
人们可以轻松或方式购买。
See is it better we buy here?
看看我们在这里买更好吗？
Safe here?
这里安全吗？
I have no. Idea.
我没有。 主意。
If three can buy wishes.
如果三可以买愿望。
Like I can buy a guardian for Skara.
就像我可以为斯卡拉买一个监护人一样。
But people who can't buy, I just take a guy, take my gun when I die.
但是买不到的人，我就带个男人，死的时候带上我的枪。
Yeah, I would. Just take your gun when he died.
是的，我会的。 等他死的时候拿起你的枪。
Like a bag arguing.
像个包袱吵架。
Oh, no, no. Great.
哦，不，不。 伟大的。
Yeah. Three terrible areas.
是的。 三个可怕的领域。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
The plane to play this character.
扮演这个角色的飞机。
Yeah, well, next. Time I smoke my.
是的，接下来。 时间我抽我的。
Itsy peed somewhere.
它在某处撒尿。
There's one on the top of it.
上面有一个。
There way.
有办法。
He pull
他拉
oh, you want to play?
哦，你想玩吗？
I didn't expect that.
我没想到。
What?
什么？
It's like
它像是
oh, I thought it was cleared.
哦，我以为它被清除了。
Yeah,
是的，
Lily, you're insane.
莉莉，你疯了。
And I'm actually so insane.
我真的很疯狂。
That was a good play now.
那是现在的好戏。
Oh, that's.
哦，那是。
Playing.
播放。
Well, you want to play, but
好吧，你想玩，但是
I'm just.
我只是。
Tired of
厌倦了
let's try this again.
让我们再试一次。
I cannot. And she frog with my all to.
我不能。 她和我一起青蛙。
OK, over.
好的，结束。
We just. Oh, we were poor.
我们刚刚。 哦，我们很穷。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I'll trade my trade my corpse for this viper.
我会用我的尸体换取这条毒蛇。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
Yeah, I'll just run through the money.
是的，我只会花光钱。
We want to sack this.
我们想解雇这个。
Round of the. Trade.
回合的。 贸易。
Yeah, we should like we should say bye for next. OK.
是的，我们应该希望我们应该说再见。 好的。
I get back.
我回来。
I get
我明白了
to they pick from the doors.
给他们从门上挑。
Right? Or no,
对？ 或者不，不确定。
OK, once you watch this.
好的，一旦你看到这个。
I don't think they have before ok.
我不认为他们之前还可以。
All right.
好的。
Never mind.
没关系。
Forget what I said. Operate.
忘了我说的话。 操作。
We can't stop. OK.
我们不能停下来。 好的。
Ok. He'll shoot.
行。 他会开枪。
Gotcha. Oh.
明白了。 哦。
I'm so scared.
我很害怕。
No idea.
不知道。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
I'm gonna throw this issue I'm holding. OK.
我要抛出我持有的这个问题。 好的。
We're looking for a way to get a kill somehow.
我们正在寻找一种以某种方式获得杀戮的方法。
Oh, we just go TV. Oh.
哦，我们只是去看电视。 哦。
In there.
在那里。
Or at least looks like.
或者至少看起来像。
For you.
为你。
Oh, my God. I'll know what to do.
我的天啊。 我会知道该怎么做。
What's the plan? What's the. Plan?
计划是什么？ 是什么。 计划？
Lily. Lily, we create the space in space.
百合。 莉莉，我们在太空中创造空间。
Yeah.
是的。
It just go be it.
就这样吧。
Go and try.
去试试。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He just found Odin. Me.
他刚刚找到了奥丁。 我。
All right, you
好吧，你
ooh. Marshall Maximiser knife out plan.
哦。  Marshall Maximiser 出刀计划。
I like it.
我喜欢。
Oh, no, almost.
哦，不，几乎。
Oh, that's too big.
哦，太大了。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
That's. It's really. Cute. Yeah.
那是。 真的。 可爱的。 是的。
It helps.
它有助于。
I can, honestly.
我可以，老实说。
Well, I didn't get the memo to save.
好吧，我没有得到要保存的备忘录。
I didn't do my maths, right. Oh.
我没有做数学，对吧。 哦。
No, it's fine.
不，没关系。
It's fine.
没事。
The way I was paper things.
我的方式是纸质的东西。
Yeah, OK. We want you to fall. OK, listen.
是的，好的。 我们希望你跌倒。 好的，听着。
Unless you want us to run up me
除非你想让我们跑到我前面，因为我可以抽中路，我们可以做一些愚蠢的事情。
I can. All. Huh? How about this? I was all.
我可以。 全部。 嗯？ 这个怎么样？ 我就是。
I'll rather me.
我宁愿我。
I'm a smoke nest and tunnel.
我是烟巢和隧道。
And so you guys choose whether I don't care what the hell you guys do.
所以你们选择我是否不在乎你们到底在做什么。
You said you want to ulti.
你说你想要ulti。
It's just got a little bit somewhere. Go.
它只是在某个地方得到了一点点。 去。
Hey, which colour. Ooh.
嘿嘿，什么颜色。 哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He's just better.
他只是更好。
He's stuck 93, but he's can heal it all back up
他被卡住了93，但他可以恢复一切
if I had the needle there.
如果我在那里有针。
It's time to jump.
是时候跳了。
This is so intense.
这太激烈了。
I think they're just holding. Yeah.
我认为他们只是持有。 是的。
So I don't think they want to push up.
所以我不认为他们想推高。
And anybody like.
任何人都喜欢。
Oh nice try.
哦，不错的尝试。
There's one sitting. And.
有一个坐。 和。
Oh Bob's got the site.
哦，鲍勃有这个网站。
30 seconds. Yeah.
30秒。 是的。
Come bring the bomb.
来把炸弹拿来。
Nice good pick of in
不错的选择
that chamber.
那个房间。
You got to hurry and implant three
你得快点植入三个
here if you.
如果你在这里。
Viper's coming up we're going to turn bumpers
毒蛇来了我们要转保险杠可以转很不错的杀室人。 你
came bullet 74 left.
子弹 74 离开了。
Oh sorry.
哦对不起。
I should clarify. He's behind.
我应该澄清一下。 他在后面。
He was behind over.
他在后面。
Playing seat on the snap also.
打位子也按扣。
So now yeah because it's just really big.
所以现在是的，因为它真的很大。
There's not a lot of, like, tight hallways.
没有很多，像，狭窄的走廊。
Yeah.
是的。
Like in Haven or something.
就像在避风港什么的。
I if I could go. To.
我如果可以去。 到。
OK, I'm not. A
好吧，我不是。 我们只是去这里。
I have a little playfulness.
我有点贪玩。
OK, gotcha.
好的，明白了。
Right ankle.
右脚踝。
Yeah.
是的。
Lily can hold t the skirt. Mom.
莉莉撑得住裙子。 妈妈。
All right.
好的。
Oh, we have rest.
哦，我们休息了。
OK, I'm gonna take a peek.
好的，我去看看。
OK? Yeah, I'm going to pick a soup as well.
好的？ 是的，我也要去挑汤。
Or try to
或者尝试
all right.
好的。
Enemy spotted.
发现敌军。
If there was one.
如果有的话。
Box, why do I have to spike.
盒子，我为什么要秒杀。
Spikes to drop this one begins to.
尖峰下降这个开始。
Get his vision. Hang him.
得到他的愿景。 挂他。
No one.
没有人。
There's someone in the fridge area.
冰箱区有人。
Yeah. Stay
是的。 停留
right there.
在那里。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He just ran.
他只是跑了。
Ran through the doors. Wants to see.
跑过门。 想看。
That player standing.
那个球员站着。
On the whole bit.
总的来说。
I. I didn't think that would buy me.
I. 我不认为那会买我。
That was like in the corner.
就像在角落里一样。
Of all corners.
各个角落。
Oh, my what's.
哦，我的什么。
The guy or old see me? My office after class.
那个家伙或老看到我？ 下课后我的办公室。
Let's talk about our definitions of there's no one here.
让我们谈谈我们对这里没有人的定义。
OK, great.
好的，不错。
Great.
伟大的。
It was here is right in front of us.
它就在我们面前。
And she she.
而她她。
Swung after you. Well.
跟着你摇摆。 好。
I didn't see I actually didn't see her.
我没看到我真的没看到她。
That's Nancy she must've been invisible or something.
那是南希，她一定是隐形的什么的。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
She had her old see, she got a free orb.
她有她的老见，她得到了一个免费的球体。
OK, let's see.
好吧，让我们来看看。
All right.
好的。
Yes, everyone. Bye for now.
是的，每个人。 暂时再见。
Safe and say, look, I will.
安全地说，看，我会的。
I don't know what will I do?
我不知道我会怎么做？
Believe that flash.
相信那一闪而过。
Or I'll do this.
或者我会这样做。
Welcome to my world.
欢迎来到我的世界。
Of course.
当然。
To my world.
到我的世界。
It's her world I don't want to go through anymore.
这是她的世界，我不想再经历了。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Is that is that there?
那是那里吗？
Marshall's my.
马歇尔是我的。
It's all yours.
这都是你的。
Oh, here,
哦，这里，
here. A lot of marshals.
这里。 很多元帅。
Oh, we have two marshals. OK. Yeah.
哦，我们有两个元帅。 好的。 是的。
Oh. Spotted met.
哦。 见识了。
Coast tagged.
海岸标记。
He's low.
他很低。
Goes low. That's the only one I got.
走低。 那是我得到的唯一一个。
I'm scared.
我害怕。
I'll take that.
我会接受的。
I'll take the teleport.
我会接受传送。
Take a
拿一个
quick.
快的。
Yeah, well.
是的，嗯。
If it was, it was a good idea or it was interesting.
如果是，那是个好主意或者很有趣。
Oh, OK. She's in. Was it.
哦好的。 她进来了。是吗。
She was.
她。
Not oh.
不是哦。
Betty Lindsay N.S.A..
贝蒂·林赛 N.S.A.
You might find her.
你可能会找到她。
Go push your.
去推你的。
Eyes to your rescue. Yeah.
拯救你的眼睛。 是的。
Oh, honest. Yellow sunglasses come now.
哦，诚实。 黄色太阳镜来了。
It's like.
它像是。
Oh, sorry, dude.
哦，对不起，伙计。
He was so close.
他是如此接近。
Let them.
让他们。
If I had the fucking ham plate food.
如果我有他妈的火腿盘食物。
I thought so, too, but they were looking at it.
我也这么认为，但他们正在看。
Oh, dude, 93 curse is actually real.
哦，伙计，93诅咒实际上是真实的。
What the heck always happens?
什么鬼总是发生？
You're throwing.
你在扔。
You know what you get.
你知道你得到了什么。
Throw it down the halls if you want that. What's funny, dude?
如果你愿意的话，把它扔到大厅里。 有什么好笑的，伙计？
I actually thought.
我其实是这么想的。
I thought 93 curse was just the mean lights action.
我以为93诅咒只是卑鄙的灯光动作。
And people throwing mad blows without viper.
人们在没有毒蛇的情况下进行疯狂的打击。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm going to.
我要去。
I'm going to be awesome.
我会很棒的。
Hey, Ray.
嘿，雷。
I'll call here as well if I die. Yep.
如果我死了，我也会在这里打电话。 是的。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Enemy spotted and
发现敌人并
spotted a wow.
发现了一个哇。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What's he was actually hiding backwards, Eric, I guess wrong ok.
他到底躲在什么后面，埃里克，我猜错了。
I actually had shot. He doesn't know.
我真的中枪了。 他不知道。
When out doors.
出门时。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Damage, motherfucker.
伤害，混蛋。
It's just so quiet and
它是如此安静和
oh. Well.
哦。 好。
Lily gaming will game making
百合游戏将游戏制作
impact.
影响。
I'll be back.
我会回来的。
I don't think. I'm sorry. Oh,
我不这样认为。 对不起。 哦，
you're so good.
你这么好。
Oh, no. Oh.
不好了。 哦。
The eagle one was problem indoors.
老鹰一号在室内有问题。
No charges left.
没有任何费用。
And indoors.
而在室内。
Yeah.
是的。
Nice top.
不错的上衣。
So what did
那么做了什么
oh. Oh, my.
哦。 天啊。
Oh. I think he has his thingy in in shopper cave.
哦。 我想他在购物者洞穴里有他的东西。
I don't know. Right. That's where it came from.
我不知道。 对。 这就是它的来源。
No idea.
不知道。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
one second.
一秒。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Nice try and see
不错的尝试看看
I'm going to come
我要来
in so close with doing these
与做这些非常接近
I respect.
我尊重。
Oh, guys, we're now about to get our reverse swept.
哦，伙计们，我们现在要进行反向扫描了。
Sorry.
对不起。
No, absolutely not right now. Oh.
不，绝对不是现在。 哦。
Never mind.
没关系。
All right, we still first. I'm gonna go for the pick again.
好吧，我们还是第一。 我又要去选秀了。
Ok? OK. I'm turning my monitor on now.
好的？ 好的。 我现在正在打开我的显示器。
We got this. Oh, really? I can buy for you.
我们得到了这个。 哦真的吗？ 我可以给你买。
Oh, you.
哦，你。
Need a trump tax.
需要特朗普税。
Whoever is doing the salads.
谁在做沙拉。
Oh, my God. I should. Should I turn those off?
我的天啊。 我应该。 我应该把那些关掉吗？
Because it might throw me off. Oh, my gosh. Stressful moment.
因为它可能会让我失望。 天啊。 紧张的时刻。
Hold on. Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
坚持，稍等。 是的，是的，我很好。
So now all for now, just in case. Here.
所以现在一切，以防万一。 这里。
You ready?
你准备好了吗？
Scarred by armour. Oh.
被盔甲伤痕累累。 哦。
You want to play? Let's play.
你想不想玩？ 让我们玩。
Oh, there you job. Or he might be mid,
哦，你的工作。 或者他可能是中间人，
I think.
我认为。
Only ones here. Oh. Ooh.
只有这里的。 哦。 哦。
I'm miserable. OK.
我很痛苦。 好的。
Which I do here. Lily, what do you think?
我在这里做的。 莉莉，你怎么看？
I can. Never mind. I can't do anything.
我可以。 没关系。 我什么都做不了。
We're just going to leave.
我们只是要离开。
Yeah, and that's an option.
是的，这是一个选择。
I'm not to kill you.
我不是要杀你。
Hopefully I can get a kill
希望我能打死
nice.
好的。
Oh, actually, that's it. That's it.
哦，其实，就是这样。 这就对了。
That's really
那是真的
fucking smoking.
他妈的抽烟。
Did you all this? Yeah. Warn us.
这都是你做的吗？ 是的。 警告我们。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, down. Be
哦，下来。 是
oh, my God. Thank you.
我的天啊。 谢谢你。
All right, let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Be quick.
快点。
Inside our show.
在我们的节目里面。
You got this on the right, right?
你把这个放在右边，对吧？
I have this bike.
我有这辆自行车。
It's another person. Do
这是另一个人。 做
huh? Oh, my God. He's an elbow.
嗯？ 我的天啊。 他是一个肘部。
Oh, did I thought I was one of you guys?
哦，我以为我是你们中的一员吗？
Those are two people right there.
那是两个人。
Beings
众生
hired by chambers behind you all just.
被你们背后的商会雇佣而已。
Closed.
关闭。
And teleported.
并被传送。
He teleports in mid, I think. 30 seconds.
他在中间传送，我想。  30秒。
Yeah, he has is all see.
是的，他已经全都看到了。
So watch out for now.
所以现在要小心。
Good idea to be done. Ooh.
好主意要完成。 哦。
Oh, OK. OK, we'll do. Clutch this hour.
哦好的。 好的，我们会做的。 抓紧这个小时。
50 McDonald's chicken nuggets.
50块麦当劳鸡块。
5050.
5050。
50 spicy chicken nuggets.
50个辣鸡块。
All right.
好的。
Oh, god.
天啊。
I have to kill him.
我必须杀了他。
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
He's in Bug.
他在虫。
He's no. OK.
他不是。 好的。
I have an idea. I have an idea.
我有个主意。 我有个主意。
OK, all your guns. Let's force up here.
好的，你所有的枪。 让我们在这里强行。
Well, let's wait for the initial.
好吧，让我们等待最初的。
You tell me and then let's direction.
你告诉我，然后让我们指导。
I don't know how like we did the first.
我不知道我们第一次做的怎么样。
Year on have any money.
一年有钱。
Bias factor.
偏差因子。
You know, let's.
你知道，让我们。
Just do like we did the first time.
就像我们第一次那样做。
We have a lot of smokes.
我们有很多烟。
Which is to with us the question to be like a
我们的问题是像一个
passive active go. Oh.
被动主动去。 哦。
It don't do martial because those give me a lot of smoke.
它不做武术，因为那些给我很多烟。
We request this.
我们要求这样做。
This. Oh.
这。 哦。
Oh my god the chill chill body aspect.
哦，天哪，寒冷的身体方面。
He flushed so. Far.
他脸红了。 远的。
Oh sorry did you hear this again?
哦，对不起，你又听到了？
All right let's go let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
I'm going in.
我要进去了。
Because left colour
因为左边的颜色
right now to me
现在对我
no, I couldn't grab it.
不，我无法抓住它。
What's it got the animation off. Oh,
是什么把动画关了。 哦，
nice to the plank.
对木板很好。
Yeah. Better guns now. Better guns on the body.
是的。 现在更好的枪。 身体上更好的枪。
Yeah. I have this bike.
是的。 我有这辆自行车。
You like player.
你喜欢播放器。
Oh, this podium.
哦，这个讲台。
We the.
我们的。
Shoe.
鞋。
You clutch these, you always clutch these.
你抓住这些，你总是抓住这些。
Two chicken nuggets.
两块鸡块。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my oh.
哦，我的哦。
Oh, my gosh.
天啊。
That's not a bad investment.
这不是一项糟糕的投资。
So you've. No, you're just better.
所以你有。 不，你只是更好。
You're just better than them.
你只是比他们好。
That's just I can see. Oh, my God.
那只是我能看到的。 我的天啊。
We're having chicken nuggets tonight, boys.
孩子们，今晚我们要吃鸡块。
OK, ok. You
好的好的。 你
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Ow. It's final round.
哦。 这是最后一轮。
Can you buy me? That's true.
你能买给我吗？ 那是真实的。
Yeah.
是的。
I got your shape push.
我得到了你的形状推动。
If you guys are looking a I don't know.
如果你们正在寻找一个我不知道。
Let's play default this round. OK? OK.
让我们玩默认这一轮。 好的？ 好的。
I get a kill and then go to that site.
我杀了然后去那个网站。
Oof! That's
钱币！ 那是
all free.
全部免费。
OK, there's a 54 there.
好的，那里有一个 54。
There
那里
that's on site
那是在现场
cutting.
切割。
There is much more micro I got opt by chamber of the stairs.
我通过楼梯的房间选择了更多的微型。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I had an up you.
我有你。
Oh, man. I'm powerless.
天啊。 我无能为力。
That hurts.
那很痛。
Oh, ok.
哦好的。
I kill for power only
我只为权力杀人
face your fears.
面对你的恐惧。
Yeah, it's like, you know.
是的，就像，你知道的。
Let's try naturals.
让我们尝试自然。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
You clutch these again. You clutches again.
你又抓紧了这些。 你又抓紧了。
This is defeated. Last game twice.
这被打败了。 上一场比赛两次。
Oh, for fun.
哦，为了好玩。
All we're going to overtime.
我们都要加班。
Tonight
今晚
single. Switching
单身的。 随时间切换。
We got one thinks that shoes insane clutch.
我们有一个认为鞋子疯狂的离合器。
Yeah, that's.
是的，就是这样。
Me. Can you just do that?
我。 你能做到吗？
Yeah. Oh. We're better. We were better.
是的。 哦。 我们更好。 我们更好。
That's offensive for some reason, which was surprising.
出于某种原因，这是令人反感的，这令人惊讶。
No, it's because. I would divide for you.
不，是因为。 我为你分。
Viper tough. Oh, yeah.
毒蛇强悍。 哦耶。
It's a little rough.
这有点粗糙。
Playing Viper.
玩蝰蛇。
Too hard to find a brain swipe.
太难找到脑刷了。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
I know.
我知道。
It's cause it's just.
这是因为它是公正的。
Like I.
像我一样。
Can't play like me.
不能像我一样玩。
Well, she requires a brain.
嗯，她需要一个大脑。
A lot of these characters require brain.
很多这些角色需要大脑。
That's I play arena.
那就是我打竞技场。
Oh, sure. My arm. My shoe. Oh.
行，可以。 我的手臂。 我的鞋。 哦。
Oh, thank you. Oh, my gosh.
哦谢谢。 天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He saved his arse.
他救了他的屁股。
Oh. Is it all
哦。 是不是全部
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
This once you.
这一次你。
I just don't know if he's going to commit to that one. There
我只是不知道他是否会承诺这一点。 那里
clip. Oh.
夹子。 哦。
Ooh. Where was she?
哦。 她在哪里？
Where she mid?
她在哪里？
Yeah. Like your elbow area.
是的。 就像你的肘部区域。
That's zero.
那是零。
Some be
有些是
the come in and be.
进来吧。
Spiked down by one enemy remaining.
被剩余的一名敌人秒杀。
Nice. Woo.
好的。 呜。
Staying out of.
置身事外。
I'm sorry what I did to this guy Middleton.
我很抱歉我对米德尔顿这个人做了什么。
Inside.
里面。
I told you left me.
我说你离开我了。
All right now we just got a.
好吧，现在我们刚刚得到了一个。
Lot. Of on its you side.
很多。 就在你身边。
Is so fuck you.
太他妈的你了。
Oh. You want to you want to like run into B
哦。 你想要你想要喜欢遇到 B 或者你认为他们会期望那样。
They will.
他们会的。
They will expect that the default.
他们会期望默认值。
You got a gun OK.
你有枪就OK了。
Let's go if.
走吧，如果。
I have to win this fight, I just got to be smart.
我必须赢得这场战斗，我必须要聪明。
I'm not that smart though.
不过我没那么聪明。
You have a bomb.
你有炸弹。
So if you want to like drop that before you go any.
所以如果你想在你去之前放弃它。
Up. Here you go.
向上。 干得好。
You can have it.
你可以拥有它。
Thank oh.
谢谢哦。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, God. It hurts there some five feet. OK.
天啊。 那里疼了大约五英尺。 好的。
Oh, I'll flash you. How about that? Look here.
哦，我会闪现你。 那个怎么样？ 看这里。
You got you do it again.
你让你再做一次。
I'll do it again.
我会再做一次。
Flashes. Good. I don't.
闪烁。 好的。 我不。
Know. It's like.
知道。 它像是。
I'm surprised.
我很惊讶。
I'm getting tired of you.
我厌倦了你。
I'll thank you for helping to so.
我会感谢你的帮助。
Much like.
很像。
I'm going to go and watch me keep.
我要去看看我继续。
Watch me watch my right. Watch my right.
看我看我的权利。 注意我的权利。
I'm watching you.
我注视着你。
Good.
好的。
I'm not a bomb.
我不是炸弹。
All right,
好的，
so under watch.
所以在监视之下。
See? See, my my blood is exposed.
看？ 看，我的血暴露了。
Yes, OK.
好的。
They're opening the doors.
他们正在开门。
So looking out for us only like.
所以只喜欢照顾我们。
A nice, nice, nice, nice, nice. He's not flash. He's not flash.
好，好，好，好，好。 他不是闪电侠。 他不是闪光的。
I think or, like, go through the floor. No.
我想或者，就像，穿过地板。 不。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Oh, oh, oh, nice.
哦，哦，哦，不错。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I know more of the priest nonsense.
我知道更多的牧师废话。
Like that. Oh.
像那样。 哦。
Hey. Bathroom break a.
嘿。 浴室休息 A.
Pack.
盒。
Bathroom break.
浴室休息。
It's a real bigger.
这是一个真正的更大。
Oh, all those, like a silver lobby.
哦，所有这些，就像一个银色的大厅。
I guess I make sense.
我想我有道理。
We're all.
我们都是。
Like, over there.
比如，那边。
OK, that. You low.
好的，那个。 你低。
But I want you to know you're the MVP for that clutch. Oh.
但我想让你知道你是那个离合器的 MVP。 哦。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You are the very.
你就是那个。
Reason why we were able to get that over time. Oh.
我们能够随着时间的推移得到它的原因。 哦。
Let's go the most nutty flick.
让我们去看最疯狂的电影。
Oh. I'm glad. You.
哦。 我很高兴。 你。
Like, I think more than 90 seconds to go to the bathroom, right? Oh.
比如，我觉得去洗手间要超过 90 秒，对吧？ 哦。
Oh, yeah. Yeah. All we do is take you.
哦耶。 是的。 我们所做的就是带你去。
Oh, I.
哦，我。
Press the and I try to press start game, but you already press it, so I
按 ，我试着按开始游戏，但你已经按了，所以我按了。 哦，
oh, oh.
哦，哦。
On. We do a kissy thing for the doll.
在。 我们为娃娃做了一个亲吻的事情。
No, me are.
不，我是。
Thank you for the 10,000 bets Mia. Oh my God. Yeah.
感谢您的 10,000 赌注米娅。 我的天啊。 是的。
So for people
因此，对于那些没有看到仅在人们出现时才会发生的警报信息的人
I think it was like more than 1000 berries or like $50
我想这就像 1000 多个浆果或 50
or I don't know, I can't do it for like a summer gift solves
美元，或者我不知道，我不能像夏天的礼物一样解决
for some reason I don't know how to do that,
出于某种原因，我不知道该怎么做，但是现在每当我们得到一些大的东西时，那个冷却器就会弹出来。
So maybe I can show it again. Let me see
所以也许我可以再展示一次。 让我看看
OK. For everybody
好的。 为所有人
where is it
它在哪里
like this?
像这样？
Pretty cool.
很酷。
I like it a lot.
我很喜欢。
You have to adjust it though, because it's new.
你必须调整它，因为它是新的。
I haven't played with this that much yet.
我还没有玩过这么多。
Oh, let's see.
哦，让我们看看。
What do I have in my store right now?
我现在商店里有什么？
Oh. Aristocrat Vandal.
哦。 贵族破坏者。
I have.
我有。
What is this?
这是什么？
OK, I can't even look. Oh.
好吧，我也看不下去了。 哦。
Splay. OK.
张开。 好的。
I like the smell. Hmm.
我喜欢这种气味。 唔。
I feel cosy here.
我在这里感觉很舒服。
I know this like the back of my head split.
我知道这就像我的后脑勺裂开一样。
Yeah. You know, I hate. I hate fracture. I don't understand.
是的。 你知道，我讨厌。 我讨厌骨折。 我不明白。
That map tool is like not too much.
那个地图工具好像不算太多。
Yeah.
是的。
Overloads and
过载和
and it's, you know.
它是，你知道的。
Well, I try wife.
嗯，我试试老婆。
Oh. Babe.
哦。 宝贝。
Yeah, she's really cool. I like her. I like.
是的，她真的很酷。 我喜欢她。 我喜欢。
I can't want.
我不能想要。
The new death and really, really, it's different.
新的死亡，真的，真的，它是不同的。
Like, yeah,
就像，是的，这是第一次有人有，比如，某种形式的小玩意。
Right? Right. It's really cool.
对？ 对。 真的很酷。
The moment I've realised how much I've relied on my ears when i go.
那一刻我意识到我去的时候有多么依赖我的耳朵。
There it is.
它在那里。
Yeah, it's insane.
是的，这太疯狂了。
You need to learn.
你需要学习。
Learn how to play, like, without sound.
学习如何在没有声音的情况下演奏。
I mean, enzymes.
我的意思是，酶。
But i think in general, that's why I started.
但我认为总的来说，这就是我开始的原因。
But you started laughing in the last round round.
但你在最后一轮开始大笑。
You know who in general who?
你知道谁一般是谁？
OK. Oh, shoot.
好的。 哦，开枪。
I have a question.
我有个问题。
Who do you think the hottest fella and character is?
你认为最火的家伙和角色是谁？
I think it's Ullman personally.
我个人认为是厄尔曼。
That's just me, though. Oh.
不过，这只是我。 哦。
Oh, man. OK,
天啊。 好的，
I think Chambers a pretty popular team.
我认为钱伯斯是一支非常受欢迎的球队。
Very. Yeah.
非常。 是的。
Chamber also, he's, like, mocking my second.
房间里，他就像，嘲笑我的第二个。
Love Viper.
爱蝰蛇。
Over. Virtue.
超过。 美德。
I think. Fate or viper.
我认为。 命运或毒蛇。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Sage neon guys.
圣人霓虹灯家伙。
Volcano I thought you liked Reno mankind.
火山 我以为你喜欢雷诺人类。
Oh, yeah. Oh.
哦耶。 哦。
Wow. Scholar of that cliff. Oh,
哇。 那个悬崖的学者。 哦，
what's
什么是
so for you?
所以对你？
Might clue.
可能有线索。
I know he person in general.
我一般都认识他。
Here's a legal fucking shot.
这是一个合法的他妈的镜头。
Does she feel the same?
她有同样的感觉吗？
Oh, my gosh.
天啊。
How did you do that?
你是怎么做到的？
Now, what's.
现在，是什么。
That's valid. Baby?
这是有效的。 婴儿？
Valid, baby. OK.
有效，宝贝。 好的。
I'll hold mid watch mid.
我将保持中观。
I want to be
我想成为
somewhere.
某处。
Chat.
聊天。
I'm a I'm arena addicts.
我是一个我是竞技场上瘾者。
Like, I love this character so much. She's just so simple.
就像，我非常喜欢这个角色。 她就是这么简单。
Like, you kill people and you get sucked.
就像，你杀了人，你会被吸。
Oh, yeah. Now I. Like sucking. Your.
哦耶。 现在我喜欢吸吮。 您的。
Fucking he economy me lily iron.
他妈的他经济我百合铁。
Was like getting the sock feels so satisfying.
就像拿到袜子感觉很满足。
Here we go.
开始了。
Let's look at your house.
让我们看看你的房子。
OK? You hear me? OK.
好的？ 你听见了吗？ 好的。
Be watching our midst, though.
不过，请注意我们中间。
I don't know if they're all committing. So we're all here.
我不知道他们是否都在承诺。 所以我们都在这里。
They're all here. OK,
他们都在这里。 好的，
so anti-Putin.
如此反普京。
Oh. Nice.
哦。 好的。
What does.
有什么作用。
Oh, I'm scared.
哦，我很害怕。
Thank you for the heel face. 50.
谢谢你的后跟脸。  50.
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
They're both talented.
他们俩都很有才华。
They're both tagged right now. Lily, we got this.
他们现在都被标记了。 莉莉，我们得到了这个。
Got this insane fling.
得到了这个疯狂的投掷。
I should have now dropped down.
我现在应该掉下来了。
What was that?
那是什么？
I didn't realise you reached the audience.
我没有意识到你接触到了观众。
Oh, the sky. OK.
哦，天空。 好的。
The hold.
持有。
My fingers are so stiff, I can learn something.
我的手指很僵硬，我可以学到一些东西。
Oh, I'm cold.
哦，我冷。
Yeah. It takes, like, 2 hours.
是的。 大概需要2个小时。
To, like, turn off, right?
关闭，对吧？
Yeah. He's a laugh.
是的。 他是一个笑。
And you might have that problem the whole night.
你可能整晚都有这个问题。
I had that happen to me before. Right? You like something?
我以前也遇到过这种情况。 对？ 你喜欢什么？
You think you're so cool, you can't lift fast enough on the classic. Yep.
你认为你太酷了，你不能在经典上飞得足够快。 是的。
And on it happens. I feel you. Yep.
并且它发生了。 我感觉到你了。 是的。
A.A. and Nancy, thank you for the moral support, guys.
互诫协会 和南希，谢谢你们的精神支持，伙计们。
I love you.
我爱你。
I hear you.
我听到你了。
Footsteps Yeah. The circle. OK.
脚步声是的。 圆圈。 好的。
I cut it before they.
我在他们之前剪掉了它。
Planted in my hair.
种在我的头发里。
I'm watching this. Whoa.
我正在看这个。 哇。
What is that? Deep
那是什么？ 深的
that was unfortunate.
那很不幸。
There, in there.
那里，那里。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Spike plant up and.
穗植物和。
Oh, God, that sucks.
哦，天哪，太糟糕了。
I'm running a marathon.
我在跑马拉松。
Nice oh, frick
不错哦，弗里克
last.
最后的。
When I was.
当我是。
I mean, see, the. Oh.
我的意思是，看，。 哦。
Oh, that's true.
哦，那是真的。
Yeah, I tried to get the slide down.
是的，我试图让幻灯片滑下来。
Now that we have a tried, now it's time.
既然我们已经尝试过了，现在是时候了。
To stop back.
停下来。
I'm and.
我是和。
I'm not so good at doing the maths.
我不太擅长做数学。
Oh. He's talking oh you didn't by last hour.
哦。 他在说哦，你最后一小时还没说。
And did you. Know I did it.
你呢。 知道我做到了。
Oh OK.
哦好的。
I see.
我懂了。
I need to
我需要兰德尔法官。
The lawyers are
律师是
never worried.
从不担心。
You're correct.
你是对的。
But I'd be glad.
但我会很高兴。
They like Bailey.
他们喜欢贝利。
If you're
如果你是
watching amidst the hallway, I'm backing up into the fence again.
在走廊里看着，我又一次倒进了栅栏里。
Is there a lobby oh, that's the lobby. OK, I'm coming
有没有大堂哦，就是大堂。 好的，我来了
I'm flashing for. You.
我为之闪烁。 你。
To pushed up Sage Lady in.
将圣女推了进去。
The 130 seconds
130秒
be. Nice.
是。 好的。
We got 10, nice,
我们有 10 个，很好，
nice. Nice. Yeah.
好的。 好的。 是的。
Great job.
做得好。
By me.
由我。
Yeah, I can oil Princeton.
是的，我可以给普林斯顿加油。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Show and issue.
显示和发布。
OK, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
好的，是的，是的。 是的。
Yeah. I who
是的。 我是谁
I only showed. So this is a to clarify.
我只展示了。 所以这是一个澄清。
I'm going to go for Lilly everyone.
我要为每个人都去莉莉。
All don't watch.
大家不看。
Switch to the aid.
切换到辅助。
Push lilly iron while P2.
P2 时推 Lilly Iron。
OK, here we go.
好的，我们开始吧。
Here we go.
开始了。
I got I got smoked.
我知道我抽烟了。
Ahmed.
艾哈迈德。
I don't hear anything I'm scared.
我什么也没听到，我很害怕。
All God yeah they
上帝啊，是的，他们很快就用完了，我推着烟敲打着他们。
Spotted man.
有斑点的人。
There haven't I haven't shoes haven't seen nothing there's another guy.
没有我没有鞋子没有看到什么有另一个人。
Oh nice try and fill back
哦，不错的尝试并在手表上填满我认为他们会承诺在座位模块中来自天堂。
Player standing.
球员站着。
All right Lilly you got this
好的，莉莉，你得到了这个
they want to vomit.
他们想呕吐。
What?
什么？
No way they want yeah.
没办法，他们想要是的。
I think there's two seats so watch out
我想有两个座位所以要小心
the TV heated.
电视加热了。
With.
和。
Is he's coming up for you I think just nice
他是来找​​你的吗我觉得很好
there's another guy there this one Johnson.
还有另一个人，这个约翰逊。
Oh, close close.
哦，关闭关闭。
Yeah. Those close the job.
是的。 那些关闭工作。
Let me go mid.
让我走中路。
Man it is.
男人是的。
Time ADT. They're going to let me.
时间 ADT。 他们会让我。
You can go B if you want to swap it out.
如果你想换掉它，你可以去B。
I think they're off. I'll go. I'll go ahead.
我认为他们已经关闭了。 我要走了。 我会继续。
Can cover.
可以盖。
B, it might be better that way.
B，这样可能会更好。
So delays there. Push, right.
所以那里延误。 推，对。
I watched a YouTube video set up for me.
我观看了为我设置的 YouTube 视频。
That's why.
因此。
Oh. OK.
哦。 好的。
All of a sudden it's all
突然之间，这一切都是哦，伙计。 在YouTube上。 我们相信。
In YouTube, we trust.
在 YouTube，我们信任。
Yeah.
是的。
I've watched them tutorials to.
我看过他们的教程。
Watch this lucky man. Was.
看看这个幸运的人。 曾是。
Serious. Oh, yikes.
严肃的。 哦，哎呀。
They became a this.
他们变成了这个。
They're on the Navy Yard chair.
他们在海军工厂的椅子上。
Oh, my God. I'm afraid.
我的天啊。 恐怕。
I'm afraid of her.
我怕她。
Yeah. Now.
是的。 现在。
Nice oh, the judge claiming.
很好哦，法官声称。
Oh, frickin heaven.
哦，该死的天堂。
If I die to that, I would be released.
如果我死了，我就会被释放。
I think they know I'm coming.
我想他们知道我要来了。
Eagles
老鹰队
amass scars, take a lot of heat you can walk up show.
伤痕累累，带上很多热量就可以走秀了。
Last player still.
最后一名球员还在。
Oh 45 this you.
哦 45 这就是你。
Planted nicely.
种得很好。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
And you suck here
而你在这里很烂
feeling sad?
感到伤心？
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
I needed a gun.
我需要一把枪。
Was there a gun on heaven actually gone to heaven. Fuck.
天上有枪居然上天了。 他妈的。
Maybe I don't know. The Omen was there.
或许我不知道。 预兆在那里。
Oracle Scala where we'll take our next
Oracle Scala 我们将在哪里进行下一步
where should I set up Lily?
我应该在哪里设置 Lily？
There. They're just dodging it.
那里。 他们只是在躲避它。
And they're specifically avoiding you.
他们特意避开你。
Let me go, man.
放开我，伙计。
Let me go. It OK.
让我走。 没关系。
I did three, five night terror.
我做了三、五次夜惊。
What is. It? A good idea?
什么是。 它？ 一个好主意？
The cover my map is because that's told me to do that.
覆盖我的地图是因为有人告诉我这样做。
You can
你可以
oh, to avoid is like snipers.
哦，避免就像狙击手。
Yeah, I didn't know that was an issue.
是的，我不知道这是个问题。
Sewers like your sewers. A
下水道就像你的下水道。 一种
and I think those are a yeah.
我认为是的。
They're just thought.
他们只是思想。
Wish you
希望你
what happened to have no.
发生了什么没有。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I'm going to get away from that play for a retake.
我要离开那场比赛重拍。
Let's look at how
让我们看看如何
the pressure I'm having.
我的压力。
They're all on to site now.
他们现在都在现场。
We know. Oh.
我们知道。 哦。
Freak back every.
吓坏每一个。
Last oh landing.
最后哦着陆。
My fingers are still. Planted
我的手指还在。 种植的
feeling safe.
觉得安全。
OK, I'll
好的，我会知道谁
what.
什么。
Oh, nice try. Nice try.
哦，不错的尝试。 不错的尝试。
All right, let's stop again.
好吧，让我们再次停下来。
They can't just perfectly avoid you forever.
他们不能永远完美地避开你。
That's true.
那是真实的。
You have to mess up at least once.
你必须至少搞砸一次。
I'll tell you what, I only go offensively because I definitely.
我会告诉你什么，我只会进攻，因为我绝对。
I'm like, over here
我喜欢，在这里
yeah.
是的。
All right, OK.
好的，好的。
Let's see
让我们来看看
well, god, I don't know what to buy, Sheriff.
好吧，上帝，我不知道该买什么，警长。
Howdy, howdy.
你好，你好。
Howdy.
你好。
OK, there will be.
好的，会有的。
I think it's mid. Well, why?
我认为是中。 嗯，为什么？
How are they always avoiding you?
他们怎么总是躲着你？
Was opposite of me.
与我相反。
This guy. This is.
这家伙。 这是。
They'll feel this.
他们会感觉到这一点。
But I voted by that.
但我是这样投票的。
Initial midst.
初中。
No, I don't. Know where they're at. They're really late.
不，我没有。 知道他们在哪里。 他们真的迟到了。
They're really careful going through
他们真的迟到了。
again.
再次。
I'm almost like, yeah, I'm also going to be OK.
我几乎就像，是的，我也会没事的。
Oh, there's one.
哦，有一个。
There's one. Romney, Mitt.
有一个。 罗姆尼，米特。
Just looking.
只是看看。
To Mitt.
给米特。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Can I have that for sure?
我可以确定吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Raise any sky heavy now.
现在举起任何沉重的天空。
They're still having this to heaven right now.
他们现在仍然拥有这个到天堂。
OK, thank you.
好的谢谢。
You don't want to be.
你不想成为。
Spike planted.
穗种植。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
I'm on the walls.
我在墙上。
Whoa.
哇。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
This is rough stuff.
这是粗糙的东西。
Oh, we're. Live. Wimberley.
哦，我们是。 居住。 温伯利。
I really don't want to jinx it for you, but you can pick this that you go
我真的不想为你诅咒它，但你可以选择这个你去，我会走另一条路。
and I'll go the other way. Let's say.
比方说。
You go. See. A scene.
你去。 看。 一个场景。
Yeah, go see. Good. See?
对，去看看。 好的。 看？
You see, I think.
你看，我想。
I believe that one day you'll get to play the game.
我相信有一天你会玩游戏的。
I'm just going to go.
我只是要去。
I'm just go.
我只是去。
If he just tells you no big deal. Hmm.
如果他只是告诉你没什么大不了的。 唔。
Do they have to cancel all your sites eventually?
他们最终是否必须取消您的所有网站？
Right. There's no way.
对。 不可能。
They do. It. That's my job.
他们是这样。 它。 那是我的工作。
I'm waiting 2 seconds to smoke.
我正在等待 2 秒吸烟。
It's.
它的。
It's mid
现在是中
I could wallet.
我可以钱包。
Oh, I messed up.
哦，我搞砸了。
Right. OK,
对。 好的，
maybe only eight.
也许只有八个。
By the ultimate with go on.
由终极继续。
They're still going to have it.
他们仍然会拥有它。
I think.
我认为。
I hit them.
我打了他们。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He's sitting there the entire time.
他一直坐在那里。
This right. He's having a.
这个权利。 他有一个。
Right spike down b.
右尖峰向下 b.
Bracelet. 100 on the wall.
手镯。  100在墙上。
Heaven all.
诸天万界。
On site fade
现在在现场褪色。 我们正在做饭和
hunting.
打猎。
These guys have great game sense.
这些家伙有很好的游戏意识。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
OK, never going to be remaining three.
好吧，永远不会剩下三个。
Where was she?
她在哪里？
She was on site Siddiqui.
她在现场西迪基。
Yeah.
是的。
You could try being in our.
你可以试试我们的。
Baby heaven, though.
不过，宝贝天堂。
Yeah. Watch. Watch Heaven City. Tap the bomb.
是的。 手表。 观看天堂城。 点击炸弹。
You can go in the bomb and see where she is.
你可以进去看看她在哪里。
You have the terror for heaven, though, so you can watch City.
不过，您对天堂充满恐惧，因此您可以观看《城市》。
Watch the city.
观察这座城市。
Oh, oh, nice, nice, nice, nice.
哦，哦，不错，不错，不错，不错。
Nice, nice.
好好。
Thank you, job.
谢谢你，工作。
Good job, guys.
干得好，伙计们。
We ran. It back in back in.
我们跑。 它回来了。
Winnable.
可赢的。
Wait, Lily, did they dodge you again?
等等，莉莉，他们又躲过你了吗？
Yes. Yes.
是的。 是的。
All right.
好的。
You pick.
你选。
Are you going be OK?
你会好吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Goodbye.
再见。
All right.
好的。
Me a.
我一个。
Scarf.
围巾。
Could you buy me
你能买给我吗
thanks.
谢谢。
Can't Art. Oh,
不能艺术。 哦，
that's fine.
没事儿。
Oh, forcing this.
哦，强迫这个。
Sorry. Forcing.
对不起。 强迫。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
Oh, God.
天啊。
We made it happen as.
我们做到了。
We speak is people. It happens.
我们说话的是人。 它发生了。
It happens. Happens. It's men.
它发生了。 发生。 是男人。
Ish slash peas.
伊什斜线豌豆。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, maybe. Abby
哦，也许吧。 艾比
a nice.
一个不错的。
I should have to go back out the other hand.
另一方面，我应该退后一步。
On my marker.
在我的标记上。
You guys hold the hold. I'm going back.
你们握紧。 我要回去了。
Ok? Oh, they smell coming.
好的？ 哦，他们闻到了。
That's made it
就是这样
still OK. Any as a tree that there.
还可以。 任何如一棵树。
There on safety.
那里是安全的。
You could have me.
你可以有我。
One of us health
我们中的一员健康
yes. You come to us.
是的。 你来找我们。
Yeah, I'm on mid-song if you want to get me.
是的，如果你想得到我，我正在唱中歌。
To go this way.
要走这条路。
I think you have time because
我想你有时间因为
yeah. You haven't planted yet.
是的。 你还没种。
We're chilling. Oh.
我们不寒而栗。 哦。
There's one.
有一个。
There's one. Tell me how.
有一个。 告诉我怎么做。
I think in my.
我认为在我的。
Mark there might be one near your shoe. Careful.
标记你的鞋子附近可能有一个。 小心。
It was last seen here.
它最后一次出现在这里。
OK, how will you.
好的，你会怎么做。
Garage?
车库？
I have. A flash of a flash on.
我有。 一闪一闪。
A on the bomb.
炸弹上的一个。
Quickly.
迅速地。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Enemy.
敌人。
All right, you got this little you got this at the bomb.
好吧，你得到了这个，你在炸弹上得到了这个。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, oh, I panic.
哦，哦，我慌了。
Oh, kidding. OK.
哦，开玩笑的。 好的。
You made the right call. A.
你做了正确的决定。 一种。
Oh, carla.
哦，卡拉。
God, this is so. So badly stacked.
天哪，原来如此。 堆积得如此糟糕。
I'm I'm going to admit.
我要承认了。
Scar I can buy you here.
刀疤我可以在这里给你买。
I don't know what to do. You think you should buy here?
我不知道该怎么办。 你觉得你应该在这里买吗？
I I yeah.
我我是的。
Egg to point.
鸡蛋来点。
We can save profit.
我们可以节省利润。
By about to wrap up.
快结束了。
Just sort of support it. Just I'm sure.
只是有点支持它。 只是我确定。
You're lucky because I don't know what's
你很幸运，因为我不知道什么是
right. OK.
对。 好的。
And Bucky game and
和巴基游戏和
it's a no no.
这是不行的。
You don't know you don't know.
你不知道你不知道。
If it is they're there.
如果是，他们就在那里。
Yeah. Oh, they don't
是的。 哦，他们没有
on TV.
在电视上。
A lot room.
很多空间。
All right.
好的。
I've got your trial.
我得到了你的审判。
I got 10.
我有10个。
Strong statements on site.
现场声明强烈。
Nice got swept all smiles.
尼斯得到了所有的微笑。
Goes down a. Sage. Lily.
下降一个。 智者。 百合。
You can force them off of your own. See, maybe right?
你可以强迫他们离开你自己。 看，也许是吧？
You scare the last.
你吓到了最后一个。
Oh, nice try.
哦，不错的尝试。
I them.
我他们。
I have to years now.
我现在要几年了。
Do you think we'll have a better time on attack?
你认为我们会在进攻端有更好的时间吗？
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
I don't even know.
我根本不知道。
Where do I go? Where do I go?
我要去哪？ 我要去哪？
We have.
我们有。
They've been effectively avoiding me just like.
他们一直在有效地避开我，就像。
They chose Lily side one side of them. Yes.
他们选择了莉莉的一侧。 是的。
Good luck. Can't be that.
祝你好运。 不能那样。
Oh, me. Keep going.
哦，我。 继续前进。
Oh, all right.
哦那好吧。
Out hey.
出来嘿。
Thank
谢谢
voice. Is.
嗓音。 是。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I was on my iPad.
我在我的 iPad 上。
And back away from that rocket.
然后远离那枚火箭。
Scary.
可怕的。
They're on site. Oh.
他们在现场。 哦。
Nice, nice, nice.
不错不错不错不错
Nice, nice pass.
不错，不错的通关。
Oh, my gosh. He's watching me from.
天啊。 他正在看着我。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, hear.
哦，听说。
They're in my.
他们在我的。
Head. Say.
头。 说。
Here we go. Here we go.
开始了。 开始了。
Let me get. In
让我拿。 在你得到这个，莉莉。
Oh, no.
不好了。
You got to feel like.
你必须感觉像。
Oh, random little.
哦，随机的小。
Last round before the switch.
切换前的最后一轮。
It's like when the bowling pins are like, on the end.
就像保龄球瓶一样，最后。
Yeah, you go in the middle.
是的，你走中间。
I'm going in now.
我现在要进去了。
OK, ok. OK. With Lily for the first time.
好的好的。 好的。 第一次和莉莉在一起。
Maybe it's still.
也许它仍然是。
I don't know. It's it's.
我不知道。 它就是它。
You know, I'm just going to.
你知道，我只是要去。
I'll sit hell at that.
我会坐在那里。
So I'll be.
所以我会的。
Someone could someone play having for me?
有人可以为我玩吗？
Yeah. They're about be very fucking scared.
是的。 他们快他妈的害怕了。
Throw a blind.
扔一个百叶窗。
That's to see they're there.
那就是看到他们在那里。
Oh I hear be I hear a couple. Mid.
哦，我听到了，我听到了一对。 中。
You mother trust. You.
你妈妈信任。 你。
He was the worst killjoy can.
他是最糟糕的杀人狂。
Ever be.
永远是。
Be all.
成为所有。
I got concussed.
我脑震荡了。
They might be rotating out.
他们可能正在轮换。
Be ready. Yep.
准备好。 是的。
That's them jumping.
那是他们跳。
Yeah as I'm jumping away.
是的，因为我要跳了。
You ready
你准备好了吗
OK. You can go all I'll be all.
好的。 你可以去我将是所有。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Yeah, she hit what's
是的，她击中了什么
nice?
好的？
Very nice pick.
非常不错的选择。
It's only eight.
它只有八个。
It's three.
是三个。
We three now you guys are in a good spot.
我们三个现在你们处于一个好位置。
I think.
我认为。
You have to hear the.
你必须听到。
Scar.
瘢痕。
You're crazy.
你疯了。
They have to push up.
他们必须向上推。
Yeah, you got this. You got this. Your game. And
是的，你得到了这个。 你得到了这个。
are they back on? Think I heard be.
你的游戏。 他们又回来了吗？ 想我听到了。
They're headed towards a heaven are be heaven.
他们正走向天堂，成为天堂。
Be heaven. Maybe
成为天堂。 也许
so I did what?
所以我做了什么？
Oh, one. Enemy. Nice. Yes, Spike, we have Spike.
哦，一个。 敌人。 好的。 是的，斯派克，我们有斯派克。
Spike on home down b
秒杀回家 b
zero.
零。
You still having he's still having.
你还在，他还在。
He's on hell. He's on hell. Now. Seconds left.
他在地狱。 他在地狱。 现在。 还剩几秒。
Just way from Clint.
就在离克林特很远的地方。
Just play time.
只是玩的时间。
Place on play time. He the plan
放置在游戏时间。 他是你给我们的计划。 是的。
You have to go for it now.
你现在必须去做。
Just on. Yeah.
刚上。 是的。
Nice. OK.
好的。 好的。
Name the job.
为工作命名。
Night because actually.
晚上因为实际上。
Yeah now you him but 116.
是的，现在你他，但 116。
Your cards are OK.
你的卡没问题。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
So we're attackers.
所以我们是攻击者。
Yes, yes.
是的是的。
We are attackers.
我们是攻击者。
Yes, I'm not.
是的，我不是。
Yeah.
是的。
No, no, no, no, you are.
不，不，不，不，你是。
We're gonna you to penetrate. We are.
我们要你渗透。 我们是。
We are as a collective. 11 at a 12 time.
我们是一个集体。  11 次 12 次。
Where's Killjoy.
基尔乔伊在哪里。
Over them.
在他们之上。
Where do I go?
我要去哪？
Where do I go I'm not a hit a fast as will be this look.
我该去哪里我不会像这个样子那样快。
Yeah I think that's the plan.
是的，我认为这是计划。
He's going to go on hard.
他会继续努力。
Must it create a lot of chaos let's get on the site here.
它一定会造成很多混乱吗？让我们进入这里的网站。
OK so he ramp ramps screens haven't.
好的，所以他坡道屏幕没有。
Smoke so.
就这样抽烟。
I've been having.
我一直有。
Difficulty second place. I.
难度第二。 一世。
Know I hate this gun.
知道我讨厌这把枪。
I want I'm doing. All.
我要我在做。 全部。
They know
他们知道
I've been use.
我一直在使用。
For I got help count
因为我得到了帮助
there so many
有这么多
oh god eventually.
天哪，最终。
God that's genuinely.
上帝是真的。
So scary through people just waiting for me get on the end for. It.
如此可怕的人只是在等我结束。 它。
Oh they walled over the wall Mike yeah.
哦，他们翻墙迈克，是的。
You're coronated.
你加冕了。
The other are god.
其他都是神。
But his scars say you're
但他的伤疤说你是我的朋友，火焰都得到了卷。
Oh you nasty. Oh.
哦，你讨厌。 哦。
Yes I like dragons I get it.
是的，我喜欢龙，我明白了。
Devil looks like.
恶魔的样子。
Oh I don't want.
哦，我不想要。
A dragon penis. Move in my hand.
龙阴茎。 在我手中移动。
I just I don't like how I don't.
我只是我不喜欢我不喜欢。
Know like I should. Force force a. Rib.
我应该知道。 力力 A. 肋骨。
It looks.
它看起来。
Yeah.
是的。
I should show force up.
我应该表现出来的力量。
I'm forcing, I'm forcing. OK.
我在逼，我在逼。 好的。
Launching something.
推出一些东西。
Let's go
我们走吧
close.
关闭。
Right.
对。
All right.
好的。
Thank heaven.
谢天谢地。
Having
有
video.
视频。
Yeah. Oh, my God.
是的。 我的天啊。
This guy and his judge.
这家伙和他的法官。
Oh, spike down.
哦，秒杀。
He told the judge to watch out now.
他告诉法官现在要小心。
Oh, I saw
哦，我看到了
Dawn.
黎明。
OK, Frenzy. We know the drill.
好的，狂热。 我们知道演习。
Stick your roles and we'll crush it. Oh.
坚持你的角色，我们会粉碎它。 哦。
These guys I have.
我有这些人。
To change by.
改变。
Did they rotate off?
他们轮换了吗？
They rotate really fast for this.
他们为此旋转得非常快。
Well, are you buying this?
嗯，你买这个吗？
Yes, we.
没错，我们。
It's worth every round.
每一轮都值得。
We're so far. Behind we can't give up. OK, ok.
我们到目前为止。 后面我们不能放弃。 好的好的。
And fortunately
幸运的是
shy, right?
害羞吧？
I don't know.
我不知道。
OK, and they'll do with every caveat.
好的，他们会处理每一个警告。
OK. OK. Yeah, we'll look for pick.
好的。 好的。 是的，我们会寻找选择。
A goal together.
一起进球。
Kill and then get the other. OK,
杀死然后得到另一个。 好的，
nice really way to get a kill.
很好的杀戮方式。
Doesn't matter.
没关系。
I'm a rat.
我是一只老鼠。
I'm a rat. I'm a rat.
我是一只老鼠。 我是一只老鼠。
Rats. Rats.
大鼠。 大鼠。
We're the rats.
我们是老鼠。
You're jumping.
你在跳。
Lots of jumping.
多跳。
We spotted a.
我们发现了一个。
Guy about Obama.
关于奥巴马的家伙。
Goodbye. Goodbye, goodbye. Goodbye.
再见。 再见，再见。 再见。
Got a lot.
得到了很多。
The trade.
贸易。
OK, ok. We actually have good size.
好的好的。 我们实际上有很好的尺寸。
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
I shall.
我将。
Let's go on a mission.
我们去执行任务吧。
What's our mission?
我们的使命是什么？
We're going to sneak in and country.
我们将潜入和国家。
There's to be wait and see if he wins.
得等着看他能不能赢。
We're going to be read.
我们将被阅读。
Your own
你自己
oh, ok.
哦好的。
Plant Lily.
种植百合。
Now I know, I know.
现在我知道了，我知道了。
I'll kill the guy. Haven't
我会杀了那家伙。 没有
shows going city
显示城市，我们可以观看实际的仔细飞行。
Careful if like the.
喜欢的话慎点。
Nice one.
好一个。
I'm psyched out with.
我很兴奋。
All my guts back there.
我所有的胆量都回来了。
She's one time. She's once had.
她是一次。 她曾经拥有过。
These on her
她身上的这些
turn.
转动。
Oh, yeah, that's her.
哦，对了，就是她。
Got me your turn.
轮到我了。
Got to kill time
必须消磨时间
companion that's pretty good.
伴侣说的还不错。
Is there respect on the ground?
有尊重吗？
Nothing else.
没有其他的。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, I may one yeah.
哦，我可能一个是的。
I think the question was.
我认为问题是。
This.
这。
I can't believe we're going to win this game, guys.
我不敢相信我们会赢得这场比赛，伙计们。
Yeah, this is where we snowball back.
是的，这就是我们滚雪球的地方。
They give us an inch, you know?
他们给我们一英寸，你知道吗？
Yeah, they're robots.
是的，他们是机器人。
Everybody win one gunfight.
每个人都赢得一场枪战。
Yeah.
是的。
All right.
好的。
OK, there's one.
好的，有一个。
Oh, there's 2 million.
哦，有200万。
Yeah, you get.
是的，你明白了。
See these
看到这些
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. How'd she do that so fast?
我的天啊。 她怎么那么快？
I'm sure I'm going to come to you for him.
我相信我会为他来找你的。
I sure just swung wide and fast.
我肯定只是挥动得又快又宽。
Please,
请，
just one minute.
只需一分钟。
All right, Lily, you and I are going to go fighting, OK?
好吧，莉莉，你和我要去打架，好吗？
Is this right?
这是正确的吗？
We're both both going to kick the wall on three, ok?
我们俩都要踢三分，好吗？
One, two, three.
一二三。
I don't think I'm the oven alarm on this.
我不认为我是这方面的烤箱警报。
Oh, that's. Good. That's big. That's big. That's big.
哦，那是。 好的。 那是很大的。 那是很大的。 那是很大的。
Really big. Huge.
真的很大。 巨大的。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, RAISA 58.
哦，莱萨 58。
Good luck, guys.
祝大家好运。
50 seconds.
50 秒。
Oh. Oh,
哦。 哦，
out of.
在......之外。
Judges.
法官。
Right? Really?
对？ 真的吗？
Takes the orbit notice. 30 seconds left.
接受轨道通知。 还剩 30 秒。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的。
OK. Oh, dude.
好的。 哦，伙计。
Like guys, I actually, I can't tell if it's like, um,
就像男人一样，我实际上，我不知道它是否像，嗯，
boy, I can't tell if they're actually, like, if I really cover my mouth is a.
男孩，我不知道他们是否真的像，如果我真的捂住嘴是一个。
Big huge jets. Crashing down. B
巨大的喷气式飞机。 轰然倒下。 乙
Because some people are saying like, it's a it's an issue, right?
因为有些人说，这是一个问题，对吧？
I know.
我知道。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Oh, no. Oh.
不好了。 哦。
They double over the wall.
他们翻墙。
Come on, man. OK.
来吧，伙计。 好的。
You know, I don't like giving false hope.
你知道，我不喜欢给人虚假的希望。
We may or may not have this.
我们可能有也可能没有。
We have this.
我们有这个。
Leaning towards keep. It up in the air.
倾向于保持。 它在空中。
We don't
我们不，我们不确定我们是否有这个，但如果我们赢了，它是一个
we're not sure if we have this or not, but it it's a 5050 on if we win or not.
5050。
Yeah. You either win or you don't win.
是的。 你要么赢，要么不赢。
You need a drop.
你需要一滴。
Yeah. I'll take one of those.
是的。 我将采取其中之一。
Things I have I have an idea of how to get.
我有的东西我知道如何得到。
What the hell.
我勒个去。
They're all shooting at me. What?
他们都在朝我开枪。 什么？
That's crazy. And I'll be.
这很疯狂。 我会的。
Like three people are shooting at me. All right.
就像三个人朝我开枪一样。 好的。
What's OK. I'm leaving. I just.
什么是好的。 我走了。 我只是。
Spoke
辐
with you.
与你。
There.
那里。
All right.
好的。
Invents
发明
one jumps out, one comes out.
一个跳出来，一个出来。
Now what we're having.
现在我们所拥有的。
Style not oh.
款式不行哦。
Spike down B.
下降 B.
Oh, shit. That player's standing.
妈的。 那个球员站着。
Like a shoe.
像一只鞋。
You win these, you win these.
你赢了这些，你赢了这些。
Right? 100
对？  100
all right, you're there, buddy.
好吧，你在那儿，伙计。
So, first.
所以，首先。
Of all, you have a right, too.
总之，你也有权利。
Nice. It's big. It's massive.
好的。 它很大。 这是巨大的。
There's one just on Ramon. No,
有一个就在拉蒙。 不，
you're telling me.
你在告诉我。
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
Me show up five in
我出现在五个
my oh.
我的哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Alvin.
阿尔文。
So sick.
真恶心。
Oh. All right.
哦。 好的。
Got a go scar.
有伤疤。
Yeah, I got you.
是的，我得到了你。
I got nothing.
我什么都没有。
Did you. Buy scalloping?
你是否。 买扇贝？
I care.
我在乎。
I've been the dream.
我一直是梦想。
Oh, I got a viper now.
哦，我现在有一条毒蛇。
Mm do we have a fifth to replace?
嗯，我们有第五个可以替换吗？
There might be
可能有
or or. Wow.
或或。 哇。
Two people to replace
两个人换
I think.
我认为。
I think they're not levelled enough for play ranked, but
我认为他们的水平还不够高，但
they would be down and play unrated
如果你们都很好，他们会失望并且不打分。 谁。
You keep.
你保持。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Yeah.
是的。
Dude, another purple boy.
伙计，另一个紫色男孩。
Let's go
我们走吧
oh, shoot.
哦，开枪。
Are you still there.
你还在吗。
Don? OK, you know, it's ok
大学教师？ 好的，你知道，没关系
when he gets.
当他得到。
Oh, shoot.
哦，开枪。
Yells hit or cut off.
叫喊声击中或切断。
Oh, my fucking way.
哦，我他妈的方式。
My head's cut off.
我的头被砍了。
Yeah. You're like.
是的。 你就像。
Half.
一半。
Half headed.
半个头。
To Shuki.
给舒淇。
Shoot, shoot.
射击，射击。
Kito.
基托。
Suki kids.
苏琪孩子。
Aaliyah
艾莉亚
ok, let me.
好吧，让我。
I was this the the code for it.
我就是它的代码。
OK, thank you.
好的谢谢。
Use that later. OK?
以后用那个。 好的？
What I use the car may not then
我用的车可能就不会只用你。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Anything works.
什么都行。
Or wiggly or wiggly.
或摇摆不定或摇摆不定。
Form. Oh, yes. Yeah.
形式。 哦是的。 是的。
I'm distracting them when they try to look at the map.
当他们试图看地图时，我会分散他们的注意力。
Yeah, that's me.
是的，就是我。
Mortgage and try to cover it and the time come
抵押并尝试覆盖它，时间到了
that.
那。
Say send them the invite to the server.
说向他们发送邀请到服务器。
Or I think so. Yeah is ok. I'm going.
或者我认为是的。 是的，没关系。 我要去。
Oh yeah sure. OK.
哦，是的，当然。 好的。
I won't help me.
我不会帮助我。
And then that's and then who do we have for fifth.
然后就是第五名了。
Do you know
你知道吗
we have anyone. Else
我们有任何人。 别的
not sure you see.
不确定你看到了。
We have four fifth oh.
我们有五分之四哦。
What is, what is cycle no doing.
什么是，什么是循环不做。
I know he's busy.
我知道他很忙。
I think, I think yeah.
我想，我想是的。
If you could ask for more slot two.
如果你可以要求更多的插槽二。
Anybody from anybody else from these you wants to play.
您想玩的任何其他人中的任何人。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
All right.
好的。
Like I know Fuller might be on on this time probably.
就像我知道富勒可能会在这个时候上场一样。
I'm not sure. Hello.
我不确定。 你好。
Oh, hello. Key.
哦你好。 钥匙。
What's up? Hi. Welcome. Welcome.
怎么了？ 你好。 欢迎。 欢迎。
Can you send me your food link, by the way?
顺便问一下，你能把你的食物链接发给我吗？
Mine.
矿。
Yeah, yours. OK,
是的，你的。 好的，
ok. Yeah.
行。 是的。
Is there.
有没有。
A show? Just DMA to you?
一场表演？ 只是给你DMA？
Yeah, just the to me. OK.
是的，只是对我来说。 好的。
Hierarchy.
等级制度。
Hi. Nice to meet you.
你好。 很高兴见到你。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm not good.
我不好。
I'm probably worse.
我可能更糟。
OK? I'm not.
好的？ 我不是。
I'm not that good either.
我也不是那么好。
We're all I feel like you're gone.
我们都是我觉得你走了。
That's something.
那是东西。
I mean, I feel like that's a mistake, honestly.
我的意思是，老实说，我觉得这是一个错误。
OK, I should know easier.
好吧，我应该知道更容易。
You know, you're pretty good.
你知道，你很不错。
Yeah. You're Katie.
是的。 你是凯蒂。
My Katie.
我的凯蒂
Was that mean? I'll kill death, right?
那是什么意思？ 我会杀死死亡，对吧？
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
During the first match, you're like 26 and 15.
在第一场比赛中，你就像 26 和 15。
I really. I didn't notice. Yeah.
我真的。 我没有注意到。 是的。
Oh. GUMI might be down a chain.
哦。  GUMI 可能是一个链条。
Puts both of you right here. OK,
把你们俩都放在这里。 好的，
here we go.
开始了。
So we're switching to what's a unrated, right?
所以我们正在转向什么是未评级的，对吧？
OK, then if we switch on rhythm, we don't need to worry about mouth
好的，那么如果我们打开节奏，我们就不用担心捂嘴了。
covering stuff. Oh, no. We can just, like, have fun with it, right?
不好了。 我们可以，喜欢，玩得开心，对吧？
Yeah, we could just. Yeah.
是的，我们可以。 是的。
I mean, we were we were.
我的意思是，我们曾经是。
Already showing, to be honest, so.
老实说，已经显示了，所以。
Yeah, pretty much.
是的，差不多。
I'm going to the restroom real quick.
我要去洗手间真快。
Okey dokey. OK.
对。 好的。
Ok. Oh, anyways, so now I finally had a chance to talk got to chat.
行。 哦，无论如何，所以现在我终于有机会说话了。
Are you guys doing what's up?
你们在做什么？
I was, I was.
我是，我是。
I was up
我起来了
actually.
实际上。
Purple Voice.
紫声。
Yup. Or Voice Club finally. Right?
是的。 最后还是 Voice Club。 对？
It was gun.
那是枪。
It was bound to happen eventually because I really wanted to do something
它最终一定会发生，因为我真的很想做那样的事情。
like that.
但是，是的，今天我想我们也有机会，所以
that's pretty cool, right,
这很酷，对，
guys? I'm not.
伙计们？ 我不是。
I'm really not that good at Valentine's.
我真的不擅长情人节。
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么。
Like, I feel like most of the time, the first one,
就像，我觉得大多数时候，第一个，
I think we're just really well coordinated as a team.
我认为我们作为一个团队非常协调。
The second time around was kind of suss knuckle.
第二次是一种怀疑的指关节。
I, I think they might have actually been sniping.
我，我想他们可能真的在狙击。
I don't know if that's true or not
我不知道这是否属实，因为我对暴力知之甚少，就像人们实际上一样。
People really students like that seems kind of sucky.
像这样的学生真的很糟糕。
So be honest.
所以说实话。
I feel like they wouldn't bite because I guess I have like more v a.
我觉得他们不会咬人，因为我想我更喜欢 v a。
I. Have more faith in people.
一、对人更有信心。
I'll I'll come back. OK, we ready?
我会回来的。 好的，我们准备好了吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Okeydoke.
奥基多克。
Let me leave the map.
让我离开地图。
Oh, warming up.
哦，热身。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, all right.
好吧，好吧。
I haven't played since yesterday here.
我从昨天开始就没有在这里玩了。
Or was that.
或者是那样。
Oh, you're.
哦，你是。
Perfect.
完美的。
You're ready. Mm
你准备好了。 毫米
I don't know about that.
我不知道。
Go to warm up.
去热身。
Do they look so, so cute next to me?
他们在我旁边看起来那么可爱吗？
Oh, my God. I love it. So adorable.
我的天啊。 我喜欢它。 好可爱。
Look at these dudes.
看看这些家伙。
Well, these dudes look at them.
好吧，这些家伙看着他们。
I feel crazy.
我觉得疯了。
I feel so crazy.
我觉得太疯狂了。
I want to wiggle.
我想扭动。
Hi, wiggle. Hi.
你好，摇摆。 你好。
Match found.
找到匹配。
All right.
好的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Wow. Not breathing. Oh. Hell, yeah, exactly.
哇。 没有呼吸。 哦。 地狱，是的，完全正确。
Ill do it.
我会做的。
OK, but this is unrated, so we can just have fun with it.
好的，但这是未分级的，所以我们可以玩得开心。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
That new shit you wanted to try out.
你想尝试的新东西。
True.
真的。
Oh, sure.
行，可以。
OK. OK, ok. Look around. Yeah.
好的。 好的好的。 看看周围。 是的。
A low key on.
低调开。
If it is really hot. Sil.
如果真的很热。 西尔。
Yeah, fade.
是的，褪色。
Fade is hot and fun. Oh, she looks very feral.
褪色是热的和有趣的。 哦，她看起来很野蛮。
And there's something about that. It's just like
还有一些关于那的。 就像杰斯有她的铬，有她的恐惧症头，她的铬
chrome yeah.
铬是的。
Yeah, I identify with her.
是的，我认同她。
Oh, yeah, yeah.
哦，是的，是的。
I've had her chromium too.
我也有她的铬。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
And mites yeah.
螨虫是的。
Oh, Lily, you're gonna.
哦，莉莉，你会的。
You're going to frag out on Raina.
你会在 Raina 上争吵不休。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
It could.
它可能。
I never do well. Athena Oh.
我从来都做得不好。 雅典娜哦。
No, no, no.
不不不。
No. This is this time I went like zero 14, I.
不，这次我像零一样去 14，我。
Think and go play. Oh, French guy.
想想就去玩。 哦，法国人。
And they're they're just sweaty
他们只是汗流浃背
can you speak French?
你能讲法语吗？
Uh, zip them.
呃，把它们拉上拉链。
Oh, that's a good for sore.
哦，这对疮有好处。
That's like now.
就像现在一样。
You know, you know, the bad thing about that
你知道，你知道，这件事的坏处是我只知道怎么说我们，就是这样。
Yes, I don't know how to speak French.
是的，我不会说法语。
What's a no in French?
法语中的no是什么？
And he's just. No.
他是公正的。 不。
No. OK, you.
不，好的，你。
Know, when you say rooted sorry in French, they don't understand you apparently.
知道，当你用法语说“rooted sorry”时，他们显然听不懂你。
And you have to say it like to to.
你必须说它喜欢。
Know.
知道。
You're like, what the fuck is a waiter to we?
你会说，我们他妈的是什么服务员？
And a that's exactly right that you.
那是完全正确的，你。
Got that because.
明白了，因为。
I think Louis.
我想路易斯。
Cora I think I don't.
科拉我想我不知道。
Know him French confirm that.
认识他的法语证实了这一点。
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
Can you say can French?
你能说法语吗？
No. I said can a French.
不，我说法国人可以。
And a. French person confirm that? I'm sorry.
和一个。 法国人证实？ 对不起。
French speaking person confirm that.
说法语的人证实了这一点。
We in a French.
我们用法语。
Yeah.
是的。
Put my trademark back here.
把我的商标放回这里。
Did you get that from counterclaim.
你是从反诉中得到的吗？
Acquaintance I might. Of might just talk to.
认识我可能。 的可能只是交谈。
How did you know that.
你怎么知道的。
Oh, you oh.
哦，你哦。
Chat knows all they know. Yeah.
聊天知道他们所知道的一切。 是的。
Oh I am French can confirm.
哦，我是法国人可以确认。
There it is.
它在那里。
Oh OK.
哦好的。
You're a
你是一个
oh I'm out of there.
哦，我不在了。
I got one.
我得到了一个。
Nice. Nice.
好的。 好的。
I got another.
我得到了另一个。
Look at that
看那个
crack
裂缝
oh it's on the count of three, three, three
哦，它是在数三，三，三
OK. OK,
好的。 好的，
now you're Hilscher.
现在你是 Hilscher。
Oh are. You.
哦是。 你。
Oh, thank you. Call him.
哦谢谢。 给他打电话。
Are you all right here.
你在这里还好吗。
Nice. Oh, you got five hey.
好的。 哦，你有五个嘿。
Hey. Oh.
嘿。 哦。
Come on, come on. Come from.
好啦好啦。 来自。
I'm walking over there
我走过去
yeah.
是的。
I'll just leave them. I'll even for you.
我会离开他们。 我什至会为你。
All right, let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
Blue let's go.
蓝色我们走吧。
Is more than just a nice suit.
不仅仅是一件漂亮的西装。
Well done.
做得好。
I think I'll go.
我想我会去的。
La, la, la la la la la OK.
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦好啦。
You think that is
你认为那是
getting a lot of gold?
得到很多黄金？
I like money.
我喜欢钱。
Oh, yeah. I'm looking for an
哦耶。 我正在寻找一个
oh, that's a lot.
哦，很多。
People. Look, I'm on the radio.
人们。 看，我在收音机里。
A lot.
很多。
On our way on.
在我们前进的路上。
Are we.
我们是吗。
Fucking. Ooh,
他妈的。 哦，
oh, yeah, I can.
哦，是的，我可以。
Cause I got concussed. No.
因为我脑震荡了。 不。
Or oh, oh, oh.
或者哦，哦，哦。
Oh. There will be. Oh.
哦。 将有。 哦。
That was terrifying.
那太可怕了。
Yeah, I got to be Roxy. Cool.
是的，我必须成为 Roxy。 凉爽的。
And pulled
并拉
oh, god.
天啊。
I know.
我知道。
I was wrong. Oh, sorry.
我错了。 哦对不起。
I didn't mean to do that.
我不是故意的。
What the heck?
有没有搞错？
Here we go.
开始了。
For what are we doing here?
我们在这里做什么？
Uninterrupted. Oh.
不间断。 哦。
Yeah.
是的。
They need to rotate.
他们需要轮换。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
They whoa.
他们哇。
They're scared.
他们害怕。
Oh, thank you.
哦谢谢。
Bucky.
巴基。
Also pretty
也很漂亮
monsters.
怪物。
Want us off the
想让我们摆脱困境吗？
Thinks like player.
像玩家一样思考。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Racist. One time.
种族主义的。 一度。
Reasonable armour.
合理的装甲。
No enemy remaining.
没有敌人了。
All my guys just rules.
我所有的人都只是规则。
I really.
我真的。
I'm not shy. Oh, my God.
我并不害羞。 我的天啊。
I can pull through my pistol.
我可以拔出我的手枪。
So you mean.
所以你的意思是。
You're safer nose too much
你鼻子太安全了
oh. Pflueger might join later.
哦。  Pflueger 可能会稍后加入。
Vulgar. Oh, nice. Yeah. Yeah.
庸俗。 不错哦。 是的。 是的。
You got a five, man?
你有一个五，伙计？
Yeah, we can all.
是的，我们都可以。
You know, for all of them.
你知道，对于他们所有人。
And just through all my.
只是通过我所有的。
You tell me they are so dead.
你告诉我他们已经死了。
They are so dead.
他们已经死了。
OK, one.
好的，一个。
Neon as he didn't push out, did they know they didn't.
霓虹因为他没有推出，他们知道他们没有推出。
OK, we're chilling then.
好的，那我们就凉了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Have them
拥有他们
there's one back there.
后面有一个。
Thank you. Nice.
谢谢你。 好的。
Oh, they're using their abilities, though.
哦，不过，他们正在使用他们的能力。
Are they going to push through
他们会挺过去吗
yeah.
是的。
Just coming from here.
刚从这里过来。
Oh, no. Oh, shit.
不好了。 妈的。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Putting baby food. On.
放婴儿食品。 在。
RB, maybe.
RB，也许吧。
I think everybody be at home.
我想每个人都在家。
Oh, yeah, they maybe be too.
哦，是的，他们可能也是。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, shit, lady,
哦，妈的，女士，
please.
请。
Just not last time.
只是不是上次。
Oh. 52. Mm
哦。  52. 嗯
spike planted.
穗种植。
It's actually be. What the heck. I'm so confused.
它实际上是。 有没有搞错。 我感到很困惑。
The worst part was that the minimum
最糟糕的部分是，最低保持OK。
Just two more. No pressure.
就多了两个。 无压力。
Yeah, yeah. Free house. Oh, my God.
是啊是啊。 免费的房子。 我的天啊。
Oh, that TV's kind of like that.
哦，那个电视有点像。
Three health in a dream.
梦中三生。
Finding
发现
one enemy remaining.
剩下一个敌人。
I'm watching, I'm watching for you.
我在看，我在等你。
I'm watching.
我在看。
Last player stand.
最后一名球员站立。
Who? Hello?
谁？ 你好？
Oh, the man of Arcade
哦，街机的人
Yep. No idea.
是的。 不知道。
I could have.
我本可以有。
I could have stuck.
我本来可以卡住的。
I think maybe.
我想也许吧。
I got this.
我懂了。
You're the down.
你是失败者。
Close. Close. Right. Try it.
关闭。 关闭。 对。 尝试一下。
I my heart
我我的心
Mozart.
莫扎特。
Can't deny
不能否认
I don't know.
我不知道。
Are receiving. I think we are you.
正在接收。 我想我们就是你。
An early by.
早过。
Yeah.
是的。
Seems about right.
似乎是对的。
Oh, my goodness. Ten kills.
哦，我的天啊。 十杀。
Yeah, I I have known.
是的，我已经知道了。
Ready
准备好
that is was massive.
那是巨大的。
Oh, a
哦，不错的一个。
Oh, how do I live that
哦，我该如何生活
they're coming from there.
他们来自那里。
Dropping down. You're dropping down. From. Yeah.
下降。 你正在倒下。 从。 是的。
Oh no I'm feeling.
哦，不，我有感觉。
Like oh my God.
就像我的上帝一样。
They just tied one of four down
他们只是将四个中的一个捆绑在一起
spikes. Sputters suck.
尖峰。 溅射很烂。
Is that.
就是它。
All right? Let's go.
好的？ 我们走吧。
All right, Lily,
好的，莉莉，
this is the one.
这是一个。
Who. Won this run Reno.
谁。 赢得了这场比赛里诺。
Break out for up player standing.
突破上位球员。
Nice. OK, what.
好的。 好的，什么。
Do you.
你。
Oh, oh, you're doing it right.
哦，哦，你做得对。
You're doing great.
你做的很棒。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
Oh, you're all. You're sick.
哦，你们都是。 你生病了。
You're in
你在
the. Shrine.
这。 神社。
Enjoy yourself.
玩的开心。
I forgot.
我忘了。
Yeah, the other one. Oh, yeah, I am the sulky.
是的，另一个。 哦，是的，我是闷闷不乐的。
Or you can, like, turn on me again, ok? Yeah.
或者你可以，比如，再次打开我，好吗？ 是的。
Yeah,
是的，
there are.
有。
There are.
他们眼中的恐惧。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
Covering of yourself.
覆盖自己。
So cool. Yeah, yeah.
非常酷。 是啊是啊。
Yeah. Rain is bad arse.
是的。 雨是坏屁股。
What are we not missing?
我们没有错过什么？
Uh, for me, I think I, like, fade more.
呃，对我来说，我想我，喜欢，褪色更多。
Just I know she's doing something to me.
只是我知道她在对我做某事。
He single.
他单身。
Nice.
好的。
You don't tell
你不告诉
some things.
一些事情。
I see. Yeah. They destroyed my haunts.
我懂了。 是的。 他们摧毁了我的出没。
OK. I
好的。 一世
I shouldn't have done that.
我不应该那样做的。
I'm on my way.
我在路上。
Come on.
来吧。
Oh, they know where I am.
哦，他们知道我在哪里。
I know exactly where you are.
我确切地知道你在哪里。
I've got him.
我得到了他。
Oh, yeah?
哦耶？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Just pull my handle.
只要拉我的把手。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
What the heck? Oh, what the heck?
有没有搞错？ 哦，什么鬼？
What's going on?
到底是怎么回事？
Dodge.
躲闪。
So? Well, Spike planted
所以？ 好吧，斯派克种下了
like.
像。
It healing
它治愈
you oh, oh.
你哦，哦。
Be right there.
快到了。
Nice shot.
好球。
Nice head shot.
不错的爆头。
There's an. Oh, my God. Too yummy. No.
有一个。 我的天啊。 太好吃了。 不。
Oh. Yeah.
哦。 是的。
To wall that off. I think that's a wall that off.
把它关掉。 我认为那是一堵墙。
And four straight or like down three. Was it.
和四连胜或像下降三。 是吗。
Go to the other side.
去另一边。
Yeah. And diffuse. Diffuse.
是的。 并扩散。 扩散。
Nice. Got this easy.
好的。 轻松搞定。
When I was a sick teleport. Oh she's not there.
当我是一个生病的瞬移。 哦，她不在。
She can't get there.
她无法到达那里。
Yeah, you you're so good.
是的，你真好。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Those head shots OK
那些爆头OK
all of oh go.
哦，去吧。
For the guardian if I want.
如果我愿意，给监护人。
Yeah.
是的。
That's how PEDs.
这就是PED的方式。
OK. Yeah, if I could
好的。 是的，如果我可以使用它。
I suppose to do have this.
我想应该有这个。
Where are
在哪
Philip Roth ready?
菲利普罗斯准备好了吗？
All right,
好的，
OK. I didn't catch it.
好的。 我没有抓住它。
Oh. Oh, my God.
哦。 我的天啊。
There's some.
有一些。
There's one. Seattle.
有一个。 西雅图。
Oh, I'm. Sorry. Oh, neons here at APL.
哦，我是。 对不起。 哦，APL 的霓虹灯。
I missed.
我错过了。
I fucked up real hard.
我搞砸了。
Oh, sorry.
哦对不起。
I can't. A slower
我不能。 较慢的
oh, god.
天啊。
Oh, this is.
哦，这是。
There's an oh, the omen night.
有一个哦，预兆之夜。
Nice. The Omen night.
好的。 预兆之夜。
Yeah, the home.
对，家。
We got a night
我们有一个晚上
lessons.
教训。
Yeah, lessons over the night.
是的，通宵上课。
Go be yeah. To pick b.
去吧，是的。 选择 b.
I think they have to.
我认为他们必须这样做。
Oh, she sounds. Like her mind.
哦，她的声音。 喜欢她的心思。
Never mind.
没关系。
Whatever it's called. Satellite dish something, huh?
不管叫什么。 卫星天线什么的，嗯？
The big round plate.
大圆盘。
It's sticking out of the ground.
它伸出地面。
Oh, dish. Yeah.
哦，菜。 是的。
Oh, she dropped.
哦，她摔倒了。
Oh, no, she dropped.
哦，不，她摔倒了。
She's not.
她不是。
This.
这。
Good straight. Yeah.
好直。 是的。
Great. Great.
伟大的。 伟大的。
Pretty much can uranium India.
几乎可以铀印度。
It helps with. A can someone find me?
它有帮助。  A 有人能找到我吗？
I have no money.
我没钱。
Does anyone have funds?
有人有资金吗？
Oh. My God.
哦。 我的上帝。
I'm in.
我在。
A nice.
一个不错的。
Place. Meet someone.
地方。 见个人。
Am I just a few yummy toes is our common thing.
我只是几个美味的脚趾是我们共同的事情。
Oh, oh, yeah. If you.
哦，哦，是的。 如果你。
If you go to the nearest Sandy website, you could observe my toes.
如果你去最近的桑迪网站，你可以观察我的脚趾。
Look. Oh, I.
看。 哦，我。
Have seen your country.
见过你的国家。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I'll there's.
我会有的。
I have a virus there. Oh.
我那里有病毒。 哦。
Oh, hell.
哦地狱。
No. Oh.
不，哦。
I just got one tapped.
我刚拍了一个。
My God. Hi.
我的上帝。 你好。
Oh. Oh, my.
哦。 天啊。
That neon quake, right?
那场霓虹地震，对吧？
I keep forgetting that character is like speed. Oof!
我一直忘记角色就像速度。 钱币！
Your behind. Oh.
你的背后。 哦。
Yeah. They blink
是的。 他们眨眼，或者它甚至不是一面旗帜。
They're just coming from both directions.
他们只是来自两个方向。
What will it be this time?
这次会是什么？
Have any pattern
有任何图案
of receiving.
的接收。
This this round? You guys can save them.
这一轮？ 你们可以拯救他们。
Yeah.
是的。
Let me.
让我来。
See if it's something like, you
看看是不是像，你
know.
知道。
I kind. Of feel sometimes too hot to play.
我善良。 的感觉有时候玩的太热了。
Well. Shit brown. They'll cap on a stack.
好。 该死的棕色。 他们会在堆栈上加盖。
You're going to use an awful.
你将使用一个可怕的。
Just like me.
就像我。
For ill. For ill.
为病。 为病。
Just like
就像
out of chance.
出于偶然。
Because they are so dead.
因为他们已经死了。
They are so dead.
他们已经死了。
Sage is going to be long.
圣人会很长。
They found my trap. Oh.
他们发现了我的陷阱。 哦。
You got one right there.
你那里有一个。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Neon piano all down here.
霓虹钢琴都在这里。
And watch out.
小心。
No was gone.
没有消失。
They kill my soul apart. OK, ok.
他们把我的灵魂分开了。 好的好的。
Once I get
一旦我得到
well there also. Oh.
也有。 哦。
They're oh, god.
他们是哦，上帝。
Oh, oh. Oh.
哦，哦。 哦。
Lily gymnastics.
百合体操。
Seasoning.
调味料。
Oh. Spike planted.
哦。 穗种植。
Oh, oh. Oh, my goodness.
哦，哦。 哦，我的天啊。
That neon.
那个霓虹灯。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Is a neon on over there.
那边有霓虹灯。
She's come for you.
她是来找你的。
Oh, charges.
哦，收费。
Wait, my action.
等等，我的行动。
Oh, nice try.
哦，不错的尝试。
Nice try.
不错的尝试。
Re that neon is kind of crazy.
那个霓虹灯有点疯狂。
Yeah, she's running around like she owns the place
是的，她到处乱跑，就像她拥有这个地方一样
everywhere.
到处。
I think
我认为
oh, I hope I.
哦，我希望我。
Oh, yeah, yeah.
哦，是的，是的。
God, I wish I played Reno
上帝，我希望我能在 Reno 把我的眼睛移开的时候扮演她。
Oh, you said more.
哦，你说的多了。
Or you mean her suck.
或者你的意思是她很烂。
All her suckers or her?
她所有的吸盘还是她？
Yeah, I her souls. Yes.
是的，我是她的灵魂。 是的。
She's have four of those, right?
她有四个，对吧？
Yeah. Four. Oh, my God.
是的。 四。 我的天啊。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
Oh, get them those weird.
哦，给他们那些奇怪的东西。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh. They never, ever split between it.
哦。 他们从来没有，曾经在它之间分裂。
Dude.
老兄。
Damn. Nice, nice, nice.
该死。 不错不错不错不错
Dr. Swan.
斯旺博士。
Oh, watch out. Yeah.
哦，小心。 是的。
My my rotate. All
我的我的旋转。 全部
oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Firing that ball or wrestle.
发射那个球或摔跤。
Oh. Oh, my God.
哦。 我的天啊。
I got rocketed that's a big rocket cover going out.
我被火箭击中了，那是一个巨大的火箭掩体。
Like, planted. Ooh. Crazy.
比如，种植。 哦。 疯狂的。
Oh, thank you.
哦谢谢。
Oh, the target.
哦，目标。
I'm not.
我不是。
Ready.
准备好。
All right.
好的。
Wow. Like this.
哇。 像这样。
Is out.
出来了。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
One enemy remaining cover going.
一名敌人剩余掩护。
Oh, my God. Moments.
我的天啊。 时刻。
I believe.
我相信。
Oh, they don't have time.
哦，他们没有时间。
Oh, no.
不好了。
You're sick, dude.
你病了，伙计。
Hot. Good job. Nice
热的。 做得好。 好的
woo hoo hoo.
呜呜呜。
Let's go away for our boys.
让我们为我们的孩子们走开吧。
For a bit.
就一点。
You must missed
你一定错过了谋杀现场。
This is true.
这是真的。
Oh, I know that word.
哦，我知道那个词。
Is a mercy or mercy boku.
是怜悯或怜悯boku。
I don't know the difference between those two.
我不知道这两者之间的区别。
That works more.
这更有效。
I'm a.
我是一个。
French now.
现在法语。
They understand.
他们明白。
Now they understand their on all the French fears.
现在他们明白了他们对法国人的所有恐惧。
Cover going out.
盖出门。
Mm. Huh.
毫米。 嗯。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
You drop.
你掉。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
They're pushing.
他们在推动。
Right
对
see me.
看我。
Little corner.
小角落。
See you right there
见你在偷看。
Oh, I messed up
哦，我搞砸了
that slow or
那慢或
they're coming.
他们来了。
My tip
我的小费
I got one.
我得到了一个。
Nice and yeah, nice I.
很好，是的，我很好。
Got to where is the other guy planted snipers by dish.
到了另一个人在哪里种植狙击手的地方。
Enemy remaining.
敌人剩余。
First my dish.
先说我的菜。
OK, we can defuse we can if you will watch for.
好的，如果你愿意的话，我们可以化解。
Yeah, you know.
是的，你知道的。
I see nice. Nice.
我看不错 好的。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
We nice.
我们很好。
I got a gun.
我有枪。
A pretty gun seal.
漂亮的枪海豹。
I survived over.
我活过来了。
This is made out of wood.
这是用木头做的。
Oh, shoot.
哦，开枪。
Flushed emotion.
激动的情绪。
Sorry.
对不起。
Oh, look, he wants to buy.
哦，看，他想买。
Oh, can I get a bite? Yeah. Yeah, I can buy you.
哦，我可以咬一口吗？ 是的。 是的，我可以买给你。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I didn't notice
我没有注意到谢谢你告诉我，因为，就像，我能听到上面的声音。
Well. Red Hook, that's not ready.
好。 红钩，还没有准备好。
Look who's ready.
看看谁准备好了。
Fletcher.
弗莱彻。
I oh, oh, whoa oh, whoa oh.
我哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦上哦
Come on. We'll have to help me.
来吧。 我们必须帮助我。
Oh, my. Oh, oh, oh, wait.
天啊。 哦，哦，哦，等等。
He'll come all the way.
他会一路过来。
I got you.
我接到你了。
All right.
好的。
No. Oh.
不，哦。
No, no, no.
不不不。
You got that trade because. It's, like.
你得到那笔交易是因为。 就像是。
Sounds like something.
听起来像什么。
Nice.
好的。
I'm running over one enemy.
我正在碾过一个敌人。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You guys don't even.
你们甚至没有。
You're you're cracked
你是你被破解了
you run.
你跑。
Nice.
好的。
Nice job.
不错的工作。
And the body of an bulldogs.
还有斗牛犬的身体。
Very great job.
非常棒的工作。
Last round in the half.
半场最后一轮。
Oh, I can buy the fence.
哦，我可以买栅栏。
There you go.
你去吧。
That's a good spot.
那是个好地方。
This last round, most of the.
这最后一轮，大部分了。
Actually
实际上
find the operator.
找到运营商。
Ready to say operator.
准备说运营商。
Yes, I did.
是的，我做到了。
Oh, I missed my shot.
哦，我错过了我的投篮。
Oh, you're home.
哦，你到家了。
So did.
也是如此。
They are all dead.
他们都死了。
Come on, pick me. Pick me.
来，选我。 选我。
Oh, when drop destroyed
哦，当水滴被摧毁
I know exactly where you are.
我确切地知道你在哪里。
Foetus coming be long
胎儿要长
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
Who's watching me?
谁在看着我？
Ahmed's on Thomas, dude.
艾哈迈德在看托马斯，伙计。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, eight. Plenty, a plenty. And pick Tim.
哦，八。 很多，很多。 并选择蒂姆。
Spike planted.
穗种植。
Yeah.
是的。
And always picks here only instead my
总是选择这里而不是我的
nice pair
不错的一对
left side.
左边。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, so many.
哦，这么多。
Yeah, they're all in site.
是的，他们都在现场。
Yeah.
是的。
Two of them aren't half.
其中两个不是一半。
I know. That the year time.
我知道。 那一年的时间。
Yeah.
是的。
Run in there some who's there.
跑进去一些在那里的人。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
Big Josh doing your big balls. Yeah.
大乔希做你的大球。 是的。
Mark one. 23.
标记一个。  23.
Woo. Sure, sure, sure. Oh.
呜。 确定，确定，确定。 哦。
Nice try.
不错的尝试。
This. Sorry I freaked out. No.
这。 对不起，我吓坏了。 不。
You're getting there.
你快到了。
That's Valerie.
那是瓦莱丽。
I love horror games.
我喜欢恐怖游戏。
All right.
好的。
Have you played Poppy's playtime?
你玩过波比的游戏时间吗？
Oh, I fell for.
哦，我爱上了。
The first episode.
第一集。
I'm going to emotionally support someone.
我要在情感上支持某人。
I played ball.
我打球。
Yeah. I
是的。 一世
do not like hugging swaggy.
不喜欢拥抱swaggy。
Oh. Are we going?
哦。 我们去吗？
Let's push a pushing.
让我们推一推。
Yeah, I'll support trademark. Right.
是的，我会支持商标。 对。
All right.
好的。
Just like Russian. OK.
就像俄语一样。 好的。
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。
You can counter this site
你可以反驳这个网站
oh. This one's behind sand behind me.
哦。 这个在我身后的沙子后面。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
I lost the fight sound
我现在失去了战斗的声音。在你们后面。
Watch out, watch out.
小心，小心。
Oh, he killed her.
哦，他杀了她。
Nice. Oh.
好的。 哦。
It was Omen doing.
是预兆在做的。
Oh, he's on satellite. Oh,
哦，他在卫星上。 哦那好吧。
Oh. Lily, for better, you're better than OK.
哦。 莉莉，为了更好，你比OK。
You're better than really.
你比真的好。
Oh. Oh, my.
哦。 天啊。
Gosh. That sage.
天哪。 那个贤者。
Yeah, sage.
是的，贤者。
The sheriff shots. Francine Yeah.
警长开枪。 弗朗辛 是的。
Actually, she. Said I.
其实，她。 我说。
Jinx it.
恶搞它。
Oh, my gosh.
天啊。
Screams.
尖叫声。
All right,
好的，
well, a lot of that report.
好吧，很多报告。
What we do hear gamers, I don't know.
我们确实听到了游戏玩家的声音，我不知道。
The right thing to do is sit and.
正确的做法是坐下来。
Be responsible for money.
对钱负责。
Yes. And we're going to. What's that? Yeah.
是的。 我们要去。 那是什么？ 是的。
Just go for a rush.
赶紧去吧。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, he's going to the other side.
哦，他要去另一边。
Follow this good workout, and you.
遵循这个良好的锻炼，你。
Even want to push off him or anything or whatever.
甚至想推开他或任何东西。
And they want you push first, and then they'll
他们希望你先推动，然后他们会看到我们，然后他们会旋转。
And then, I mean, it would be a long shot, like, I think.
然后，我的意思是，这将是一个长镜头，就像，我认为。
Sake.
清酒。
While we kill them.
当我们杀了他们。
And our aren't.
而我们不是。
Oh, man. Oh, he's going up there.
天啊。 哦，他正在往上走。
All right, clear terrorism.
好吧，清除恐怖主义。
It's clear.
很明显。
Right down.
就下来。
Be one less.
少一个。
Nice plant.
不错的植物。
Rees was like canteen.
里斯就像食堂。
Oh, yeah. Oh, the.
哦耶。 哦，那个。
10, tag.
10、标签。
Your eye tag is nice.
你的眼睛标签很好。
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
哦，不错，不错，不错。
Oh, my God. The eco. Yeah.
我的天啊。 生态。 是的。
They didn't buy that round for some reason.
由于某种原因，他们没有买那轮。
What's this? Strangers want me dead. Weird.
这是什么？ 陌生人要我死。 奇怪的。
Yeah. I always liked how you want that one.
是的。 我一直很喜欢你想要的那个。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
It's OK.
没关系。
It'll
它会
refrigerate.
冷藏。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I just realised you have an exposed thigh, Lily.
我才意识到你的大腿暴露在外，莉莉。
Like, I. Know it's a. Tie.
就像，我知道它是一个。 领带。
Oh, my God. What's.
我的天啊。 什么是。
Oh. And how long.
哦。 还有多久。
Never noticed that.
从来没有注意到这一点。
Hug you for a second.
拥抱你一秒钟。
I thought it was something in game, and I was like, wait. What
我认为这是游戏中的东西，我就像，等等。 什么
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Oh, Neil.
哦，尼尔。
They found my. Trap. Me?
他们找到了我的。 陷阱。 我？
What is this woman doing?
这个女人在做什么？
They found my trap.
他们发现了我的陷阱。
Apparently.
显然。
Hey, I ii
嘿，我 ii
Oh, cover going up.
哦，盖上去。
Yeah, there's some drop
是的，有一些下降
Nice.
好的。
I need a hero.
我需要一个英雄。
All know she's my eyes, and I want to god.
都知道她是我的眼睛，我要上天。
Like, is on the ropes of sin.
就像，是在罪恶的绳索上。
She's on scene right now.
她现在就在现场。
She might be coming through, Link.
她可能会通过，林克。
Oh, no.
不好了。
She's behind us.
她在我们身后。
Nice shot.
好球。
Clean. Clean.
干净的。 干净的。
That's a pretty sure.
这是相当肯定的。
What's his name?
他叫什么名字？
I Yeah. I couldn't resist.
我是的。 我无法抗拒。
When it came out.
当它出来的时候。
Oh, yeah. That's your skin.
哦耶。 那是你的皮肤。
The skin?
皮？
Yeah.
是的。
See, if you want a better gun,
看，如果你想要更好的枪，
I can buy you and me the ultrasound. OK?
我可以给你和我买超声波。 好的？
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Okay.
好的。
So did people say.
人家也是这么说的。
So did. A good start.
也是如此。 一个好的开始。
You went. Behind.
你去了。 在后面。
Okay.
好的。
I told you.
我告诉你了。
That's one
那是一个
I'll go pick a gun on.
我去捡枪。
No one's there just yet.
还没有人在那里。
Ah, look out.
啊，小心。
Can you.
你可以吗。
Nice.
好的。
But I don't know if they does.
但我不知道他们是否这样做。
Just in the arcade.
就在拱廊里。
She jumped down What's being said?
她跳了下来，说什么？
Oh. Right.
哦。 对。
Nice. Long.
好的。 长。
Oh, flawless.
哦，完美无缺。
Nice.
好的。
Nice job, guys.
干得好，伙计们。
Any good?
有什么好处吗？
I took a. Seat.
我拿了一个。 座位。
It's working. It's working.
这是工作。 这是工作。
All right, run it back.
好吧，跑回去。
It's took a worse gun for some reason.
由于某种原因，它使用了更糟糕的枪。
I think. Are these. These stronger?
我认为。 这些是。 这些更强？
Let's copy. Yeah.
让我们复制。 是的。
I got my all.
我得到了我的一切。
I'm manifesting my arse here.
我在这里展示我的屁股。
Okay. Okay.
好的。 好的。
Okay. Oh, it's already happened.
好的。 哦，已经发生了。
Uh oh, hold on.
哦，等一下。
We only have fun.
我们只有乐趣。
I mean, can you. Ah, yes. Thank you.
我的意思是，你能。 是啊。 谢谢你。
What does that say?
那说明什么？
No. Come on.
不，来吧。
Stay with.
留下来。
Sorry about that.
对于那个很抱歉。
Oh, she's pissed.
哦，她生气了。
She's pissed cause she's pissed. Oh.
她生气是因为她生气了。 哦。
I'm floored.
我晕倒了。
I can't go Sounds behind us and behind us.
我不能去我们身后和我们身后的声音。
Oh, behind you on your track.
哦，在你的轨道上。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
She won't hear me in the leaves or she didn't sing in the leaves.
她不会在树叶中听到我的声音，或者她没有在树叶中唱歌。
Oh, my. God.
天啊。 上帝。
Oh, oh, there's.
哦，哦，有。
There's another arcade, I think. I'm scared.
我想还有另一个拱廊。 我害怕。
I'm scared. I'm scared.
我害怕。 我害怕。
It's like this.
就像这样。
Could be.
可能。
We do what we do.
我们做我们所做的。
Dude, I'm scared.
伙计，我害怕。
Oh, blah,
哦，废话，
blah.
废话。
Oh, wait. That's a smoke. OK.
等一下。 那是烟。 好的。
Shut up.
住口。
I don't know what's happening. This is a. Lot of people coming.
我不知道发生了什么。 这是一个。 很多人来。
Oh, that's like.
哦，是这样的。
Oh, nice try.
哦，不错的尝试。
I won't be mean down.
我不会吝啬。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Stop it. Stop it. It's.
停下来。 停下来。 它的。
They are only near-sighted.
他们只是近视。
They got a stool.
他们有一个凳子。
Know your mind? Oh, no.
知道你的想法吗？ 不好了。
Forget about the sound.
忘记声音。
Nice try.
不错的尝试。
Nice, right?
不错，对吧？
Isn't that sounds very spooky.
这听起来是不是很吓人。
Isn't
不是吗
that actually became a horror game?
居然变成了恐怖游戏？
They came from us from both angles.
他们来自我们两个角度。
We were just looking each other dead, holding hands, not going to do a sweating
我们只是看着对方死去，手牵着手，不会出汗
problem.
问题。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
We haven't tried from the other side yet, have we?
我们还没有从另一边尝试过，不是吗？
You know, like pincer. A sight like a.
你知道，就像钳子一样。 像一个景象。
Yeah, let's do that.
是的，让我们这样做。
Okay, let's.
好吧，让我们。
Go a yeah. OK,
去，是的。 好的，
a gift.
一个礼物。
Neon likes to peek this so hot on
霓虹灯喜欢在不存在的地方偷看这个这么热
Spike down. Oh,
秒杀。 哦，
Oh, I'm all
哦，我没事。
It's not
它不是
all of them.
他们都是。
Ow, ow.
呜呜呜
One enemy.
一敌。
I didn't realise.
我没有意识到。
Oh, guys, we were hogging what's.
哦，伙计们，我们在抢夺什么。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
OK, we just need to Spike VI of
好的，我们只需要对所有的霓虹灯发育不良进行
all neon dysplasia. Yeah, this is.
Spike VI。 是的，这是。
She's not on the spike.
她不在钉子上。
She's on some Johnson. She's on sound.
她在一些约翰逊。 她的声音很好。
Yeah.
是的。
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
不错不错不错不错不错不错
I like watching Lily run out with.
我喜欢看莉莉跑出去。
The axe.
斧头。
Immediately.
立即地。
Yeah.
是的。
It's called.
它被称为。
She wants to ask them a question, that's all.
她想问他们一个问题，仅此而已。
Well.
好。
Yeah,
是的，
there are people.
那里有人。
People? People should try it again.
人们？ 人们应该再试一次。
Yeah, let's do it again.
是的，让我们再做一次。
There's no way they expect it again, right?
他们不可能再期待它了，对吧？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Be, like, all because it works here.
就像，一切都是因为它在这里有效。
They're going to go be this time.
这次他们要去。
Try to, like, cripple psychology us. But no.
试着像削弱我们的心理一样。 但不是。
And you do the same side again.
你又做同样的事情。
They will look stupid once we're on there.
一旦我们在那里，他们会看起来很愚蠢。
And watch this. Oh. Wait
并注意这一点。 哦。 等待
to find you.
找到你。
Oh, she has a fucking lying down.
哦，她他妈的躺着。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Let's go. Help.
我们走吧。 帮助。
Yeah, that was really rude.
是的，那真的很粗鲁。
I didn't think that was going to happen.
我不认为那会发生。
One 17th.
一个 17 号。
I think I know it.
我想我知道。
OK, where you. Are.
好的，你在哪里。 是。
Do you have rows oh, yeah.
你有行哦，是的。
I think all the bodies are
我认为所有的身体都是
it's kind of risky to rotate
轮换有点风险
yeah.
是的。
Let me try to get the ball on. Be
让我试着接球。 是
you know, you have a minute still.
你知道，你还有一分钟。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
Oh, ok.
哦好的。
Well.
好。
Assuming the inverted already. OK.
假设已经倒了。 好的。
I'll find you
我会找到你的
anyway.
反正。
No, no. Oh,
不，不。 哦，
oh, no.
不好了。
And see. Hot.
看看。 热的。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
But they're everywhere.
但它们无处不在。
I panic.
我恐慌。
OK, which gun to pick?
好的，选择哪把枪？
I think a couple of them are just hiding on B
我想他们中的一些人可能只是躲在 B 上。 是的。
I think so.
我认同。
Does anyone have fun?
有人玩得开心吗？
Ooh. Guns, money? Yes.
哦。 枪，钱？ 是的。
Miss Nancy.
南希小姐。
Uh, let's try B.
嗯，让我们试试B。
Yeah, he's been working for us, right?
是的，他一直在为我们工作，对吧？
So. Yeah.
所以。 是的。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
Oh. I'm all right.
哦。 我没事。
I'm off.
我走了。
Oh, could I buy wolves?
哦，我可以买狼吗？
The wolves are coming.
狼群来了。
Oh, fine.
哦，好吧。
OK, maybe. Gang.
好吧，也许吧。 刚。
Gang.
刚。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
The on flanks are so fast.
侧翼的速度如此之快。
She's so quick.
她是那么快。
Nice.
好的。
Oh, try.
哦，试试。
Oh, she's reloading.
哦，她正在重新加载。
He's got the sound.
他得到了声音。
Oh, interesting.
哦，有趣。
Oh, I. Saw what he was going there for. I like.
哦，我看到了他去那里的目的。 我喜欢。
I like it sounds.
我喜欢它的声音。
I can respect it. Mm.
我可以尊重它。 毫米。
If resisting a good position for that
如果抵抗那里的好位置。 唔。
OK, we buy him for.
好的，我们为他买单。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I'm for I'm poor, but I could buy a guardian but I'm poor.
是的，我是因为我很穷，但我可以买一个监护人，但我很穷。
I'm serious.
我是认真的。
My life is secure.
我的生活是安全的。
Yeah.
是的。
Maybe I'll share
也许我会分享
for you.
为你。
Let's try to see if we can win our fight.
让我们试试看我们能否赢得这场战斗。
Ok? Yeah.
好的？ 是的。
We are. Yes.
我们是。 是的。
I mean,
我是说，
what's that? OK.
那是什么？ 好的。
Face your fear.
面对你的恐惧。
I know
我知道
hard oh.
辛苦哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Spike down.
秒杀。
Attack. Respond.
攻击。 回应。
Oh. Oops.
哦。 哎呀。
Oops.
哎呀。
Now you.
现在轮到你。
Yeah. Oh, man.
是的。 天啊。
And you're ready to go there.
你已经准备好去那里了。
Introduce
介绍
uh, I mean, what type of dish
呃，我的意思是，什么类型的菜
or not?
或不？
A cipher I'm.
我是一个密码。
Zales.
扎莱斯。
They are.
他们是。
Nice.
好的。
This Blake
这个布莱克
you don't need this.
你不需要这个。
Like, if you kill them, they'll.
就像，如果你杀了他们，他们会的。
So that's true.
所以这是真的。
True what you will with that did for me.
真的，你会为我做的。
30 seconds left. No,
还剩 30 秒。 不，
oh, nice.
不错哦。
OK, all you have to.
好的，你必须做的。
Oh, God.
天啊。
10 seconds left.
还剩 10 秒。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh. I'm sorry.
哦。 对不起。
I try. Nice try.
我试试。 不错的尝试。
I surrender.
我投降。
We don't need surrender.
我们不需要投降。
You win this.
你赢了这个。
Yes. Never surrender.
是的。 决不投降。
All right.
好的。
A gift
一个礼物
all right, now let's try b b,
好的，现在让我们试试 b b，
yeah.
是的。
I like B.
我喜欢B。
These B's pretty sexy until.
这些 B 很性感，直到。
Cover going up.
盖上去。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
She's crazy. Yeah.
她疯了。 是的。
Yeah, I think Neon always tries to go for the Insta is the flag.
是的，我认为 Neon 总是试图以 Insta 为标志。
They win.
他们赢了。
And this time the LA Times did.
而这一次，《洛杉矶时报》做到了。
A song is behind us then. Oh,
我们身后有一首歌。 哦，他们做到了。
I'll show
我会展示
for you.
为你。
One enemy remaining.
剩下一个敌人。
For Sephora,
对于丝芙兰来说，
maybe. Okay.
也许。 好的。
Yeah, I'll plant. No.
嗯，我会种。 不。
Well.
好。
What am I doing?
我在做什么？
All mm
全部毫米
cross.
叉。
Fire.
火。
I'm scared.
我害怕。
I home is making me dizzy.
我家让我头晕目眩。
Oh. One Tony
哦。 一个托尼
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh. And on one on one, you have to.
哦。 一对一，你必须这样做。
Always go for a knife.
总是去拿刀。
Like that.
像那样。
He always gets it.
他总能得到它。
Oh, my God. This is.
我的天啊。 这是。
It's crazy.
这太疯狂了。
I like it.
我喜欢。
Okay. OK.
好的。 好的。
Oh, my God. I love this guy.
我的天啊。 我喜欢这个人。
Oh, oh, man.
哦，哦，伙计。
That was funny as fuck.
那真是他妈的好笑。
The enemy seems calling him mommy.
敌人似乎在叫他妈妈。
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
Yeah. Oh.
是的。 哦。
I'm gonna stay here to make him think we're all going to come this way.
我会留在这里让他认为我们都会这样。
I can walk.
我可以走。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
Then we set satellite.
然后我们设置卫星。
Yeah.
是的。
So for this part one.
所以对于这一部分。
To the to to decipher.
来去破译。
Yeah,
是的，
we're not this time.
我们不是这个时候。
OK, about ok.
好吧，差不多吧。
Catching mm.
抓mm。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
In a way, little hamster
在某种程度上，小仓鼠
sorry.
对不起。
You're not here. Oh, wait. OK.
你不在这里。 等一下。 好的。
They flanking.
他们在侧翼。
Oh. Oh, we got to pick a link.
哦。 哦，我们必须选择一个链接。
We could go.
我们可以走了。
Oh, let's go, let's go.
哦，走吧，走吧。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
They rotate off b, though.
但是，它们从 b 处旋转。
They check.
他们检查。
Oh, I see an assassin spike down.
哦，我看到一个刺客秒杀。
Oh, there's two on say all right, team.
哦，有两个在说好的，团队。
We had three a.
我们吃了三个。
I know exactly where you are.
我确切地知道你在哪里。
No, you don't oh.
不，你没有哦。
Nice.
好的。
I got
我有
30 seconds left.
还剩 30 秒。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
I know.
我知道。
I was like they're on map.
我就像他们在地图上一样。
Oh shit. Oh.
妈的。 哦。
Oh I was looking at the map. It's
哦，我在看地图。 它是
match point.
比赛点。
My bad. Remember. All right.
我的错。 记住。 好的。
We're only forcing.
我们只是强迫。
What do we do?
我们做什么？
What do we do.
我们做什么。
What's the play.
什么戏。
Gamers play better.
游戏玩家玩得更好。
Yeah.
是的。
We do, right?
我们有，对吧？
Yeah. Come on, people.
是的。 来吧，人们。
Yeah.
是的。
You better, Fred.
你最好，弗雷德。
Yeah, let's do it.
是的，让我们去做吧。
Just tap their heads.
只需轻敲他们的头。
Nice room.
很棒的房间。
Let's just you guys rush B from that side.
就让你们从那边冲B吧。
I'll rush rugby from the side and see what happens, OK? Oh.
我会从旁边冲橄榄球，看看会发生什么，好吗？ 哦。
Oh, oh, she got me
哦，哦，她抓住了我
shadow.
阴影。
That's awkward.
这很尴尬。
Oh, the
哦，那个
the slow or arcade oh.
慢的还是街机哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, lava.
哦，熔岩。
No way.
没门。
Oh, roger.
哦，罗杰。
Defender, if you.
后卫，如果你。
You're, like, presenting yourself. It.
你，就像，展示自己。 它。
Take me
带我去
just let
让我把我从设备里弄出来。
OK? Like this.
好的？ 像这样。
I get closer
我靠得更近
maybe if I get closer, it'll hit me.
也许如果我靠近一点，它会击中我。
Yeah.
是的。
How's it?
怎么样？
Good. Try it.
好的。 尝试一下。
All right.
好的。
Let's see if we're still there.
让我们看看我们是否还在。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
Um, know water break.
嗯，知道破水。
OK, one more game for me.
好吧，给我再来一场比赛。
OK? OK, that sounds fun.
好的？ 好吧，这听起来很有趣。
OK, we better win.
好吧，我们最好赢。
Yeah.
是的。
And then our losses.
然后是我们的损失。
Have been lost.
已经丢失。
All right.
好的。
Oh, hey, what's up? It's me again.
哦，嘿，怎么了？ 又是我。
I muted myself so I can talk to you real quick. Wow.
我把自己静音了，所以我可以很快地和你说话。 哇。
Those are good games.
这些都是好游戏。
Those are really good games.
这些都是非常好的游戏。
What? Man, like you're so close.
什么？ 男人，就像你如此接近。
Hey, fracture did fracture such a weird map.
哎，骨折确实骨折了这么诡异的地图。
For me to play on. Sometimes I feel like I'm getting it.
让我继续玩。 有时我觉得我得到了它。
I think I'll get some water to leave you.
我想我会弄点水离开你。
Okeydokey, take your time. Oh, hello.
Okeydokey，慢慢来。 哦你好。
Hello? Hello. Hi.
你好？ 你好。 你好。
Is that you? Folder?
那是你吗？ 文件夹？
Yo, what up so tall. Hello.
哟，怎么这么高。 你好。
It would be good to play Valla again.
再玩一次瓦拉就好了。
What? Can you send me your fuji, actually.
什么？ 你能把你的富士发给我吗？
Oh, sure.
行，可以。
Thank you. You know it. You
谢谢你。 你知道的。 你
oh, man.
天啊。
Only nominal, man.
只是名义上的，伙计。
Hi. Nice to meet you. Amongst fun. Popinjay.
你好。 很高兴见到你。 在乐趣之中。 波宾杰。
Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你。
I'm. I'm Fall Grove, and I.
我是。 我是福尔格罗夫，我。
Just thought I stock all of your twitters.
只是以为我储存了你所有的推特。
Oh, like.
哦，喜欢。
What did you, like, profile us?
你对我们有什么看法？
You like, under?
你喜欢，下？
No, no, no.
不不不。
The in and outs of what we do every day.
我们每天所做的事情的来龙去脉。
Know where we live aren't at the school.
知道我们住的地方不在学校。
We go to our wives.
我们去找我们的妻子。
Our children. You are, you know.
我们的孩子。 你是，你知道的。
A big boy.
一个大男孩。
I love being to the.
我喜欢去。
Same.
相同的。
I wish I was 20 right now.
我希望我现在是 20 岁。
If only.
要是。
I think being.
我认为存在。
Around all the tattoos.
周围所有的纹身。
Huh? Lila sorry.
嗯？ 莉拉对不起。
What tattoos?
什么纹身？
Oh, know, this is the new me. I'm.
哦，知道，这是新的我。 我是。
I'm just, you know, no one understands me.
我只是，你知道，没有人了解我。
You know.
你知道。
No one understands me.
没有人理解我。
God, I.
天啊，我。
Feel that there's a demon sealed in this arm.
感觉这手臂里封印着一只恶魔。
Exactly.
确切地。
It's not a phase. It's not a phase.
它不是一个阶段。 它不是一个阶段。
My mom, the lifestyle.
我的妈妈，生活方式。
I mean, I used to unironically really love hot topic.
我的意思是，我曾经非常喜欢热门话题。
I still unironically love hop.
我仍然非常喜欢啤酒花。
Told me, too. But as you. Should.
也告诉我了。 但是像你一样。 应该。
Know, no, I wasn't getting angry.
知道，不，我没有生气。
It was just like, that's me. Now.
就像，那就是我。 现在。
That's cool. Stuff like that.
太棒了。 类似的东西。
Some cool t shirts once in a while.
偶尔穿一些很酷的T恤。
And this is a safe space.
这是一个安全的空间。
Like, nice chokers and little knickknacks.
比如，漂亮的项链和小摆设。
Are we ready for this tour?
我们准备好参加这次旅行了吗？
Oh, hell, yeah. Oh.
哦，见鬼，是的。 哦。
Yeah.
是的。
Invites are for genuine sorry.
邀请是真正的抱歉。
My man.
我的男人。
How do I do, you guys?
我该怎么做，你们？
Oh, I, uh.
哦，我，呃。
I have to. Or from in.
我必须。 或从内。
Somehow, I saw an addict.
不知怎的，我看到了一个瘾君子。
Oh, I'm still level 16.
哦，我还是16级。
You can just right click me and do an invite.
您只需右键单击我并发出邀请即可。
Oh, do you have, I guess. Yeah.
哦，你有吗，我猜。 是的。
Make sure automatically I need.
确保自动我需要。
You as a friend just to come. Across you.
你作为朋友刚来。 在你身边。
Your fortune is so shiny.
你的财运如此耀眼。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, yeah. Everybody's good to go.
是啊是啊。 大家可以出发了。
Let's pop heads.
让我们爆头。
All right. We're a squad of five now.
好的。 我们现在是五人小队。
We can't lose.
我们不能输。
We have to win this.
我们必须赢得这场比赛。
Yes, but I don't want to lay 13 of them or anything.
是的，但我不想放置其中的 13 个或任何东西。
I want it at least like that.
我希望它至少是那样的。
Yeah. Yeah, like a fight. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的。 是的，就像打架一样。 耶耶耶。
We could a fight.
我们可以打架。
Remember that one card game where we want, like, 30 rounds?
还记得我们想要的一款纸牌游戏，比如 30 轮吗？
I just.
我只是。
Oh, I wanted to die.
哦，我想死。
I was, like, in over an hour.
我是，就像，在一个多小时内。
It was me. You, Michael sounds awful. Oh.
那是我。 你，迈克尔听起来很糟糕。 哦。
It went on. For we had two.
它继续。 因为我们有两个。
Games like that back there, like, just so many rounds
像那样的游戏，就像，就这么多轮哦，我以前从来没有发生过这种情况。
Those games are only fun if you windle.
那些游戏只有在你放松时才有趣。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Oh, yeah. You feel that I'm wasted.
哦耶。 你觉得我很浪费。
Uh oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
But when you win, you feel like a goddamn champion at the end of an arc.
但是当你获胜时，你会感觉自己就像一个该死的冠军在弧线的尽头。
Uh huh.
嗯。
Let's go tell champion I like him.
让我们去告诉冠军我喜欢他。
Yeah, I like his. I like the way you say Arctic.
是的，我喜欢他的。 我喜欢你说北极的方式。
You say it again.
你再说一遍。
I'm March.
我是三月。
Yeah, Arctic Walk.
是的，北极漫步。
I'm not half. British.
我不是一半。 英国人。
I've slowly lost my British accent, so I've got a weird accent. No.
我慢慢地失去了我的英国口音，所以我有一种奇怪的口音。 不。
No, it's really cool.
不，真的很酷。
I wanted to finish high school.
我想读完高中。
Oh, God. Do it, do it, do it.
天啊。 做，做，做。
Do it, do it.
做，做。
Do it. Yeah.
去做吧。 是的。
So, are we ready for this?
那么，我们准备好了吗？
So guide. Us.
所以引导。 我们。
OK, you know what? I'm doing.
好的，你知道吗？ 我在做。
Good. It's getting there, getting there, getting there, going. Good.
好的。 它正在到达那里，到达那里，到达那里，去。 好的。
But you pay me for the basics.
但是你付给我基本的费用。
Just hit me with the Volvo.
就用沃尔沃打我。
Oh. Did you want to go for some?
哦。 你想去一些吗？
Is that the same Maccas Australia?
是同一个Maccas Australia吗？
I thought that's.
我以为是。
Yeah, not Australian.
是的，不是澳大利亚人。
All the time.
每时每刻。
Oh. These Mickey D's.
哦。 这些米奇 D。
Oh, the kids. Get some Mickey D's brothers.
哦，孩子们。 找一些米奇 D 的兄弟。
Yeah, yeah. For them.
是啊是啊。 为他们。
Rough eat jellied eels.
粗吃鳗鱼冻。
What is jellied eels?
什么是鳗鱼冻？
Are we talking in British accents now for the rest of the stream?
我们现在在用英国口音说话吗？
I mean.
我是说。
That sounds really fun.
这听起来真的很有趣。
I'm down for that. Oh, yeah.
我为此感到沮丧。 哦耶。
Look, it doesn't have to do anything.
看，它不需要做任何事情。
Yeah, I've always just.
是的，我一直只是。
Just insists and talks to them again.
只是坚持并再次与他们交谈。
If you speak another language.
如果你说另一种语言。
I came in some
我进来了一些
Vietnamese a bit, but that's on.
越南语有点，但就是这样。
I don't really.
我不是很。
I'm bilingual with the English and Japanese
我会说英语和日语
yeah.
是的。
I've got like basic comprehension of Spanish and Japanese.
我对西班牙语和日语有了基本的理解。
And Spanish in high school, just like, yeah, I don't remember too much now, but.
还有高中的西班牙语，就像，是的，我现在不记得太多了，但是。
One day I start to bibliotheque. Of course.
有一天，我开始阅读书目。 当然。
You know, I like, I like Plato, Il Bologna as well.
你知道，我喜欢，我也喜欢柏拉图，Il Bologna。
That one's really handy
那个真的好用
now. Not be in. C c.
现在。 不在。 C c。
I want to try
我想尝试
them.
他们。
My favourite word right now is like real Torah.
我现在最喜欢的词就像真正的妥拉。
I don't know, it just sounds so nice.
我不知道，它只是听起来很好听。
Oh, I love that.
哦，我喜欢那个。
Because Raina says. It.
因为雷娜说。 它。
That's you.
那是你。
And I don't know, I just.
我不知道，我只是。
You're people.
你们是人。
It's a meme or something.
这是一个模因或什么的。
I'm not sure what.
我不确定是什么。
Yeah, it's a mean kind of wild.
是的，这是一种卑鄙的野性。
And especially if they're like, small, incised.
尤其是如果它们像，小，切割。
Like Torah
就像妥拉
I speak survival Asian languages.
我说生存亚洲语言。
Oh, Bible each way, right?
哦，圣经各方面，对吧？
Yeah. A survival level, like.
是的。 一个生存级别，比如。
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
是的。 哦耶。
When you visit.
当你访问。
A. Toilet with a scarf.
A. 带围巾的马桶。
Oh. That's a good there.
哦。 那里很好。
That's. Yes.
那是。 是的。
Imagine that.
想象一下。
You know.
你知道。
It comes harmony the all comes.
它来了和谐，一切都来了。
I know.
我知道。
Imagine when they ask for the restroom and then they give you, like,
想象一下，当他们要求上厕所，然后他们给你，比如，最复杂的方向。
the most complicated directions. Oh, yeah, right.
哦，是的，对。
The reply the only.
唯一的回复。
One I know is Rama on local. Got it.
我知道的一个是当地的拉玛。 知道了。
That's it.
这就对了。
Oh, is it is it that far.
哦，就这么远吗。
From the on the got it.
从一开始就知道了。
The equivalent in Netflix and chill.
Netflix中的等价物和寒意。
Yes it is. Yeah, yeah.
是的。 是啊是啊。
Yeah.
是的。
It's just like, hey, come over and you remember
就像，嘿，过来，你记得你真的很想他妈的我想。 哦。
Oh rolling it sounds way better than.
哦，滚动听起来比。
Ramen and hot and.
拉面和热和。
Everything and sounds like a good.
一切和听起来都很好。
Friday.
星期五。
You think that's kind of well the prices are going up
你认为这很好 价格正在上涨
and they're selling sometimes it's not the best.
他们卖的有时不是最好的。
And they have way less original content nowadays.
现在他们的原创内容越来越少。
Yeah,
是的，
that's after my own car.
那是在我自己的车之后。
I'll go.
我要走了。
Yeah, I'll set up one a.
是的，我会设置一个。
I'm just going to see
我只是想看看我能不能惹到人。
Oh, so they're watching me.
哦，所以他们在看着我。
Yeah. Watch me.
是的。 看着我。
I got some.
我得到了一些。
Oh, what's it called?
哦，它叫什么？
Amy's good.
艾米很好。
Ilona, I thought, do you want me to come up the
伊洛娜，我想，你想让我上来吗？
I think.
我认为。
Yeah, I come over here, they nerf me as a sentinel, so I kind of suck now.
是的，我来这里，他们把我当作哨兵削弱，所以我现在有点烂。
Oh, there.
哦，那里。
Said she's got he got nerf oil.
说她得到了他得到了神经油。
Quite a bit. What they do to him.
相当多。 他们对他做什么。
They took away my trademark, my other trademark charge and something else.
他们拿走了我的商标，我的其他商标费用和其他东西。
And forget
然后忘记
oh e be ok.
哦，没关系。
Oh shit.
妈的。
Doesn't look like any came through.
好像没有人通过。
My walls going down.
我的墙要倒了。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
As long as heaven on.
只要上天。
No no shit the.
不不该。
Insight.
洞察力。
Oh, there's some mean there's some man I.
哦，有些意思是有些人我。
Went back.
回去。
To saw one on the aisle.
在过道上看到一个。
She's like 55. You got it, got it.
她就像 55 岁。你明白了，明白了。
Rayna's trapped in there
蕾娜被困在那里
waiting garage.
等待车库。
Yeah.
是的。
Crash corner oh my God.
崩溃角落哦，我的上帝。
She's fucking. Kill killing.
她在他妈的。 杀戮杀戮。
Nice, nice.
好好。
Yo you two, you had the same idea.
你们两个，你们有同样的想法。
No, we rushed at the same time.
不，我们同时冲了。
Yeah.
是的。
So some, like, cartoon shit a virus.
所以一些，比如，卡通狗屎病毒。
You know what?
你知道吗？
Yeah.
是的。
You know that meme of, like, the characters
你知道那个表情包，比如角色互相看着对方和电话的各个方面吗？
That was exactly.
那正是。
That was like. Wait a minute.
就像那样。 等一下。
Lily, I'm manifesting your frag outs.
莉莉，我在显化你的残缺。
Oh, for this game.
哦，为了这场比赛。
Let's go to your audience. Apparently.
让我们去你的听众。 显然。
Yeah, this is our best.
是的，这是我们最好的。
Yeah, I think. Focus now is off me.
是的，我想。 现在焦点不在我身上。
That's a good start.
这是一个好的开始。
You know, one thing nice.
你知道，一件好事。
One time it was a jet
有一次是一架喷气式飞机
know. Oh.
知道。 哦。
You're coming through Gates, man.
你正在通过盖茨，伙计。
You're just lurking here.
你只是潜伏在这里。
Behind Blast now.
现在在 Blast 后面。
Oh, it's like three or four.
哦，好像三四个。
Be just hiding in sponge.
只是躲在海绵里。
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
And you had a you had a marshal.
你有一个元帅。
They saw me.
他们看到了我。
They pushed me.
他们推我。
Yeah, I think so. Then push it, though.
是的，我想是的。 然后推它，虽然。
I don't think.
我不这样认为。
Oh, they're still around. Men, enemies.
哦，他们还在。 男人，敌人。
But I mean, like, just outside of B gates.
但我的意思是，就在B门外。
Or gates.
或门。
Oh, yeah. When great.
哦耶。 伟大的时候。
Creatures.
生物。
Oh, nice kill.
哦，不错的杀戮。
Of their.
他们的。
Enemy. That's like that's like Spike.
敌人。 就像那样，就像斯派克。
Nice, nice.
好好。
Nice. Nice. Nice, too nice.
好的。 好的。 不错，太不错了。
Good around.
周围好。
Pretty guns.
漂亮的枪。
Thing. You want to kill it? I wonder.
事物。 你想杀了它？ 我想知道。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, this is the killjoy one.
哦，这是杀戮的。
Pretty rarely the killjoy one. Yes.
很少有killjoy的。 是的。
You right.
你说得对。
That works.
这样可行。
Yeah.
是的。
Bonus round.
奖金回合。
Wait, they bought that round
等等，他们买了那轮
I'm like, oh, my gun tags is so much.
我想，哦，我的枪牌太多了。
She's kind of low, though.
不过，她有点低。
No one. Him can.
没有人。 他可以。
Unlock.
开锁。
Oh, I'm not tested anymore.
哦，我不再测试了。
Jets working B, I'm going to rotate.
喷气机工作 B，我要旋转。
He just me.
他只是我。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I think oh, my God. Oh.
我想哦，我的上帝。 哦。
Nice, nice. Nice.
好好。 好的。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Enemy spy, man.
敌人的间谍，伙计。
Nigeria killed like that.
尼日利亚就这样被杀了。
Nice in and very good.
很好，很好。
I don't want to die.
我不要死。
So that's all you guys know.
所以这就是你们所知道的。
My dog.
我的狗。
Lily cracked.
百合裂开了。
Oh, my God. I'm really feeling this cancer.
我的天啊。 我真的感受到了这种癌症。
Yeah, this is the game. This is the game.
是的，这就是游戏。 这就是游戏。
I'm really feeling. It.
我真的很有感觉。 它。
Oh, don't jinx it, please.
哦，请不要诅咒它。
I oh, yeah.
我哦，是的。
We kind of jinx the last time, didn't we?
上次我们有点恶作剧，不是吗？
All on you guys were doing.
你们都在做。
Those about those out feeling it again.
那些关于那些再次感受到它的人。
You can jinx of feeling it.
你可以感觉到它的厄运。
I'm really feeling it.
我真的感觉到了。
Yeah, you can as soon as you hear that, it just makes me throw and smash. Oh.
是的，你一听到就可以，它只会让我摔倒。 哦。
Just to end the game as fast as possible
只是为了尽快结束游戏并远离震惊
oh, they love middle games.
哦，他们喜欢中场比赛。
No one.
没有人。
No one beast so far.
到目前为止没有一只野兽。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, my God, she's tied. 57.
哦，我的上帝，她被绑了。  57.
I did not expect her to be there.
我没想到她会在那里。
She's walking up.
她正在往上走。
I mean, I'm walking up.
我的意思是，我正在向上走。
Be mean
刻薄
she might of grabbed.
她可能会抓住。
No, she didn't walk up. I mean, she's on camera. No.
不，她没有走上去。 我的意思是，她在镜头前。 不。
They're all middle top.
他们都是中上。
Yeah, I think they're walking catwalk or they're rotating too.
是的，我认为他们正在走秀，或者他们也在旋转。
I mean
我是说
they're mid definitely right now.
他们现在肯定是中等的。
Yeah. OK, right.
是的。 好的，对。
It's on me.
它在我身上。
Oh. But
哦。 但
oh shit.
妈的。
Oh, you got this. You got this.
哦，你明白了。 你得到了这个。
They don't know, you know. And now they know.
他们不知道，你知道。 现在他们知道了。
Oh now they know.
哦，现在他们知道了。
Wait, no, no, they're flesh.
等等，不，不，它们是肉体。
OK, ok, ok. OK, ok. I'll stay on.
好好好。 好的好的。 我会留下来。
The left side.
左侧。
Left side, of course.
当然是左侧。
Oh. Oh, good wall game.
哦。 哦，好的墙游戏。
Oh, wow. OK. She's crazy.
哦，哇。 好的。 她疯了。
You have your ulti.
你有你的终极。
Oh, my God. It's possible we have.
我的天啊。 我们有可能。
Go, go, go. Go.
去！去！去。 去。
Yeah.
是的。
His real name is. Folger of Falls.
他的真名是。 福尔杰。
Auto.
汽车。
Waking up is Folger in your cart.
醒来是您购物车中的 Folger。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
OK, I. Got one.
好的，我有一个。
More.
更多的。
One more.
多一个。
Five.
五。
Oh, no, she's on time.
哦，不，她准时。
Oh, close, close.
哦，接近，接近。
As I. Said.
就像我说的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
No. Can I watch him in this fun abilty?
不，我可以用这个有趣的技能看他吗？
Oh, yeah, we.
哦，是的，我们。
I think we save here too.
我想我们也保存在这里。
Oh, yeah. I'm just buying like.
哦耶。 我只是买喜欢。
Ok. Oh, ok.
行。 哦好的。
And yeah, my name comes from electric.
是的，我的名字来自电动。
She as lol.
她一样大声笑。
I'm a literature nerd say ok.
我是一个文学书呆子说好的。
So did so this.
所以就这样做了。
Past so dead.
过去那么死。
At. Peak. It's all muted. Now.
在。 顶峰。 全部静音。 现在。
So how do you.
那你怎么办。
Know how do they do they there's always one.
知道他们是怎么做的，他们总是有一个。
A catwalk for sure.
肯定是走秀。
Oh, they're coming.
哦，他们来了。
Next now how does one activated nature up the candle.
接下来现在如何激活蜡烛。
OK or a man
好的还是男人
129 on killjoy 52 on stage.
129在舞台上的killjoy 52。
Oh someone's there.
哦，有人在那里。
I spotted him it.
我发现他了。
May be. Oh god a lot of that.
或许。 哦，天哪，很多。
Arm of the Russian government I mean just hanging.
俄罗斯政府的手臂，我的意思是挂着。
Around yeah.
周围是的。
Yeah. Went the catwalk.
是的。 走秀了。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Oh, shit. Oh, good to hatch.
妈的。 哦，好孵化。
All right.
好的。
Yeah, right there to.
是的，就在那里。
I had a zero.
我有一个零。
So 22 total
所以总共22个
blank. Blank.
空白的。 空白的。
I can do that.
我能做到。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
There. What's back there, Michael?
那里。 迈克尔，后面是什么？
Back in on a million.
回到一百万。
Oh, nice, nice.
哦，不错，不错。
Marshall Maximiser Shoeless Cash Maximiser.
Marshall Maximiser 无鞋现金最大化者。
Oh, oh, yeah. I tried.
哦，哦，是的。 我试过。
Throwing a.
投掷一个。
Thought.
想法。
Watch mid maybe.
看中期吧。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm scared.
我害怕。
30 seconds left.
还剩 30 秒。
On the soccer.
在足球场上。
Yeah, and I spotted a nice.
是的，我发现了一个不错的。
Nice clean.
好干净。
Is going.
正在走。
You can give me your gun, your good.
你可以给我你的枪，你的好。
You can did.
你可以做到。
I hate that slow feels wrong.
我讨厌那种缓慢的感觉是不对的。
Watch out and
注意和
you should
你应该
well, a physical ready?
好了，身体准备好了吗？
That's a good start.
这是一个好的开始。
OK, just.
好的，只是。
Just tap their heads forehead.
只需轻拍他们的额头即可。
Easy dot their heads. Easy peasy. Here.
轻松点他们的头。 十分简单。 这里。
Easy peasy.
十分简单。
Oh. Let me not
哦。 让我不要
I'm not going to push this anymore.
我不会再推动这个了。
I know someone's watching it.
我知道有人在看。
Maybe
也许
is there a lobby thing?
有大厅的事吗？
It's just meant to be.
它只是注定的。
Push.
推。
Raise and rain. RB
升起和下雨。  RB
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
That's a lot of link because I hit pretty
这是很多链接，因为我打得很漂亮
hard.
难的。
I got you there's another one in there right.
我知道了，里面还有一个。
I might be falling back.
我可能会倒退。
Down. B Oh, so extended, right?
向下。  B 哦，这么长，对吧？
Like you see.
就像你看到的那样。
Spike still here watching it.
斯派克还在这里看着它。
Again. OK.
再次。 好的。
Go in corner them.
进入他们的角落。
Yeah. Oh.
是的。 哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
It gets left you standing on top of the box.
它让你站在盒子的顶部。
Not mine. Oh,
不是我的。 哦，
well, all agencies work with me.
好吧，所有机构都与我合作。
It's like
它像是
chatter.
喋喋不休。
No, I think I got you.
不，我想我得到了你。
I can buy for people.
我可以给人们买。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Nice really nice noise.
尼斯真的很好的噪音。
Noise. Love having a sugar daddy.
噪音。 喜欢有个傍大款。
Sugar, sugar.
糖，糖。
All right, kill them.
好吧，杀了他们。
Oh, it's the only thing so far.
哦，这是迄今为止唯一的事情。
Meant to be. Meant to be. Yeah.
原意是要。 原意是要。 是的。
They threw a grenade up city.
他们向城市投掷了一枚手榴弹。
Were they a link? B link. I mean.
他们是链接吗？  B 链接。 我是说。
A bullet can be link.
项目符号可以是链接。
OK, um, hear anything over here?
好的，嗯，听到这里有什么吗？
They might be waiting for me to push up something.
他们可能在等我推一些东西。
Oh, that's a lot.
哦，很多。
And when I'm. Pushing. Ah, I'm gonna rotate.
当我在。 推动。 啊，我要转了。
I mean,
我是说，
a lot mid, right?
很多中间，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah. And
是的。 和
nice screen
漂亮的屏幕
nice one.
好一个。
I down.
我下来。
Watch out the left and right corner.
注意左右角。
I think she might be there like
我想她可能在那里
oh yeah. Always. She's good. Never mind.
哦耶。 总是。 她是很好的。 没关系。
I forgot. Of.
我忘了。 的。
All the killjoy. Yeah, I took her
所有的杀戮。 是的，我带走了她
my suitcase.
我的手提箱。
I'm watching B link. I mean B, man, I know. Oh.
我在看B链接。 我的意思是B，伙计，我知道。 哦。
Oh that corner the whole time.
哦，那个角落一直都是。
Yes. Need
是的。 需要
oh the delta like 49.
哦，像 49 的三角洲。
Five. Oh.
五。 哦。
Oh. Job guys doing great.
哦。 工作人员做得很好。
We're doing really good.
我们做得很好。
Yeah. Yeah. Using something own.
是的。 是的。 使用自己的东西。
No offence.
没有恶意。
But fucking go.
但他妈的去。
That frickin grow.
那个该死的成长。
I love.
我爱。
Like four. Critical stuff.
像四个。 关键的东西。
Yeah. It's
是的。 它是
cookies. Even, even. Crouching.
饼干。 甚至，甚至。 蹲下。
Yes, always. There's not even a question.
是的，总是。 连一个问题都没有。
Why you even ask. Only she.
你为什么还要问。 只有她。
Just. Oh, wow.
只是。 哦，哇。
Oh, four. Three, four, three.
哦，四个。 三，四，三。
That got. It.
那得了。 它。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
They killed me as I had it.
他们杀了我，就像我拥有它一样。
Socks hurry.
袜子快点。
Yeah. That put you in a hard.
是的。 这让你很难受。
Oh yeah.
哦耶。
They got to pick a they probably put that you guys.
他们必须选择一个他们可能放的你们。
Go down.
下去。
Oh why not.
哦，为什么不呢。
Nice. Oh that's spike on one. Spike on one.
好的。 哦，这是一个秒杀。 钉在一个。
We can, we can play for that.
我们可以，我们可以为此而战。
They can't grab it and run out against
他们不能抓住它并跑出来反对
is also flanking.
也在侧翼。
Yeah. I'm going to do a.
是的。 我要做一个。
Little big everyone.
大家有点大。
Say on site I can grab that and run
在现场说我可以抓住它并运行
a nice.
一个不错的。
Wall to shoot your crazy.
墙射你的疯子。
Oh I went for me.
哦，我去找我了。
All right let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
Just how nice Colombo style. Oh.
多么美妙的科伦坡风格。 哦。
Do they run.
他们跑吗。
Oh, yeah, they ran.
哦，是的，他们跑了。
They ran. OK,
他们跑。 好的，
look. Oh, they're from Mexico.
看。 哦，他们来自墨西哥。
Nice is. Another one.
尼斯是。 另一个。
Oh. Oh, bang.
哦。 哦，砰。
That was a hard game.
那是一场艰苦的比赛。
They're moving together. Fine.
他们正在一起移动。 美好的。
Yeah. Nice try.
是的。 不错的尝试。
Nice try.
不错的尝试。
I could buy some yeah.
我可以买一些是的。
I can buy for you guys are talk. Talk you?
我可以买给你们说话。 谈你？
Yeah, I can buy for you. I'm going to this round.
是的，我可以给你买。 我要去这一轮。
I'm going to watch and see if that's OK.
我要去看看，看看是否可以。
Yeah, just wild me.
是的，只是让我疯狂。
Mm. Yeah.
毫米。 是的。
Yeah, I saw that. I was watching your POV. Yeah,
是的，我看到了。 我在看你的 POV。 是的，
that freaked. Me.
吓坏了。 我。
Like he was clearly trying to block you off, but she just lifted you off.
就像他显然想阻止你，但她只是把你拉了起来。
Yeah.
是的。
Drinking somebody.
喝人。
Right.
对。
Oh, I know. There's another one.
哦，我知道。 还有一个。
I heard multiple.
听过很多次。
She's in that corner.
她在那个角落。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Can look at my car for me.
可以帮我看看我的车。
I look at link. Yeah.
我看链接。 是的。
Thank you for doing this.
谢谢你这样做。
Hello.
你好。
Oh. Racist raises hit a 90
哦。 种族主义者加薪达到 90
share market or issue.
股票市场或发行。
Oh, when I knock a corner.
哦，当我敲了一个角落。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Yeah.
是的。
Back on the machine.
回到机器上。
First we have Spike. No, Spike.
首先我们有斯派克。 不，斯派克。
Not. Nice job, guys.
不是。 干得好，伙计们。
We're not getting the message.
我们没有收到消息。
Leave it to me.
交给我。
You like a buy or something?
你喜欢买什么的？
I didn't know that, huh?
我不知道，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Team game.
团队游戏。
It's not.
它不是。
A game.
一个游戏。
Yeah, you game.
是的，你的游戏。
The team deserves it
球队应得的
as a team. You ready?
作为一个团队。 你准备好了吗？
As a member of this team?
作为这个团队的一员？
I agree.
我同意。
Yeah, oo si, si.
是的，哦，我，我。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
All that Spike Lee.
所有的斯派克·李。
Spike down.
秒杀。
Clean.
干净的。
This is the map that made an entry, Chris.
这是进入的地图，克里斯。
Oh, don't see that.
哦，没看到。
Oh, look.
哦，看。
Clean. Zurich.
干净的。 苏黎世。
I'll got it.
我会得到它。
Oh, TOM In. 12 out.
哦，汤姆。  12出。
I need help. I need help.
我需要帮助。 我需要帮助。
A little. Down.
一点。 向下。
We got this. Where's.
我们得到了这个。 哪里。
Oh, oh, gosh.
哦，哦，天哪。
OK, ok. OK, ok. OK.
好的好的。 好的好的。 好的。
Yeah. Okay.
是的。 好的。
All right, guys.
好吧，伙计们。
A little spooky duty, right?
有点恐怖的职责，对吧？
If you need help figuring out how.
如果您需要帮助找出方法。
Maybe I.
也许我。
Could get hold.
能抓住。
Should I hold a hug? Yeah.
我应该抱抱吗？ 是的。
So they're forced to go on b where lily set up
所以他们被迫去百合建立的地方
if if I die from my peak,
如果我在巅峰时期死去，
then I'll say, yeah, ok.
然后我会说，是的，好的。
Only if I die, though.
不过，只有我死了。
Ready? I think lily has a sight held down us
准备好？ 我想莉莉有一种景象把我们压住了
as a future.
作为未来。
Literally never lose us.
从字面上看，永远不会失去我们。
Yeah. Never. Yeah.
是的。 绝不。 是的。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Okay.
好的。
Maybe yeah.
也许是的。
Old, old.
老，老。
Stinky.
臭。
Now you're stinky now.
现在你臭了。
Oh, that's.
哦，那是。
Well, that's big for us.
嗯，这对我们来说很重要。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Taking has really stinky
服用真的很臭
Oh. Oh, oh, oh.
哦。 哦哦哦。
Are they challenging the old?
他们在挑战老人吗？
No way.
没门。
On the way they came up the challenging the old.
在路上，他们遇到了挑战老人。
They're trying again.
他们正在再次尝试。
Oh, gosh.
哦，天哪。
Oh, there's one that pushed off gardens.
哦，有一个推开花园。
Yeah. Rose came to tree crazy.
是的。 罗斯疯狂地来到树上。
What's gone.
什么没了。
Oh, she got me
哦，她得到了我
outta your. Cracks.
离开你的。 裂缝。
Oh, no. God.
不好了。 上帝。
Big rocket.
大火箭。
OK, they had to OK, shoo, shoo.
好的，他们必须好的，嘘，嘘。
Let's hear it. Let's go.
让我们听听。 我们走吧。
There's one heaven.
有一个天堂。
There's one heaven. I think it's sage.
有一个天堂。 我认为是圣人。
Yeah,
是的，
oh, she was behind you. Oh.
哦，她在你身后。 哦。
Wait, what's your right and what's your left?
等等，你的右边是什么，你的左边是什么？
Yeah. Then, yeah. Besides.
是的。 那么，是的。 除了。
Oh, nice try.
哦，不错的尝试。
I'm right here.
我就在这里。
Oh, my gosh.
天啊。
Like my back up into her.
就像我背对她一样。
I thought I was five heading, but they five headed.
我以为我是五个头，但他们五个头。
We can't take should we throw this place.
如果我们扔掉这个地方，我们不能拿走。
We don't go 930.
我们不去930。
I think we got this. Got this.
我想我们得到了这个。 收到。
I'm going to wash them with this.
我要用这个洗它们。
I bought.
我买了。
Up. Look, I could buy you a spectre
向上。 听着，我可以给你买一件幽灵买的盔甲。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Thank you. Yeah. The curse. Doesn't exist.
谢谢你。 是的。 诅咒。 不存在。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I. Am just going back.
是的，我只是要回去。
You guys, I want to play small points let's do this.
各位，我想打小分就这样吧。
A little bit.
一点点。
The 84 curse also exists.
84诅咒也存在。
OK, well well, then.
好，好，那么。
That's just not how.
那不是怎么回事。
There's a lot.
有很多。
I just. Can't.
我只是。 不能。
Uh huh, ok.
嗯嗯，好的。
Oh, that doesn't penetrate that.
哦，这并没有穿透那个。
I'm done.
我做完。
What do you mean,
你是什​​么意思，
it's just
这只是
oh, man freezes there too.
哦，人也僵在那里。
Yeah.
是的。
She doesn't want to sight jets on sight.
她不想看到喷气式飞机。
Well, no way, man.
好吧，没办法，伙计。
It's not the I
这不是我
Oh like.
哦喜欢。
That's right. 78.
没错。  78.
Tell me.
告诉我。
All I got is so many things happening.
我得到的只是发生了很多事情。
My life son was destroyed. All right.
我一生的儿子被毁了。 好的。
Wow. OK.
哇。 好的。
Plenty
很多
plenty.
很多。
And so oh.
所以哦。
She's drunk. She's jumping. Oh, no.
她喝醉了。 她在跳。 不好了。
His wallet.
他的钱包。
Oh, that's her. Oh.
哦，是她。 哦。
You're standing.
你站着。
OK, ok. OK, ok.
好的好的。 好的好的。
Look, look, look.
看，看，看。
Like all the man's hits in the world, ok?
就像世界上所有男人的热门歌曲一样，好吗？
Or at stake right now.
或者现在处于危险之中。
He wouldn't let down man things, right?
他不会让男人的事情失望的，对吧？
Oh, good try.
哦，很好的尝试。
Try to think.
试着思考。
Nice t what?
不错呢？
Anti switching continues.
反切换继续。
OK, we're here for so, like, we don't get the curse right?
好的，我们在这里是为了这样，比如，我们没有得到诅咒吗？
And we play.
我们玩。
Tough to prevent the curse from. Happening.
难以阻止诅咒。 正在发生。
Yeah, I saved it.
是的，我保存了。
That's why I fired my old hat.
这就是为什么我解雇了我的旧帽子。
No one that's so easy.
没有人是那么容易的。
Yeah, that's what I was doing.
是的，这就是我正在做的。
Yeah. Yeah, exactly, exactly.
是的。 是的，正是，正是。
It's to dig for family. Harvey
就是为家人挖坑。 哈维
that's exactly what the plan was.
这正是计划的内容。
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
对，对，对，对。
Do you like coffee?
你喜欢咖啡吗？
I like colleague. E.
我喜欢同事。  E.
I like coffee.
我喜欢咖啡。
Soccer.
足球。
What soccer club?
什么足球俱乐部？
Yeah, I love coffee flavoured stuff. Me too.
是的，我喜欢咖啡味的东西。 我也是。
But I also. Like off here.
但我也是。 喜欢这里。
God damn it.
他妈的。
No, oh.
不，哦。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, my God. What?
我的天啊。 什么？
Oh, my God. I didn't even see that.
我的天啊。 我什至没有看到。
She just
她只是
they can't get all of us.
他们无法得到我们所有人。
There's one behind the middle box, one by mailbox, one's left side
一个在中间的盒子后面，一个在邮箱旁边，一个在左边
I'm very low.
我很低落。
I can't watch.
我看不下去了
You got
你得到了
oh, the I.
哦，我。
Oh, man.
天啊。
I'm getting hit by the eye so often.
我经常被眼睛撞到。
The last player standing
最后一位站立的玩家
reloading.
重新加载。
Oh, liberty. Oh.
哦，自由。 哦。
I was a big brain.
我是个大脑袋。
Grenade.
手榴弹。
First. Thing in the. Beginning.
第一的。 里面的东西。 开始。
I had no idea what it was.
我不知道那是什么。
All right, you heard it. And I died.
好吧，你听到了。 我死了。
Who you are.
你是谁。
Go be these terror insects.
去成为这些恐怖的昆虫。
I don't like a choo. Choo choo
我不喜欢一个choo。 咻咻咻咻。
Maybe when they all rotated, we could have rotated away.
也许当它们都旋转时，我们本可以旋转离开。
Yeah. Mm
是的。 嗯，这听起来是谁？
Weak.
虚弱的。
That's not really true.
这不是真的。
This just tapped their heads easy.
这只是轻敲他们的头。
That's not really wow.
那不是真的哇。
How do they know how the fuck she
他们怎么知道她他妈的
oh, hold my shoulder.
哦，抱住我的肩膀。
Ouch.
哎哟。
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁丁．．．．．．．
Ding, ding.
叮叮叮
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, oh, oh,
哦哦哦，
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. OK.
哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦~ 好的。
So I learnt. I learnt something there.
所以我学会了。 我在那里学到了一些东西。
I was off.
我走了。
The lot, so not. To pain.
很多，所以没有。 去痛。
What was that? Just killjoys.
那是什么？ 简直是乐此不疲。
It was.
它是。
Yeah, that was a double killjoy grenade.
是的，那是一个双重杀戮手榴弹。
Had the alarm, but.
有警报，但是。
Archie's cheese.
阿奇的奶酪。
OK, this time. Don't think we go middle.
好，这次。 不要以为我们走中间。
I think we go.
我想我们走了。
May be my pie from Lyndsey.
可能是我从林赛买的馅饼。
Fall in from. B and look for pix.
从落入。  B 并寻找 pix。
Yeah, that's ok.
是的，没关系。
Yeah. Yeah, I like doing that. That's a good sign.
是的。 是的，我喜欢这样做。 这是一个好兆头。
Yes. So they had to do that.
是的。 所以他们不得不这样做。
We now see why they never challenged to be before with Lily.
我们现在明白了为什么他们从来没有挑战过与莉莉在一起。
Yeah.
是的。
Had to the.
不得不的。
Likes.
喜欢。
Of she's really low.
她的颜值真的很低。
Yeah. Yeah. 41 five to one.
是的。 是的。  41 五比一。
No way we lose this whole a
我们不可能失去这整个
left side.
左边。
Left side. Of.
左边。 的。
The market.
市场。
Oh no. Just one CC.
不好了。 只有一个CC。
I'm going to have I'm going to hell.
我要去有我要去地狱。
I mean that's it can't be long enough.
我的意思是它不能足够长。
To catch you.
来抓你。
Got to oh nice nice.
哦，不错不错。
Then they. Keep me.
然后他们。 留着我。
Here give me your gaming, your gaming, your gaming. Too. What do we do now?
在这里给我你的游戏，你的游戏，你的游戏。 也。 我们现在干什么？
I don't know what you doing with me remaining?
我不知道你把我剩下的做什么？
Oh, we have a flat with a plinth.
哦，我们有一个带底座的公寓。
Or the bombs down with phrases.
或者用短语炸毁炸弹。
Can I hear you loose? Tell me.
我能听到你松动吗？ 告诉我。
Let's pick together all right.
让我们一起挑选好吧。
One, two, three, peak.
一二三，巅峰。
Stick out my guys.
伸出我的家伙。
Look at about.
看一下。
I have ten different.
我有十个不同的。
Arms for. Eight more years.
武器为。 还有八年。
Does anyone have funds on this?
有人有这方面的资金吗？
I got you.
我接到你了。
You guys are pets.
你们是宠物。
I wish I.
我希望我。
Could. Have them. I don't want oh.
可以。 拥有他们。 我不要哦。
Well, I don't have a pet right now, but I'm babysitting a dog. Oh.
好吧，我现在没有宠物，但我正在照看狗。 哦。
Uh, I think it's a beagle.
呃，我觉得是比格犬。
I'm not. Sure.
我不是。 当然。
A beagle. A beagle? Yeah, a beagle.
一只小猎犬。 比格犬？ 是的，一只小猎犬。
You know.
你知道。
I love the results.
我喜欢结果。
With everything seasoning.
一切调味。
What kind of cream cheese? Something.
什么样的奶油芝士？ 某物。
Mm. Strawberry.
毫米。 草莓。
Very extraordinary. Yeah.
非常非凡。 是的。
I love strawberry.
我爱草莓。
I love honey walnuts.
我喜欢蜂蜜核桃。
You did?
你有吗？
That was terrifying.
那太可怕了。
I want to know.
我想知道。
All right, boy.
好吧，男孩。
I want. You cheese.
我想。 你个奶酪。
Goddammit, there's one.
该死的，有一个。
That comes.
那来了。
When heaven.
当天堂。
Spikes down a glass.
倒下一杯。
They are so dead
他们因被摧毁而死去。
That's when
那是什么时候
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. It's OK. It's OK.
我的天啊。 没关系。 没关系。
Hey, you stop. 15 seconds. Fucking Oh, stop
嘿，你停下来。  15 秒。 他妈的哦，停止
sakes.
看在眼里。
Oh, that's what they're doing.
哦，这就是他们正在做的事情。
Oh, my poor show to go to hell.
哦，我可怜的表演要下地狱了。
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
哦，哦，哦，哦。
What happened when I don't have any?
当我没有任何东西时发生了什么？
30 seconds left. My heart rate my heart rate went.
还剩 30 秒。 我的心率我的心率去了。
Over to one on the wall. One well, one below
到墙上的一个。 一口井，一口以下。 对。
Oh, that's right.
哦，没错。
That's pure panic.
那是纯粹的恐慌。
I think my heart rate, we hit like one E to.
我想我的心率，我们打得像一个E来。
The we still get the kill, the killjoy.
我们仍然得到杀戮，杀戮的喜悦。
Even you just got to scream.
即使你只需要尖叫。
Yeah, yeah. Scream at. Them.
是啊是啊。 对着尖叫。 他们。
Yeah. Scream for the kill.
是的。 为杀戮而尖叫。
Oh, oh, man.
哦，哦，伙计。
I took a shower before she even had to.
我什至在她不得不洗澡之前就洗了个澡。
Another shower.
另一个淋浴。
Still
仍然
I think.
我认为。
I think I'll be sailing, but don't mind me.
我想我会航行，但不要介意我。
I'll say.
我会说。
Do you think it's weird to take showers once every three days?
你觉得三天洗一次澡很奇怪吗？
No, no. No.
不，不。 不。
I mean, if you're not that oily.
我的意思是，如果你不是那么油腻。
Right? Yeah. It depends on what physical activity you're doing.
对？ 是的。 这取决于你在做什么体育活动。
No physical activity. You just sitting and playing games.
没有身体活动。 你只是坐着玩游戏。
What do you. Think? Yeah.
你是什​​么。 思考？ 是的。
And if you don't have that much oily skin, then you're killing it.
如果你没有那么多油性皮肤，那么你就是在杀死它。
Every three days.
每三天一次。
No big deal.
没什么大不了的。
I want that comic book.
我想要那本漫画书。
I just like to fast
我只是喜欢禁食
I drew a circle around that guy's head.
我在那个人的头上画了一个圈。
Also, the nice.
还有，不错。
Thing I have. Oh.
我有的东西。 哦。
Oh. She's made it.
哦。 她成功了。
She's made Raina's medal. Yeah.
她成为了雷娜的勋章。 是的。
I had Spike on me. Whoops.
我身上有斯派克。 哎呀。
Well, that's. Great.
嗯，就是这样。 伟大的。
Now he's clean, clean, clean.
现在他干净，干净，干净。
Gee. Oh, my God. Which would show where she.
哎呀。 我的天啊。 这将显示她在哪里。
Uh. She's not the kills her.
呃。 她不是杀死她的人。
It's here.
是这里。
So yeah, but it's around there. Huh?
所以，是的，但它就在附近。 嗯？
Oh. Just run. Just run. Just run.
哦。 赶紧跑。 赶紧跑。 赶紧跑。
All right?
好的？
Destroy
破坏
my plant.
我的工厂。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
He's watching me.
他在看着我。
For a piece of.
为一块。
Trash. You know, she's beaming.
垃圾。 你知道，她在喜气洋洋。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, oh, my God.
哦，哦，我的上帝。
That's right.
没错。
You got the.
你得到了。
Right angle through the a good easy.
直角穿过好容易。
Yeah, it's everywhere.
是的，它无处不在。
Colour.
颜色。
Watch was it
看是不是
everyone?
每个人？
Is that a recording? Yeah.
那是录音吗？ 是的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
But in my dream, I see you
但在我的梦里，我看到了你
I feel you.
我感觉到你了。
Oh, I reached for.
哦，我伸手去拿。
And I know. That's all I know.
而且我知道。 这是我所知道的。
I don't know any of it.
我什么都不知道。
Really looks like him frogging until.
真的看起来像他青蛙直到。
Yeah.
是的。
I knew immediately when you said I feel you instead of.
当你说我感觉到你而不是，我立刻就知道了。
I hear you on the phone.
我听到你在电话里。
You is I feel you're a hero.
你是我觉得你是英雄。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I thought I was. I always thought I saw you.
我以为我是。 我一直以为我看到了你。
Oh, that's nice.
哦，那很好。
You're not.
你不是。
Yes. Notice that.
是的。 请注意。
I hear you. And it was like, you know, that's.
我听到你了。 就像，你知道的，就是这样。
Just not made.
只是没做出来。
More, right?
更多，对吧？
Then I feel it's scary. OK.
然后我觉得很可怕。 好的。
You know.
你知道。
But then all right.
不过后来就好了。
Well, good luck. Gamers
好吧，祝你好运。 玩家不认为她有。
Is on the vandal. There's no way I could.
是在破坏者。 我没有办法。
Get in there.
进到那里去。
Go, go.
走，走。
Go, go, go, go, go, go. Go, go, go, go, go.
走，走，走，走，走，走。 走，走，走，走，走。
Oh, yes.
哦是的。
Ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈。
How is she?
她怎么样？
Not that.
不是那个。
Ok. OK.
行。 好的。
Plant plump. Purple, thank God.
植物丰满。 紫色，感谢上帝。
Is not a.
不是一个。
She. Still have any idea.
她。 还是有什么想法。
How. She might be walking?
如何。 她可能会走路？
Yeah, she might be
是的，她可能是
something.
某物。
Nothing.
没有。
I thought.
我想。
Would she go
她会去吗
down where a cage is?
笼子在哪里？
She might be.
她可能是。
Yeah. I'm watching amy.
是的。 我在看艾米。
Amy and might be exposed.
艾米，可能会被曝光。
I see.
我懂了。
And Tierney dropped just yet, so
而蒂尔尼刚刚下降，所以
I think we went.
我想我们去了。
Yeah, well, I'm pushing.
是的，好吧，我正在推动。
Yeah, I think they're saving the arm.
是的，我认为他们正在拯救手臂。
That's probably why.
这大概就是为什么。
Uh, OK, Ron.
嗯，好的，罗恩。
No. No, no.
不不不。
I should have ran faster.
我应该跑得更快。
No, earlier
不，之前是可以的。
It's OK.
没关系。
You carry on the will.
你继续遗嘱。
For both of us.
为了我们俩。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Every home that needs you sons.
每个需要你儿子的家庭。
You be.
你是。
Can I ask why you decide to name him Twinkie, by the way? Oh.
顺便问一下，你为什么决定给他取名 Twinkie？ 哦。
No. We the another name.
不，我们是另一个名字。
Is that why?
这是为什么？
And then.
进而。
Jeffrey, this is Jeffrey Starr.
杰弗里，这是杰弗里·斯塔尔。
Has, like, the Pomeranian.
有，像，博美犬。
Nice.
好的。
Colouring is like similar.
着色就像相似。
So, I mean, did you
所以，我的意思是，你有没有
yeah.
是的。
He was doing something awesome.
他正在做一件了不起的事情。
Doomed from birth and lots that women.
从出生就注定和很多女人。
Had a to have.
有一个。
Oh say it's clear.
哦说清楚了。
Oh yeah. Yeah. What the heck.
哦耶。 是的。 有没有搞错。
Oh nice
不错哦
oh it's me.
哦，是我。
What's my is.
什么是我的。
Rebecca site now.
丽贝卡网站现在。
My wall is coming down.
我的墙要倒了。
Just the good
只是好的
I'm from.
我是从。
Oh nice
不错哦
oh market market.
哦市场市场。
One enemy remaining.
剩下一个敌人。
Is a market for sure.
肯定是市场。
I can uh oh OK.
我可以哦哦好的。
F-k oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Oh OK.
哦好的。
Yeah. Hi.
是的。 你好。
It was clear. Let's go. OK. Yeah.
这很干净。 我们走吧。 好的。 是的。
That's not so good.
那不是很好。
When you know.
当你知道。
I mean.
我是说。
Yeah, come on. On f k yourself. Oh, my god.
是啊来吧。 在 f k 你自己。 我的天啊。
Two of the left.
左边两个。
No. Oh.
不，哦。
Oh, I guess we have to play.
哦，我想我们必须玩。
One more after all.
毕竟再来一张。
Yes. It's not a real winner.
是的。 它不是真正的赢家。
Just have to. Absolutely.
只是不得不。 绝对地。
Another when I. Was already 11.
另一个我已经 11 岁了。
Today we're going to lose anyway, right? Yeah.
今天我们无论如何都会输的，对吧？ 是的。
They were going to lose anyway.
反正他们会输的。
As I was, like, quit a little more.
就像我一样，放弃一点。
He will be free.
他将获得自由。
And I'm going to pick them.
我要挑选它们。
And they were going to lose anyway.
无论如何，他们都会输。
There's no one watching MIT or not.
没有人在看 MIT。
There's no one not being so sad.
没有人不那么悲伤。
There's no one here.
这里没有人。
Yeah. Maybe they just maybe.
是的。 也许他们只是也许。
They stocks a on your head.
他们在你头上放了一个。
I just realised I have a thing.
我才意识到我有一件事。
That was embarrassing.
那很尴尬。
Oh it was tactical setting them up to be more confident.
哦，这是让他们更有信心的战术。
I like the city where city girl city.
我喜欢城市女孩所在的城市。
Is feeling safe.
感觉很安全。
Mind you love.
留心你爱。
Side by side of city know.
并肩的城市知道。
I know.
我知道。
That's why I got that going.
这就是我这样做的原因。
I was just like, no, this was fun.
我就像，不，这很有趣。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Oh, my God, I forgot to order.
哦，我的上帝，我忘记订购了。
Nice cider, right?
不错的苹果酒，对吧？
No, I did. Yeah.
不，我做了。 是的。
Oh, right.
啊对。
There you go.
你去吧。
Run at them enough and eventually they'll fall.
向他们奔跑，最终他们会跌倒。
For vandal.
对于破坏者。
Match points.
匹配点。
Let's put them in
让我们把它们放进去
I feel I actually do feel kind of bad because they don't have two people right.
我觉得我确实感觉有点糟糕，因为他们没有两个人对。
OK, come on.
好的，来吧。
Time to make is fair. Ref
制作时间是公平的。 参考
so afk with me.
所以我很喜欢。
OK, I'll just sit here with my gun. OK.
好吧，我就拿着枪坐在这里。 好的。
You guys got this.
你们得到了这个。
OK. OK, if there we sit. A you guys can push me.
好的。 好的，如果我们坐在那里。 你们可以推我。
All right? I said I'll believe you.
好的？ 我说我会相信你的。
But i already told them knife fight.
但我已经告诉他们刀战了。
Yeah. You know, not fight it. Yeah, you're right.
是的。 你知道的，不要打架。 是的，没错。
I fight. Fight. Fight.
我打架。 斗争。 斗争。
Fight, fight.
战斗，战斗。
Fight. Oh, my god. They're shooting. They're shooting.
斗争。 我的天啊。 他们在射击。 他们在射击。
They're shooting a knife fight.
他们正在进行一场刀战。
They're shooting a few wars.
他们在射击。 他们正在打几场战争。
You are very.
你很。
Oh, this is so sad.
哦，这太可悲了。
Yeah, what you're hearing. What the hell is.
是的，你所听到的。 到底是什么鬼。
He yelling at a knife?
他对着刀大喊大叫？
I oh, my gosh.
我哦，我的天哪。
Abilities are ok. OK.
能力还行。 好的。
So pauses
所以停顿
oh, man.
天啊。
I'll go flank him on the phone. Come watch this.
我会在电话里陪他。 来看看这个。
Big shots. Big shots.
大招。 大招。
I think is going to play the runaway game until they have to.
我认为在他们不得不玩之前，我会一直玩失控的游戏。
We have to buddy. Me on mom.
我们必须伙计。 我对妈妈。
Oh, never mind.
哦，没关系。
Backs down when I leave you on here.
当我把你留在这里时，我会退缩。
Oh, like a tripod or something.
哦，像三脚架什么的。
Oh, yes.
哦是的。
Yeah, yeah. That was fun.
是啊是啊。 那很有趣。
Thanks for playing, Lily. Appreciate it.
谢谢你玩，莉莉。 欣赏它。
I'm going to be real awkward now. Here
我现在会很尴尬。 我可以在这里吗？ 妈的。 对不起。
Can you what?
你能做什么？
Oh. Can I can I can I add you?
哦。 我可以加你吗？
Oh, yeah. Yeah, go ahead.
哦耶。 是的，继续。
Yeah, I think I don't have my auto reject on right now.
是的，我想我现在没有自动拒绝。
Yeah, I don't feel free to add me.
是的，我不放心加我。
OK, hold on.
好的，稍等。
There's an auto reject.
有自动拒绝。
Yeah, I turned mine off.
是的，我把我的关了。
Yeah, in the settings you could auto reject friend request.
是的，在设置中你可以自动拒绝好友请求。
Oh, for Bellerin.
哦，对于贝莱林。
Yeah, all I can do that.
是的，我只能这样做。
All I need to do that sometime. OK.
我需要做的只是某个时候。 好的。
That's pretty useful.
这非常有用。
Yeah.
是的。
If you're free to add you or is that easier.
如果您可以自由添加您或者更容易。
Just to add them?
只是为了添加它们？
Right. Maybe
对。 也许
how do I
我如何
oh, i don't think I can.
哦，我不认为我可以。
Wah wah.
哇哇。
Wah wah. Pad anyone. What the heck?
哇哇。 垫任何人。 有没有搞错？
Those are good games, by the way.
顺便说一句，这些都是好游戏。
I hope you guys enjoyed that are going to watch on right now.
我希望你们喜欢现在正在观看的内容。
Click your name.
点击你的名字。
How to.
如何。
I'm on the phone right click some people's names. Either way. How do I.
我在电话里右键点击一些人的名字。 无论哪种方式。 我如何。
Yeah, I had that same issue for some reason
是的，由于某种原因，当我这样做时，我遇到了同样的问题，就像它不允许我添加一些人一样。
Oh, now it's us.
哦，现在是我们。
Oh, I know, I know. Auto reject wrangler.
哦，我知道，我知道。 自动拒绝牧马人。
Where is off. Huh?
哪里没了。 嗯？
Well, maybe you try just typing your yeah.
好吧，也许你试着只输入你的是。
ID yeah. Manually.
身份证是的。 手动。
OK, yeah. Let me try that.
好的，是的。 让我试试。
By the way, for you.
顺便说一句，为你。
Do you want to keep going after this
你是想继续这件事，还是你完成了我能做的工作，我可以继续做下去。
Yeah, I can keep. Going and after I there.
是的，我可以保留。 我去那里。
Yeah I. Cool.
是的，我很酷。
I can keep going there. Yeah.
我可以继续去那里。 是的。
Nice is going to be a long night.
尼斯将是一个漫长的夜晚。
Oh OK.
哦好的。
I think I had a lot.
我想我有很多。
Oh, thank you.
哦谢谢。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's play again next time.
下次再玩吧。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
Thank you for agreeing to collab with me.
感谢您同意与我合作。
It means a lot more.
这意味着更多。
It was really fun.
这真的很有趣。
Let's do it again. I'll feel to the next time.
让我们再来一次。 下次还会有感觉。
I swear.
我发誓。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
We should do league next time because you said you want to do league.
我们下次应该做联赛，因为你说你想做联赛。
I'm also feeling like sometimes. Oh, boy. League.
我有时也有这种感觉。 好家伙。 联盟。
All. Play league.
全部。 玩联赛。
I play league.
我打联赛。
I don't know if.
我不知道如果。
Yeah, barely. Barely.
是的，勉强。 仅仅。
Oh, I don't. Mind.
哦，我没有。 头脑。
I'm there to learn.
我在那里学习。
Guys. We could play amongst us. Oh, oh.
伙计们。 我们可以在我们中间玩。 哦，哦。
You know, I'm down for that.
你知道，我为此感到沮丧。
I haven't played amongst us in a while, so.
我有一段时间没有和我们一起玩了，所以。
The you will play with me. What?
你会和我一起玩。 什么？
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
I've tried to invite people to play amongst us,
我试着邀请人们和我们一起玩，每个人都就像，哦，我们上次玩的时候
that, people started to fight.
那，人们开始战斗。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
Come at me.
来我这。
OK, well, the
好的，好的，
when there's 15 players, it's a bit much, but if it is, it should be fine.
15人的时候，有点多，但如果是的话，应该没问题。
50 intensive. Yeah.
50 密集。 是的。
Yeah, 15 is kind of crazy, though. I
是的，不过 15 有点疯狂。 一世
All right, guys, who's going to be our fifth, or you just won't go with us for.
好吧，伙计们，谁将成为我们的第五个，否则你就不会和我们一起去。
Up to you.
由你决定。
You have anyone you can call? Yeah.
你有可以打电话的人吗？ 是的。
I have no body.
我没有身体。
No. Is is like, what time is it right now?
不，就像，现在几点了？
2 a.m. for me.
凌晨 2 点对我来说。
So I don't think anybody else is on right now.
所以我认为现在没有其他人在上。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
A better bet betting.
更好的投注。
I'm just going to click Start and see what happens.
我只是要单击开始，看看会发生什么。
All right?
好的？
Heck, yeah.
哎呀，是的。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Okay.
好的。
Oh, boy, oh, boy. Oh.
哦，男孩，哦，男孩。 哦。
I would invite, like, yeah, guys, I would invite other people,
我会邀请，是的，伙计们，我会邀请其他人，但我认为他们现在都很忙。
Like, there's already another vibrant lobby with Thor,
就像，已经有另一个充满活力的大厅有托尔，
and then I see, like, you know,
然后我看到，就像，你知道的，
there's like, two other veteran lobbies already and another one that's just.
就像，已经有另外两个老牌游说团和另一个刚刚的游说团。
Yeah, yeah, I know who's online usually at this time.
是的，是的，我知道这个时候谁通常在线。
Oh, shit. Yeah. Do you want me to post a thing and then just on.
妈的。 是的。 你想让我发布一个东西，然后就可以了。
It's one of them for you guys.
对你们来说，这是其中之一。
Make them,
使他们，
or I'm going to give them
或者我要给他们
boys night boy time, maybe.
男孩晚上男孩时间，也许。
Yeah. I don't know who else is on right now.
是的。 我不知道现在还有谁在上。
Everybody is in the UK getting crunk.
每个人都在英国得到崩溃。
Like, are you saw like what's a
就像，你看到了什么是
MC miss?
MC小姐？
Are you not?
你不是吗？
Like, all, all my friends, they're just she's over there, they're vibe.
就像，所有，我所有的朋友，他们只是她在那边，他们很有氛围。
And so I know who else is around so yeah.
所以我知道还有谁在附近所以是的。
Also my room is so sweaty.
我的房间也出汗了。
It is like super hot in my room right now.
我的房间现在超级热。
Oh my God. Like. Oh.
我的天啊。 像。 哦。
I am dripping sweat.
我汗流浃背。
All right.
好的。
Now, not really dripping, but it's like I'm feeling it, you know,
现在，不是真的在滴水，但就像我感觉到它一样，你知道，
I'm feeling it starts to hit because like,
我感觉它开始受到打击，因为就像是我的电脑。
And also the fact that's just hot here, usually I have my air conditioner on,
还有就是这里很热，通常我开空调，但声音太大了
that you guys would be able to hear it if I turn on my air conditioner.
如果我打开空调，你们就能听到。
I don't want to do that to you guys because it's like it's kind of like
我不想对你们那样做，因为这有点像
little more of
在背景中多一点点。
Mm hmm. Mm.
嗯嗯。 毫米。
Oh, we've got so many people coming in nowadays.
哦，我们现在有很多人进来。
Hello. Welcome back. Thank you. I'm sweaty.
你好。 欢迎回来。 谢谢你。 我汗流浃背。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
Like like you're not even, like, gamer so I.
就像你甚至不是玩家一样，所以我。
It's just because it's hot in my. Room right now.
只是因为它在我体内很热。 现在的房间。
Yeah. Oh.
是的。 哦。
All right. See.
好的。 看。
That sounds hot.
听起来很热。
You sound like. I'm in.
你听起来像。 我在。
Oh, bruh. Max.
哦，老兄。 最大限度。
A little bit of musk.
一点点麝香。
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I see.
哦，哦，哦，哦，我明白了。
All right. Oh. Ooh.
好的。 哦。 哦。
You two want us to leave for a little bit?
你们两个要我们离开一会儿吗？
Come back. No, no. No, no. I don't love that.
回来。 不，不。 不，不。 我不喜欢那样。
This is is this NCR? I don't know.
这就是NCR？ 我不知道。
What I pr.
我的公关。
Oh, I just muted that guy immediately. I don't know.
哦，我只是立即静音了那个家伙。 我不知道。
He was about to say, but I'm probably. I'm glad I did. Oh.
他正要说，但我可能是。 我很高兴我做到了。 哦。
I have the muted.
我有静音。
Yeah,
是的，
he's he was, was say something about the game but that about.
他是他，是说一些关于游戏的事情，但关于那个。
Oh. Yeah. Mm hmm.
哦。 是的。 嗯嗯。
All right, so listen.
好吧，听着。
Yoru.
优鲁。
Oh, yoru.
哦，哟鲁。
Yeah.
是的。
Ooh, I think I'm going to try someone else that's different.
哦，我想我会尝试其他不同的人。
See, I've been playing a lot of chamber and
看，我一直在玩很多房间和
which I try.
我尝试。
This person is hard.
这个人很难。
Every time I try to bird people, I end up flashing my team.
每次我尝试鸟人时，我最终都会闪现我的团队。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Or I flash.
或者我闪现。
Next time you can practise me a flash, you hey.
下次你可以练我一闪，你嘿嘿。
You. The millions and millions of silence.
你。 数以百万计的沉默。
That was that was too you.
那也是你。
Oh, oh, yes.
哦，哦，是的。
There you go.
你去吧。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Mm mm.
嗯嗯。
I love Apex.
我爱顶点。
I tried.
我试过。
I haven't tried it in a while. OK.
我有一段时间没试过了。 好的。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
I'm flashy
我闪到快了好吗？
All they dodged.
他们都躲开了。
Ow, ow. Ow, ow. Ow.
呜呜呜 呜呜呜 哦。
You have to wait again.
你必须再次等待。
Yeah, oh, that's fine. I know. And I love them. Right.
是的，哦，那很好。 我知道。 我爱他们。 对。
Fin? Nana fish.
鳍？ 娜娜鱼。
You might have wanted to.
你可能想要。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Bah bah bah bah bah bah.
呸呸呸呸呸。
Maybe you mute that guy.
也许你让那个人静音。
All right, we're in Haven.
好吧，我们在避风港。
This time. Hmm.
这次。 唔。
I think.
我认为。
I. Oh, my gosh.
我。哦，我的天哪。
That is the lock fade.
那就是锁褪色。
Yeah.
是的。
I like her.
我喜欢她。
She's really hot, so I like her abilities, her theme, her mechanics.
她真的很性感，所以我喜欢她的能力、主题和机制。
Is right.
是正确的。
As I was watching Alina's video,
当我在看阿丽娜的视频时，这一切都已经离开了我的大脑。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm indecisive.
我优柔寡断。
Sure.
当然。
Why not?
为什么不？
Just give an offering, like, 10 seconds
给个提议，比如，10 秒，看看他们是否想玩
along. Boy.
沿着。 男生。
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Guys, we've been shooting for, like, 3 hours.
伙计们，我们已经拍摄了 3 个小时。
That's crazy. It. And I even feel like 3 hours.
这很疯狂。 它。 我什至感觉像3个小时。
Watch.
手表。
See, this will have, like, I enjoy playing games like this.
看，这会有，就像，我喜欢玩这样的游戏。
I love. Her.
我爱。 她。
My brain off is kind of hot.
我的大脑有点热。
I'm down. Bed kind of semis. Like.
我不高兴。 床的半成品。 像。
As it should be.
应该如此。
Well, let's go. Oh.
好吧，我们走吧。 哦。
All right.
好的。
Burst Updraught.
爆发上升气流。
Oh, my God. Oh. OK.
我的天啊。 哦。 好的。
We've got a fifth for next game.
下一场比赛我们有五分之一。
Argh!
啊！
Oh, my
天啊
why did I read that, Chad?
乍得，我为什么读到这个？
Because I wanted to.
因为我想过要。
Chewy Amino is a big boy.
Chewy Amino 是个大男孩。
What was he doing?
他在做什么？
Yeah. Yeah, you got to.
是的。 是的，你必须这样做。
You got to let them know, you know?
你必须让他们知道，你知道吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Keep them not expecting things.
让他们不要期待事情。
Not expecting.
不期待。
Things.
事物。
And even though it was barely English, it sounded fancy.
尽管它几乎不是英语，但听起来很花哨。
It's something quite fancy. Oh.
这是一件很花哨的事情。 哦。
I like like, the one off.
我喜欢喜欢，一关。
I'm exposed.
我暴露了。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
There you are, bitch.
你来了，婊子。
Just like my chair.
就像我的椅子一样。
Yeah.
是的。
You exposed them.
你暴露了他们。
Oh, gosh.
哦，天哪。
I mean.
我是说。
All help.
都有帮助。
Oh, I'm sure she's all right.
哦，我相信她没事。
Nice, nice, nice. I'm low. I'm low.
不错不错不错不错 我很低落。 我很低落。
Yeah.
是的。
She's back site, back site, back site.
她是后场，后场，后场。
Oh, one.
哦，一个。
One coming out of. Garage madness. Down. Me.
一个出来。 车库疯狂。 向下。 我。
Oops. Well, yeah, there's one.
哎呀。 嗯，是的，有一个。
There's one front.
有一个正面。
Kills them and keep them in our garage.
杀死他们并把他们留在我们的车库里。
She's on grass. She's on grass. Right now. Yeah.
她在草地上。 她在草地上。 现在。 是的。
Oh, oh, oh, no.
哦，哦，哦，不。
She's right outside. Bucky, look, you got this
她就在外面。 巴基，看，你明白了
fighting
斗争
he's.
他是。
Oh, he's just one girl.
哦，他只是一个女孩。
I think she's fun, right?
我觉得她很有趣，对吧？
Or she might, you know.
或者她可能，你知道的。
Oh, a little.
哦，有一点。
He's. Oh, give me that.
他是。 哦，给我那个。
Whatever happens.
无论发生什么。
Shocking who.
震惊谁。
Saquon was. I'm
萨昆是。 我猜。
guessing.
不要恐慌
you know, Turkish?
你知道吗，土耳其人？
Heck, no. Oh.
见鬼，不。 哦。
It's just.
这只是。
She's like, whatever happens, Tarquin, don't panic.
她就像，无论发生什么，塔昆，不要惊慌。
I guess. You know, that sounds about right? Yeah.
我猜。 你知道，这听起来对吗？ 是的。
Oh, it's like hunkering down the tartar.
哦，这就像蹲在牙垢上一样。
Groom.
马夫。
Where he keeps all the rest.
他把所有的东西都放在哪里。
Do think I've never watched that movie?
你以为我没看过那部电影吗？
You can't really like three.
你不能真的喜欢三个。
He no one watched Lion King. Why? Why?
他没有人看过狮子王。 为什么？ 为什么？
You mean I just never.
你的意思是我从来没有。
Watch it in biology? Really?
看生物学？ 真的吗？
Hospital stuff.
医院的东西。
Got that one of those, like, end of the school deals.
得到了其中一个，比如学校交易的结束。
They just let you watch a movie for the fun of it?
他们只是为了让你看电影的乐趣吗？
For me, it was.
对我来说，确实如此。
So it's also the circle of life.
所以它也是生命的循环。
You got to pick
你必须选择
what are we doing?
我们在做什么？
What's up, gamers?
怎么了，游戏玩家？
As a couple running through garage, so I'm just waiting. Whoa.
作为一对穿过车库的夫妇，所以我只是在等待。 哇。
Yeah. Nice one. Nice.
是的。 好一个。 好的。
There was at least one more in the.
至少还有一个。
Last time I saw you out with.
上次我看到你出去。
Yeah, let's go see. Let's. Let's see.
是的，我们去看看。 让我们。 让我们来看看。
Oh, oh, my God.
哦，哦，我的上帝。
What?
什么？
Just be
只是
I missed all my shots.
我错过了所有的镜头。
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
For the week. They just ignored you.
为周。 他们只是忽略了你。
Oh, yeah, they did.
哦，是的，他们做到了。
What was that?
那是什么？
It was fine. They were fine.
很好。 他们很好。
Oh, yeah. Breslin's one, and he's really low.
哦耶。 布雷斯林的一个，他真的很低。
He's really, really, really low.
他真的，真的，真的很低。
He's out of. Sight.
他出去了。 视线。
Wow. He's just good, though.
哇。 不过，他只是很好。
Yeah.
是的。
Ok. OK.
行。 好的。
Nice, nice.
好好。
Wow. My aim.
哇。 我的目标。
It's ok. I missed my shots to.
没关系。 我错过了我的镜头。
See. And you're not screaming. So
看。 而且你没有尖叫。 所以
true. No.
真的。 不。
Longer shoe and shot for one spectating.
更长的鞋子和一次观看的镜头。
You've nobody saw a thing.
你没有人看到任何东西。
Oh, well, yeah.
哦，嗯，​​是的。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
No worries.
不用担心。
Like no, no, no. Matata. Exactly.
就像不，不，不。 马塔塔。 确切地。
You know. I'm. It's not a.
你知道。 我是。 它不是一个。
Knock me out exam.
淘汰我考试。
I think we should go, actually, to see fall again.
我想我们应该去，事实上，再次看到秋天。
Like the falling.
如同坠落。
Oh, they got up. Oh.
哦，他们起来了。 哦。
What a
什么
well see anyone see
好看到有人看到
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Thank you for the 100 gifts
感谢您提供的 100 件圣物，应该引起北欧人的愤怒。
Is too much to it
太过分了
it's.
它的。
Been going.
一直在走。
Oh yeah.
哦耶。
I want is here.
我要的就在这里。
But to 60 on faith
但是到60的信仰谢谢你。
One enemy.
一敌。
You gotta you somebody gets up.
你得有人起来。
01 20 mike down. 09
01 20 迈克下来。  09
and you guns and your guns.
还有你的枪和你的枪。
00 hockey.
00 曲棍球。
Oh there's so many buckets.
哦，有这么多桶。
I spoke to me for a second.
我和我说了一会儿。
04 years old.
04岁。
Maybe we can do faster a.
也许我们可以做得更快。
Week.
星期。
Faster.
快点。
How. I can Dashon and Zaha try and get a pick
如何。 我可以让 Dashon 和 Zaha 尝试挑选
and do that pick someone to try usually fades, throw a crazy
并且做那个选择某人尝试通常会褪色，抛出一个疯狂的
usually why they throw something
通常他们为什么扔东西
like throws a whatever she knows a line-up just hits everybody.
就像扔一个她知道的东西一样，一个阵容只会击中每个人。
Find you
找你
oh, that's a decoy.
哦，那是诱饵。
That's a decoy. Oh, that is a decoy.
那是诱饵。 哦，那是诱饵。
I killed a real one.
我杀了一个真正的。
To help help
为了帮助
you reloading and.
你重新加载和。
Planting.
种植。
There's one behind us.
我们后面有一个。
DTP back or the Dallas to flank.
DTP 后卫或达拉斯侧翼。
To flank. Yeah, I'm scared. I'm watching short.
侧翼。 是的，我很害怕。 我看短了。
Was it serious?
严重吗？
Was this called
这叫
sewers?
下水道？
Yeah.
是的。
Where are you? Me?
你在哪里？ 我？
This one coming in from my side.
这个是从我这边进来的。
Oh, yeah. City
哦耶。 城市
oh. When?
哦。 什么时候？
Long before.
很久之前。
What happened?
发生了什么？
When we got so nice.
当我们变得这么好。
Nice, nice.
好好。
Job, guys. Nice to.
工作，伙计们。 很高兴。
Take game.
拿游戏。
Let's not.
不要吧。
I can buy for someone. I'm about to max out.
我可以给别人买。 我快到极限了。
So sure you can sell your gun and I can buy for you.
所以确定你可以卖掉你的枪，我可以为你买。
Oh, thanks.
哦谢谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Yeah.
是的。
That was a all right.
那没关系。
Good, good hold.
好，好抱。
Yeah.
是的。
Now what we do where we go.
现在我们去哪里做什么。
Let's fly.
让我们飞。
Garage to see.
车库看。
Garage hell, yeah.
车库地狱，是的。
That got.
那得了。
Who's next?
下一个是谁？
Oh, my. Wow.
天啊。 哇。
Walked right into me.
径直走进我。
Yeah. Yo,
是的。 哟，硫磺。 接下来。
Oh. Oh, my God.
哦。 我的天啊。
Oh, what a ride.
哦，多么美妙的旅程。
I got rattled.
我慌了。
Yeah. No, no, okay.
是的。 不，不，好的。
Leave it to me. Oh, rock them up.
交给我。 哦，让他们振作起来。
Oh, I can.
哦，我可以。
I can buy for you.
我可以给你买。
I can have knives
我可以有刀
Maybe he heard that.
也许他听到了。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Oh, he all team.
哦，他全队。
Member. He did. Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what. I think.
成员。 他做到了。 耶耶耶。 就是这样。 我认为。
He has his own credit card.
他有自己的信用卡。
I think he cleared, by the way, whatever.
顺便说一句，我认为他清除了。
No, but always flanks.
不，但总是侧翼。
Well off and fade.
好和褪色。
Yeah, we'll throw her tree down.
是的，我们会把她的树扔掉。
It mean.
它的意思是。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God, bro. Both of them flanks.
哦，天哪，兄弟。 两人都是侧翼。
That's crazy.
这很疯狂。
You know, bonzie
你知道，邦齐
calm down.
冷静下来。
One week.
一周。
There's an app on my body
我的身体上有一个应用程序
from that window.
从那个窗口。
Oh, she's right there. 40
哦，她就在那儿。  40
oh, you hear her?
哦，你听到了吗？
Nice balance.
不错的平衡。
Oh, she knew where I was, but it's okay.
哦，她知道我在哪里，但没关系。
I think Chamber has her.
我认为Chamber有她。
Know I think you should move it.
知道我认为你应该移动它。
All you got think you
所有你认为你杀了它。
Ow! Ow!
哦！ 哦！
Ow! Ow! OK, we can get.
哦！ 哦！ 好的，我们可以得到。
Offended. OK?
冒犯了。 好的？
OK. Well, Sam.
好的。 嗯，山姆。
Can you send the thing? Yeah. That's convenient.
可以寄东西吗？ 是的。 那很方便。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
All right.
好的。
We're getting fish in here.
我们在这里钓到鱼。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
OK, fish.
好的，鱼。
In a fish. Wow, that was really good.
在一条鱼。 哇，那真是太好了。
I guess we just. We stopped them.
我想我们只是。 我们阻止了他们。
We use the restroom real quick.
我们使用洗手间真的很快。
OK, if you're not a.
好吧，如果你不是。
Where the hell are we?
我们到底在哪里？
If you know?
如果你知道的话？
Oh, this is the jaws, the valour nerd survey play.
哦，这是下巴，勇敢的书呆子调查剧。
Finn. Hannah, where are we?
芬恩。 汉娜，我们在哪里？
This is such a different world.
这是一个如此不同的世界。
Oh, well, you know what it is.
哦，好吧，你知道它是什么。
Place
地方
what are you.
你是做什么的。
Are you high?
你高吗？
I thought it was a private group.
我以为是私人团体。
Call me oh.
叫我哦。
Oh. Honestly, we could've moved, but, I mean, I'd like.
哦。 老实说，我们本来可以搬家的，但是，我的意思是，我愿意。
We can check. Em on already.
我们可以查。 已经开始了。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
She went to the bathroom, so wait a bit so far.
她去了洗手间，所以请稍等一下。
Hello, everybody.
大家好。
Hello, Hop. Oh, OK.
你好，霍普。 哦好的。
We generate alerts. Gosh, it is.
我们生成警报。 天哪，是的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Right? Yeah.
对？ 是的。
I don't normally scream at this time. The
我通常不会在这个时候尖叫。 这
house chatter on right now.
现在开始聊天。
Uh, what's up with you guys?
呃，你们怎么了？
Doing?
正在做？
I am good.
我很好。
I'm thrilled.
我很激动。
You know, I'm really feeling it, like, unironically.
你知道，我真的感觉到了，就像，讽刺地。
I'm really feeling it right now. Are you feeling it, Mr. Kraft?
我现在真的感觉到了。 卡夫先生，你感觉到了吗？
Yes, I'm feeling it's SpongeBob. Patrick.
是的，我感觉它是海绵宝宝。 帕特里克。
I don't know who both of them say it's on.
我不知道他们俩说的是谁。
They just got out of a very intense
他们刚刚摆脱了一个非常激烈的
reading session.
读书会。
So in.
所以在。
Final Fantasy.
最终幻想。
Like brain drain right now,
就像现在的人才流失，
brain drain
人才流失
how long have you guys been playing?
你们玩了多久了？
Ah, it's been, like, three and a half hours already, but I'm still feeling good.
啊，已经过去三个半小时了，但我仍然感觉很好。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I'm enjoying two rounds ago.
是的，我很享受两轮前的比赛。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
Oh, she's been screaming for 3 hours. OK.
哦，她已经尖叫了三个小时了。 好的。
Also, hold on. Give me some.
还有，等一下。 给我一些。
Ah. Oh, my God.
啊。 我的天啊。
I missed out on a lot of subs.
我错过了很多潜艇。
Hold on. Give me a second. Anything.
坚持，稍等。 你稍等一会儿。 任何事物。
You are the 100 bitties.
你是那100个小东西。
Enzo. Gail, thank you for the nine gifts sinners.
恩佐。 盖尔，谢谢你给罪人的九份礼物。
Thank you for the big gifts. I know again, that means a lot.
谢谢你的大礼物。 我又知道了，这意味着很多。
Appreciate it, stacy.
欣赏它，斯泰西。
Thank you for the 100 bits.
谢谢你的100位。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you and all.
谢谢大家。
Thank you for there's a lot of results today, guys. Thanks for all the results.
谢谢你们，今天有很多结果，伙计们。 感谢所有的结果。
And I am thank you for the honour till I'm back out.
在我回来之前，我感谢你的荣誉。
All back to work.
都回去工作了。
Have a great time. Fog.
玩得开心。 多雾路段。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
By the way, for people that don't know,
顺便说一句，对于不知道的人，
I have a video that's going to be posted on billy.
我有一个视频将发布在比利上。
Billy soon, I think like, like 6 hours from now or something.
比利很快，我想，就像从现在起 6 小时之类的东西。
I don't know.
我不知道。
There's a video asking to be posted
有一个视频要求在那里发布，我应该诚实地发一个帖子。
But I did make a proper intro video because I felt like, OK.
但我确实制作了一个合适的介绍视频，因为我觉得，好吧。
Wolf, Wolf, Wolf isn't going to, like, make sense for some people.
Wolf，Wolf，Wolf 对某些人来说是没有意义的。
That's on that site. So yeah,
那是在那个网站上。 是的，
I mean, tell me
我的意思是，告诉我一些你知道的，也许对于另外
something that's, you know, understandable also maybe for another 10,000 bits there
10,000 位也可以理解
and lending it to 001 gives sobs and yummy thank you for the 5000 bits as well.
把它借给 001 会让人啜泣和美味，谢谢你的 5000 比特。
And Zion thank you for the 700 bits. And
锡安感谢您提供的 700 位。 和
so yeah I think of it it's Elmo
所以是的，我认为它是 Elmo
thank you guys.
谢谢你们。
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢你。 谢谢你。
I'll be enjoying the shrimp so far.
到目前为止，我将享受虾。
I didn't I don't get to talk to you much, but I am just,
我并没有和你聊太多，但我只是，你知道的，现在我很享受自己的勇气和迄今为止我的朋友们。
So it's very chill vibes hours
所以这是非常寒冷的时刻
and I'm relaxing.
我很放松。
I'm relaxing right now.
我现在很放松。
Also smiley thank you for the 531 gift subsidy.
也笑脸感谢531礼品补贴。
Appreciate it. I'll come.
欣赏它。 我会来。
Home.
家。
Now. We're just gone.
现在。 我们刚刚走了。
Pew, pew, pew. And I'm having a great time doing that.
皮尤，皮尤，皮尤。 我在这方面玩得很开心。
OK, let me see.
好的，让我看看。
Match found.
找到匹配。
Yet, right?
然而，对吧？
Oh, you go.
哦，你去。
Oh, that's good.
哦，那很好。
Are you. Buying guess?
你是。 买猜猜？
Yeah. I was thinking about it.
是的。 我在想。
Maybe after this second bind.
也许在第二次绑定之后。
Uh, rain.
嗯，雨。
The rain? Mm.
雨？ 毫米。
Hmm. Oh.
唔。 哦。
I feel like sucking.
我感觉像是在吸吮。
She does the suck
她做的很烂
well, I'm right here.
好吧，我就在这里。
Oh, whoa.
哦，哇。
God. Is bald all offer. OK.
上帝。 是秃头所有报价。 好的。
Let's get a smoker in.
让我们让一个吸烟者进来。
Thank you for the smokes.
谢谢你的烟。
I appreciate it.
我很感激。
Yeah.
是的。
That's cool.
太棒了。
You know, Line-ups on the character.
你知道，角色的阵容。
All his.
都是他的。
Brim. Yeah, as brim.
边缘。 是的，就像帽檐一样。
There's Line-ups.
有排队。
Oh, the model for the Molly.
哦，莫莉的模型。
Yeah, some are away.
是的，有些人不在了。
And then just like
然后就像
zap people if you're old, see, I think,
如果你年纪大了，就揍人，看，我想，哦，他们没有烟。 好的。
Oh. I think we'll be
哦。 我想我们会
I might be in another job or team.
我可能在另一个工作或团队。
Looks better
看起来更好
yeah.
是的。
I don't know anything
我什么都不知道
I don't know any Line-ups.
我不知道任何阵容。
I just check it chicken and pray.
我只是检查一下鸡肉并祈祷。
You don't me to.
你不要我给。
I wish I knew Line-ups on the.
我希望我知道上的阵容。
I feel like I always watch a video, but then I just don't absorb it.
我觉得我总是看视频，但我就是不吸收它。
This is a such a cute sticker. What the. Hell?
这是一个非常可爱的贴纸。 什么的。 地狱？
You know how that one is, really?
你知道那是怎么回事，真的吗？
So I bought it, and that's all right.
所以我买了它，没关系。
Before the battle pass ended.
在战斗通行证结束之前。
I just realised I shot two at zero volume from my last fumble for the game.
我刚刚意识到我在最后一次摸索比赛时以零音量开了两枪。
Fell out.
掉出来了。
Oh, no, I'm.
哦，不，我是。
Yeah, I was asking you about, like, oh, you ready?
是的，我在问你，比如，哦，你准备好了吗？
And Final Fantasy, and then you just didn't say anything, so I was like, oh.
还有最终幻想，然后你什么都没说，所以我想，哦。
My, me oh.
我的，我的哦。
I just heard violence, and I
我刚听到暴力，我
oh, like, that is so great.
哦，就像，那太棒了。
No wonder was so quiet else.
难怪别人这么安静。
Like, so it's. Clear.
喜欢，就是这样。 清除。
That's clear. I don't see anyone. Gardens.
这很清楚。 我没有看到任何人。 花园。
Oh, gone.
哦，没了。
See the corner
看到角落
we come.
我们来。
Oh, my God. Oh, my goodness.
我的天啊。 哦，我的天啊。
We saw
我们看到了
and head shot me we're sage can be kidding.
和头部中弹我们是圣人可以开玩笑。
She's telling the truth.
她说的是实话。
OK, you won't show me who
好吧，你不会告诉我是谁
she did a running head shot.
她做了一个跑步的头部射击。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
To answer your question, the earlier shelf.
回答你的问题，前面的架子。
All I did. I was it was at all.
我所做的一切。 我就是这样。
Were you doing like, were you doing pandemonium or reason like.
你是在做，你是在做混乱还是在做类似的事情。
Yeah, pandemonium. Nice.
是的，喧嚣。 好的。
You just read my mind.
你只是读懂了我的心思。
I need to do my deal. He's
我需要做我的交易。 他还是我只为我登录或不登录。
Dailies.
日报。
I mean, like, weekly reset stuff.
我的意思是，每周重置的东西。
Yeah,
是的，
that's pretty much the only thing I do.
这几乎是我唯一要做的事情。
They pick this.
他们选这个。
I heard someone walk up there
我听到有人走上去
and let's pick it together again.
让我们再一起挑选。
OK? Why do you smoke
好的？ 你为什么抽烟
oh, down. Oh.
哦，下来。 哦。
Spike down. Be nice.
秒杀。 对人好点。
And see anybody on set.
并在片场看到任何人。
I should have looked that way.
我应该那样看的。
Well,
好，
it was on.
它打开了。
I'll play elbow on the left.
我会在左边打肘部。
Oh, Dixie.
哦，迪克西。
Next film I shot
下一部我拍的电影没有。 好的。
You nice.
你真好。
Nice.
好的。
We got one enemy.
我们有一个敌人。
All was lost.
一切都丢失了。
I like how you called it out for yourself.
我喜欢你为自己喊出来的方式。
Is. Just the case.
是。 只是这种情况。
Mike died. I'm so used to dying.
迈克死了。 我已经习惯了死亡。
I still go.
我还是去吧。
Ice. It.
冰。 它。
Normally, if I see something, it's like, oh, no, I'm dead.
通常，如果我看到某些东西，就像，哦，不，我死了。
Who thought leave to me?
谁想离开我？
All of them up and.
他们都起来了。
I mean, he's been working. I like being.
我的意思是，他一直在工作。 我喜欢存在。
Just keep doing it, right? Yeah.
继续做，对吧？ 是的。
Good. Oh, I see. I love pussy tail.
好的。 我懂了。 我喜欢猫尾巴。
Banana nose.
香蕉鼻子。
That's always the choice between the pussy in the arse.
这总是在屁股猫之间的选择。
You're a I mean, you want oh.
你是我的意思，你想要的哦。
Wow. Both of you are here.
哇。 你们两个都在这里。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, in the corner. Oh.
哦，在角落里。 哦。
Yeah. Oh, there goes my love.
是的。 哦，我的爱人来了。
He was given
他被赋予
a reminder.
提醒。
Oh, citybeat.
哦，城市节奏。
You TV? Like, tell me.
你电视？ 喜欢，告诉我。
How I can stand as guardian Batman.
我如何能成为守护者蝙蝠侠。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, nice to oh.
哦，不错哦。
Oh, that coming from behind.
哦，那是从后面传来的。
Yeah.
是的。
All you're living you're living
你所过的一切，你都过得很好。 哦，哦，你疯了。
You're cracking contracts
你在撕毁合同
out OK.
出来好了。
Oh, my God. Nice title.
我的天啊。 不错的标题。
I don't know if she's on site, though.
不过，我不知道她是否在现场。
But see,
但是看，
nice. I like it. Good part.
好的。 我喜欢。 好的部分。
Five. It like that.
五。 就是这样。
Yeah.
是的。
If I've had yes.
如果我有的话。
Tell them with mine. Yes.
用我的告诉他们。 是的。
Such a thick, balding brain right now.
现在这么厚，秃头的大脑。
Yeah.
是的。
I thought you were going to start that ball.
我以为你会开始那个球。
It's like, undulating, all
它就像，起伏的，所有
thick.
厚的。
I'm jumping all over the place.
我到处跳。
I'm very.
我很。
Familiar with the.
熟悉的。
Funky yes.
时髦是的。
Don't explain
别解释
it. Doesn't explain what?
它。 不解释什么？
Yeah.
是的。
You're right.
你说的对。
Oh, you're right. Yeah.
哦，你是对的。 是的。
She come through showers.
她是通过淋浴来的。
Now then.
接着。
You could all go for that.
你们都可以去。
I oh, we like.
我哦，我们喜欢。
Yeah, she's really stuck.
是的，她真的被困住了。
Oh, just. To knock them out of it.
哦，只是。 把他们赶出去。
I think so. Aussie would I.
我认同。 澳洲我会。
I just didn't think she'd.
我只是没想到她会。
Oh, I miss my lines.
哦，我想念我的台词。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Me know that that was, that was, was like type.
我知道那是，那是，就像类型。
Oh I can buy. I. Here.
哦，我可以买。 一、这里。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, so dumb. Wow.
哦，太笨了。 哇。
Now you try. To step it up.
现在你试试。 加强它。
You have to. Yeah.
你必须。 是的。
I thought like I another lie.
我想我又是一个谎言。
I thought contesting them. Knock them off of it too hard.
我想与他们较量。 用力把他们赶走。
I didn't know that.
我不知道。
And I just my anger. Oh, my God. So cute.
而我只是我的愤怒。 我的天啊。 太可爱了。
I just thought she'd, like, tap it and then go back for a second.
我只是以为她会，喜欢，点击它，然后回去一秒钟。
Well. You're
好。 你是
trying to
尝试去
watch me, right?
看着我，对吧？
When you guys came inspired.
当你们受到启发时。
Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
I'm being cookie. Your arse is too fat.
我是饼干。 你的屁股太肥了。
Oh, sorry.
哦对不起。
Nice.
好的。
I forgot it.
我忘记了。
As clear as clear to me.
对我来说一清二楚。
OK, can try and tell for
好的，可以试着讲笑话。
jokes.
超过你的
you just one
你只是一个
of haven't. Got.
的没有。 拿到。
You catch them.
你抓住他们。
All he's low.
他的一切都很低。
Oh no he's not low. 30, 39.
哦不，他不低。  30, 39.
I couldn't do much sorry.
我不能做太多的对不起。
You it did great show tell.
你它做了很棒的表演告诉。
It's encroachment on how they.
这是对他们如何的侵犯。
Want to see you remembers that treatment.
想看你还记得那个待遇。
Oh my God I think they're ones but there might be one behind us.
哦，我的上帝，我认为他们是一个，但我们身后可能有一个。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
There is some I mean
有一些我的意思不是。 向下。
The then.
那时。
Yeah probably yeah he's tucked down nice.
是的，可能是的，他的身体很好。
There we go. Shot. Good shot.
我们去吧。 射击。 好球。
My kingdom.
我的王国。
And the tree. Line.
还有那棵树。 线。
I speak for the trees.
我为树木说话。
Oh, my leaf.
哦，我的叶子。
No, no, no, no.
不不不不。
OK, I think I'll know if it's a bear.
好的，我想我会知道它是不是一只熊。
It's a pear. It's a bear.
这是一个梨。 它是一只熊。
Oh, yeah. That's my hair.
哦耶。 那是我的头发。
Yes, sunglasses. Still, I love them.
是的，太阳镜。 不过，我爱他们。
What kills. Us.
杀什么。 我们。
Could you spray.
可以喷吗
T? Yeah,
吨？ 是的，你们所有人。 他太好了。
He is really good where.
他真的很擅长哪里。
He knows exactly where to shoot.
他确切地知道在哪里射击。
Yeah, he plays outside a lot.
是的，他经常在外面玩。
OK, I'm not going to pick him ever again.
好吧，我不会再选他了。
They're there.
他们在那里。
Just got him higher.
只是让他更高。
He's blind with fear.
他因恐惧而盲目。
Boop.
嘘。
Oh, you guys are going to do
哦，你们会这样做，倒退四个月。
Lost sight.
失明。
Phoenix
凤凰
oh, you fit.
哦，你适合。
Oh, man.
天啊。
This Phoenix is so good.
这只凤凰太好了。
You know, he pops my head immediately. So
你知道，他立即弹出我的头。 所以
oh, frick.
哦，弗里克。
Oh, very nice.
哦，很好。
Yeah.
是的。
The sun is so bright.
太阳是如此的明亮。
Don't worry. Thank you.
不用担心。 谢谢你。
And those are good on there.
这些都很好。
Phoenix that ran.
凤凰那跑。
Yeah.
是的。
Got an immediate head pop and just kept going.
立即头部弹出并继续前进。
In some the poor hold on.
在一些穷人坚持。
Need to drop me too.
也需要放下我。
You know what we should probably save?
你知道我们应该保存什么吗？
Yeah, I'm saving. Yeah, for saving.
是的，我在省钱。 是的，为了省钱。
Can't buy anything right now.
现在什么都买不到。
You know what to do.
你知道该做什么。
Jokes over your dead.
拿死人开玩笑。
Jokes over.
笑话结束。
The TV.
电视。
Money just thrown sun through the.
钱刚刚被晒过。
Karaoke show.
卡拉OK表演。
I think I'm going nice wow.
我想我会很好哇。
Thanks. Is you are
谢谢。 你是
at a real gun, dammit.
在真枪上，该死的。
The only real neons tag 19.
唯一真正的霓虹灯标签 19。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Spike down a.
秒杀一个。
Beast of an over.
一个结束的野兽。
Poor what.
可怜什么。
All grab up and run now.
现在所有人都抓起来跑。
OK what's the saving round.
好的，什么是节省回合。
Yanks might be behind I don't know
洋基队可能落后我不知道，因为他正在打球。
30 seconds left.
还剩 30 秒。
All right nice nice woo. Mm
好吧，不错不错哦。 毫米
yeah.
是的。
Too many people.
太多人。
Will chatter in the. Cars and stuff.
会喋喋不休。 汽车之类的。
That's a dark line What the hell.
那是一条黑线什么的。
I'm not there she's so edgy Yeah she's.
我不在那里，她是如此前卫 是的，她是。
Really edgy.
真的很前卫。
I love.
我爱。
Like me for real for real OK.
像我一样真正的真正的好。
Yeah, man. Hmm.
是的，伙计。 唔。
That's a bit too aggressive.
这有点太激进了。
The marshal
元帅
I'm like a big that Phoenix lover.
我就像一个大凤凰情人。
I will understand fashion first.
我会先了解时尚。
Yeah. Yeah. Actually.
是的。 是的。 实际上。
My name
我的名字
you know that.
你知道的。
Oh, is that. No.
哦，是这样的。 不。
I'm not OK.
我不好。
I'm running. I'm running.
我在跑步。 我在跑步。
All right. Annie is pretty. Clear.
好的。 安妮很漂亮。 清除。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
Oh, I was at the on left area, but don't worry,
哦，我在左边区域，不过别担心，你在该区域找不到我的凤凰护航。
I'm going to I'm going to head to showers.
我要去我要去淋浴。
Oh, there.
哦，那里。
Heaven one heaven. Bike down a.
一天堂一天堂。 骑自行车下来 a。
Nice several.
好几个。
Nice. Oh
好的。 哦
thing.
事物。
This is just. Oh, my God.
这只是。 我的天啊。
Vanessa.
凡妮莎。
I didn't even know she was on heaven. That's my bad. Holly.
我什至不知道她在天堂。 那是我的错。 冬青。
I could have killed her.
我本可以杀了她。
It was kind of good on them, too.
这对他们也有好处。
Just what do you call it?
你怎么称呼它？
Lurk there.
潜伏在那里。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You all. You all you will. Not you. All.
你们。 你会的。 不是你。 全部。
30 seconds left.
还剩 30 秒。
Life remaining.
余生。
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
Last one is around you, Hall, I think.
最后一个在你身边，霍尔，我想。
Yeah.
是的。
Nice work.
不错的作品。
Shoes
鞋
Oh, no.
不好了。
So close.
很近。
Don't panic.
不要恐慌。
I can. You know, I can't buy for you.
我可以。 你知道，我不能给你买。
I don't have money. Sorry.
我没有钱。 对不起。
Oh, finance, finance.
哦，金融，金融。
Finance for you.
为你理财。
Can you meet finance?
你能遇到金融吗？
Financial finance, the vandal.
金融金融，破坏者。
The fantastic.
太棒了。
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
嘿，是的，是的，是的。
True finance.
真正的金融。
I know the credit card. Let's go.
我知道信用卡。 我们走吧。
Fight, fight. You got the money to.
战斗，战斗。 你有钱了。
Fight this swipe
对抗这个滑动
oh, my gosh.
天啊。
You lie.
你撒谎。
Oh. That's right.
哦。 没错。
Because I crouched oh, my God.
因为我蹲下哦，我的上帝。
I got a knockout punch. Oh, sorry.
我打了一拳。 哦对不起。
He comes out having, like, crouching into their head shot.
他出来了，就像蹲在他们的头部射击中一样。
Oh. Oh, yeah.
哦。 哦耶。
My life, man.
我的生活，伙计。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Left side.
左边。
Down three
下三
spike.
长钉。
Throat.
喉。
He's pulled him back in here.
他被拉回到这里。
It's all coming up. Someone's flanking. Someone's flanking.
这一切都在发生。 有人在侧翼。 有人在侧翼。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
All right there.
那里好。
It's in the on. Yeah.
它在上。 是的。
I see you bitch. Over here. Get over here.
我看你个婊子 这边。 到这里来。
You oh, shit.
你哦，妈的。
All long.
都长。
Oh, that everywhere.
哦，到处都是。
Neon went back.
霓虹回去了。
Around. Just.
大约。 只是。
All right, shoe yummy toes.
好吧，鞋子美味的脚趾。
You got this? 30 seconds left.
你有这个吗？ 还剩 30 秒。
You die. 30 seconds.
你完蛋了。  30秒。
No pressure.
无压力。
10 seconds left.
还剩 10 秒。
Open up this guy.
打开这个人。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, I got one.
哦，我有一个。
I got to say, the life you kill the mean disease.
我得说，你杀死卑鄙疾病的生命。
New friends of ours are not.
我们的新朋友不是。
As funny the non shot the other way.
同样有趣的是，非以另一种方式拍摄。
Even though she heard you from bathroom
即使她从浴室听到你的声音
yeah.
是的。
I don't know. I mean, maybe she was. Being.
我不知道。 我的意思是，也许她是。 存在。
Like, just dumb.
就像，只是愚蠢。
Oh, yeah. Hey
哦耶。 嘿，是的，我真的觉得更容易上手。
I've been able to we could just smoke off far.
我已经可以了，我们可以抽得很远。
Yeah. And split the site was fun.
是的。 拆分网站很有趣。
She smokes. OK.
她抽烟。 好的。
You all you all.
你们大家。
So she ran finding.
于是她跑去找。
Oh they're all on site.
哦，他们都在现场。
Which her
哪个她
and nice
很好
jokes 01.
笑话01。
Oh people went out.
哦，人们出去了。
He's going from San Francisco to her. OK
他要从旧金山去找她。 好的
nice.
好的。
See bring that down
看把它放下
oh nice.
不错哦。
Nice job good job.
干得好干得好。
Thanks for picking.
感谢您的采摘。
On being clean and clean.
关于干净整洁。
Let us see what's they have planned for us this time.
让我们看看他们这次为我们准备了什么。
This time this is the.
这次就是这个了。
Was it was was.
是不是。
That apathy?
那种冷漠？
Yeah. I think through. Their apathy.
是的。 我想通了。 他们的冷漠。
Character apathy, first class.
性格冷漠，一流。
And then. The
进而。 这
yeah, I actually really want that.
是的，我真的很想要那个。
You brought it to me one day. Yes.
有一天你把它带给我。 是的。
Oh, have you know how to read it.
哦，你知道怎么读吗？
You know, never
你知道，从不喜欢令人震惊的。
Honestly, the way they make it in the actual movie.
老实说，他们在实际电影中的制作方式。
I'm like,
我就像，哦，男孩。 哇。
You I blinds.
你我瞎了。
Hook smoke down.
把烟钩下来。
Ship.
船。
Oh, she's behind the bus.
哦，她在公共汽车后面。
I think and.
我认为和。
Spike down a.
秒杀一个。
Mess of have fight.
乱七八糟的打架。
Rotate OK. Oh, we have sight.
旋转确定。 哦，我们有视力。
Do we have sight? Oh, no, we don't.
我们有视力吗？ 哦，不，我们没有。
Let's take.
让我们来。
While Phoenix up in the office nah smoke 400
凤凰在办公室里抽 400
she's she's she doesn't she's not close she's not close She round up.
她是她是她不是她不接近她不接近她围捕。
Molly
莫莉
the enemy remains nice got the space.
敌人仍然很好，得到了空间。
Oh the people
哦，人们
make it.
做了。
Here.
这里。
30 seconds left.
还剩 30 秒。
Might be on heaven already.
可能已经上天堂了。
I don't know, though.
不过，我不知道。
Yeah, I think she might be right.
是的，我认为她可能是对的。
I'm going to still be.
我还是会。
10 seconds unlucky.
10秒倒霉。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Now, uh, oh.
现在，呃，哦。
Oh, no.
不好了。
And my God. Nice. Try it. Right.
还有我的上帝。 好的。 尝试一下。 对。
Oh, man.
天啊。
The hell down all right.
该死的好吧。
You Karl theory.
你卡尔理论。
Good game sense on his part, though.
不过，他的比赛感觉很好。
I was really good.
我真的很好。
Yeah. And
是的。 和
just knew those showers
只知道那些阵雨
he smelled.
他闻到了。
Yeah. Thank you. Very good. At that.
是的。 谢谢你。 很好。 那时。
Year or.
年或。
So, I can buy anything that. I bowl.
所以，我可以买任何东西。 我打碗。
Oh, damn.
哦，该死的。
By you, Utah.
由你，犹他州。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Oh, Phoenix one time. That is always.
哦，凤凰一次。 总是这样。
Love show
爱情秀
driver
司机
lightning
闪电
inside say.
里面说。
Yeah.
是的。
Not oh massive
不是哦，他妈的大量吸烟。
Exactly.
确切地。
Who knows there I'm going to play elbow all right.
谁知道我要去打肘部好了。
Oh, she's in smoke
哦，她在冒烟
gone.
走了。
Oh, my God as.
哦，我的上帝。
You just sat in the smoke what the heck
你只是坐在烟雾中
crazy
疯狂的
you know.
你知道。
Yeah.
是的。
Jumps here by the siege are you serious? Down
被围攻跳到这里你是认真的吗？ 向下
0670 stem begins down.
0670 阀杆开始向下。
And this one an elbow still
而这一个仍然是肘部
ooh ooh.
哦哦哦。
There's like another one come from that. Oh.
就像另一个来自那里。 哦。
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
哦，你一定是在开玩笑。
What the.
什么的。
OK, OK.
好的好的。
We take those. And take those.
我们拿那些。 拿走那些。
We take those easy.
我们把这些放轻松。
All those shot they can me.
所有那些射击他们可以我。
They missed everything on shoe.
他们错过了鞋子上的一切。
And we got a pistol.
我们得到了一把手枪。
A pistol?
手枪？
Yes. OK, shoot. Dog.
是的。 好，开枪。 狗。
This guy. 10 seconds. Yeah.
这家伙。  10 秒。 是的。
I think you. Still got.
我觉得你。 还有。
You will you got a.
你会得到一个。
Behind you. OK?
在你身后。 好的？
Oh, you actually go.
哦，你真的走了。
Oh, I've no time. No. No,
哦，我没时间。 不，不，哦，伙计，这感觉很熟悉。
The last round in the half.
半场最后一轮。
Oh, man. I don't have money.
天啊。 我没有钱。
We're going to spend.
我们要花钱。
Plenty of time for.
有很多时间。